Speaker 1: Not to be morbid, but my husband's dead. Oh, hey, guys. Hey, hey, hey. Welcome in. Welcome in. I got
Speaker 2: the bad cop hat on tonight. We
got the bad
Speaker 3: cop hat on tonight. You know what that means? It's
going to be one of
Speaker 3: those nights. I hope you're adjusting to daylight
Speaker 4: savings time. No one at church this morning did. There were like 10 people there. I don't think anybody's clocks changed in the middle of the night. I prepared accordingly.
I
Speaker 4: was up. I was ready to go. I was raring to go, as they say. But, man, the parking
Speaker 3: lot was empty. There were very few people present. It was crazy. It was crazy. Now, granted, I did not make it up for the 7 o'clock
because I was a
Speaker 3: little tired. Extra night plus the Australian Grand Prix last night. I don't know if you, for those who celebrate. But
I had
Speaker 3: Don the Bad Cop hat tonight because we're going to get a little bad copy at times tonight. And I didn't want to...
Speaker 3: lose my cool without some sort of warning
Speaker 5: some
sort of
Speaker 5: warning uh so this is your warning this is what you get uh we've got the attack birds in full effect out on social media and the main attack seems to be that doggone show is just too effective hilarious entertaining and truthful and so that's going to be a problem for us down the road we better start attacking that's the best i can tell
Speaker 5: Uh, so for you attackers, I say you're welcome as well. Come on in, have fun. Um, just remember, even if you're attacking the program, hit like on your way in, just click the like button, go ahead and subscribe. You're going to want to be here.
We got a big show
Speaker 3: lined up. We
got a
Speaker 3: lot to accomplish today. We've got, I even took a shower and then donned the bad cop hat.
I could have
Speaker 3: done this dirty. I could have done this dirty. Um,
Speaker 6: all right. I want to, I want to set up a couple of things here real quick.
Speaker 6: First, I want to set up sort
of from
Speaker 7: the openings where we're going for the next little while. A lot of people
are having
Speaker 7: trouble grasping the concept of a Patsy. They're having trouble with what a Patsy is. So I'm
going to
Speaker 7: give you some examples and some openings here in the near future. Tonight's one of them. We're going to talk about a Patsy, a Patsy gone wrong, a Patsy recruit that didn't quite make it. So we'll talk about that.
Speaker 7: We'll hit some other famous patsies here in the very near future, and we'll give you an idea of how this happens. I put up a map that Tim Tebow had in front of Congress last week where it had all these red
Speaker 8: dots where all the people looking at illegal images of young people. We'll just leave it there. We'll talk about illegal young people tonight a little bit.
And
Speaker 8: we'll ask questions about why do certain
Speaker 9: people always end up around illegal young people, but that's okay. We'll, we'll get to that. We'll get to that. I don't want to get ahead of myself. I don't want to get ahead of myself.
There's some confusion. There's some
Speaker 7: confusion, but we'll get there. We'll get there. But I put up the
map and
Speaker 7: it had all the little red dots where all these people allegedly
Speaker 5: are downloading illegal
things to do
Speaker 5: with children. And, and, and then there were very few blue dots. And I said, the blue dots seem to be where the,
Speaker 5: They're recruiting
Speaker 7: the patsies. They're vetting potential patsies. The red dot, obviously, is all the potential patsies in the world. If they don't turn out to be patsy material, maybe they get arrested. Maybe they get scolded. Maybe they get a slap on the
Speaker 5: wrist. Maybe they're told to shape up or ship out.
But the blue
Speaker 5: dots are the indications that the federal authorities are looking at these potential patsies, looking at these people engaged in illegal
Speaker 10: activity, in my opinion, to see can they
be
Speaker 11: utilized for nefarious purposes going forward.
So I
Speaker 11: brought that up in the last show or a couple of shows ago. And, um,
Speaker 11: And we will explore that a little more in some of our openings because the opening
Speaker 7: tonight has to do with a, I think, what was trying to be a Patsy recruiter, a Patsy recruitment gone wrong. So we'll talk about that. I also have to get into some just completely blatantly dishonest stuff that's going on. I want to tie it
to a
Speaker 7: potential national political run. And then...
I
Speaker 7: want to dig into the way past and see, are there some things that happened that maybe they're trying to hide in the past because they focus on certain things and downplay certain things. So we'll talk about that. We finally had an answer. Why is it that the Turning Point USA people are continually using Charlie Kirk's name to put out their messaging? They finally answered that question for us here in the last couple of days. It was weird when they answered it. It's obvious they knew it was a weak spot. It's obvious to me anyway. It's obvious to me that they knew this was a real problem they had on their
hands.
And so
Speaker 7: we will talk about that as well. Talk about that as well. So buckle up. Enjoy the ride. If I lose my cool on a few people tonight, just understand it's all part of the plan. That's why I put the hat on. I was trying to warn you. I like to give you a heads up of what's going to happen. Just wanted to, you know,
didn't want to
Speaker 12: hide anything from you. Didn't want to hide anything from you. All right.
Speaker 12: I do want to get into the opening statement, get into Patsy land so you guys can kind of see where it is I am
Speaker 7: potentially taking a few of these opens in the next couple of days,
maybe next
Speaker 7: couple of weeks. I don't know that I'll do one every day, but I am going to do some opens that have to do with Patsy's here in the near future.
Because again, I
Speaker 7: see people getting confused on what does he mean when he says Patsy's?
Where do
Speaker 7: these Patsy's come from? I
get a
Speaker 7: lot of questions about it. What is a Patsy? Why a
Speaker 12: Patsy?
Here
Speaker 12: at Patsy, there at Patsy, everywhere at Patsy Patsy. And so we will hopefully, through some of the openings, clarify that just, just a little bit. So tonight's open.
I hope you guys
Speaker 8: enjoy it as much as I do. Tonight's open is coming
up right now. Khalil Abu
Speaker 13: Rayyan is his name. Kabil Khalil Abu Rayyan. he was born
Speaker 13: Around 1995, two
Speaker 7: immigrant parents from Jordan, his parents had settled in the Dearborn Heights, Michigan area, a Detroit suburb known for its large Arab American and Muslim community.
He identified
Speaker 7: strongly with
Speaker 5: his Arab heritage and Muslim faith and often posted about these aspects of his life on social media.
Khalil grew up
Speaker 5: in a working class family. His father owned a pizzeria in Detroit, where Khalil eventually worked as a delivery driver.
His
Speaker 5: delivery driver job involved long late night shifts navigating desolate inner city streets, which he found both monotonous and frankly a little dangerous. So
to cope
Speaker 5: with the boredom and isolation, he frequently indulged in a bad habit. He smoked marijuana as a habit that began when he was just 17 years old. His
mental health
Speaker 5: issues surfaced early in his life at the age of 12. He confided in a teacher about a disturbing nightmare he
had in
Speaker 5: which he brought a
child.
Speaker 5: firearm to school and deployed it against classmates.
This landed him
Speaker 5: on the radar of authorities and led to a mandatory counseling session. This marked the beginning of a documented history of psychological challenges.
Throughout his
Speaker 5: teenage years, he faced fairly relentless bullying at school. This escalated into physical fights and resulted in at least three suspensions from school.
Speaker 5: He was particularly self-conscious about his physical appearance. He attended a local gym, but immediately felt intimidated by
Speaker 14: weightlifters and avoided social interactions there. Instead, he turned to online forums where he could craft a more empowered persona. By 2014, his online activity took a darker turn.
He
Speaker 14: began consuming videos produced by
Speaker 7: terrorist entities that were gaining global notoriety at the time for brutal propaganda. He posted a graphic that included graphic content on social media, including images of things like people missing their heads and the people being, frankly, burnt alive. And it was...
Speaker 7: Also, things like execution of people thrown from rooftops for their alleged deviant lifestyles. These posts were not
Speaker 12: just passive shares. He actually was commenting on them. He was retweeting videos and remarking, thanks, brother,
that made
Speaker 12: my day.
And this behavior
Speaker 12: signaled a
Speaker 5: fascination with this sort of ideology, and it was intertwined with his personal loneliness and depression.
He
Speaker 14: portrayed himself online as a menacing warrior.
And
Speaker 14: it contrasted sharply with
Speaker 5: his real-life personality and real-life insecurities.
His troubles
Speaker 5: escalated in late 2015. In
October that
Speaker 5: year, he was pulled over by Detroit police for speeding. Officers discovered a concealed.22
Speaker 14: caliber handgun, four plastic bags of marijuana,
and some
Speaker 14: sleeping pills in his car.
He was
Speaker 14: arrested and released on bond.
But the
Speaker 14: incident once again landed him on the radar of authorities. This time,
what
Speaker 14: is known as a prohibited person under federal law. Specifically, he was now known to law enforcement as an unlawful user of a controlled substance. This barred him from possessing firearms. In fact, he attempted to purchase a new firearm shortly after the arrest, but was denied due to the pending charges. Two weeks after that, he rented an AK-47 style rifle and an AR-15 style a rifle at a low full firing range,
Speaker 14: And he practiced with them, but he didn't take them
Speaker 5: home.
Around this time,
Speaker 5: in late 2015, he tweeted a photo of himself cloaked in camouflage, holding a firearm and pointing
Speaker 7: his index finger skyward.
This was a
Speaker 7: gesture often associated with support of certain terrorist groups. The caption read, and referred to
Speaker 12: Sunni tribesmen who opposed ISIS and allied with U.S.-led forces in Iraq.
These
Speaker 12: posts and others caught the attention of the FBI. The
FBI had
Speaker 12: been monitoring him since at least May of 2015 due to his social media activity. By this point, Khalil was in a state of chronic gloom. This was exacerbated by court appearances from his October
Speaker 14: arrest. He experienced suicidal thoughts and at one point purchased a rope with the intention of hanging himself.
His
Speaker 14: family later described him as a vulnerable young man, had no prior criminal history beyond a few minor infractions. They
Speaker 12: said he was shy, awkward, and desperately seeking companionship. A defense-hired psychologist assessed his risk of violence as very low and attributed his online statements to a longing for attention rather than any kind of genuine radicalization.
Speaker 12: Shortly after his tweet in late 2015, the FBI began running a sting operation on Khalil. About
a week after
Speaker 12: that post, an undercover FBI employee contacted him on Twitter. The undercover FBI employee deployed the persona GADA, G-H-A-A-D-A. GADA,
at
Speaker 7: least according to the fake profile the FBI was using, was a young Pakistani American Muslim woman from Cleveland.
Goddard
Speaker 12: described herself as a woman facing family pressure for an arranged marriage. And this resonated with
Speaker 14: Khalil's cultural background. The conversations quickly turned romantic. This
marked
Speaker 7: the first time Khalil had ever had a girlfriend. Within days, they were discussing wedding plans, even though they had never met in person. Khalil expressed overwhelming emotion in their
Speaker 12: messages. Quote, while I was driving, I started
to cry
Speaker 12: immediately.
Speaker 12: because of how happy I am to have you, end quote. Gada responded affectionately,
Speaker 15 (lower-pitched voice): quote, don't cry, my love, please. Notice the my love there used by the FBI, just in case it ever comes up in the future, in a case in Utah.
This prompted
Speaker 15 (lower-pitched voice): Khalil to reply, it's
Speaker 12: tears of joy. I never felt this way before, he added. I need you. You had me from our first tweet.
He
Speaker 12: shared visions with her of their future, including how many children he wanted to have. It mentioned that he and his father had planned to visit her in Cleveland to formalize their engagement. The
relationship built
Speaker 14: Khalil up emotionally, and it provided the companionship he craved. Messages showed his deep affection for Gada. Quote, every time I close my eyes, I see you right by me. Words can't explain my love for you.
Speaker 16: However, the FBI...
Speaker 16: abruptly ended this persona's communication gada disappeared off the
Speaker 14: face of the earth without explanation this devastated khalil it left him extremely vulnerable
but it was
Speaker 14: all part
of the
Speaker 14: plan it set the stage for the next phase of the operation because just two days after gada's immediate and sudden disappearance
Speaker 12: I'll
Speaker 7: see you
Speaker 14: next time.
Speaker 12: Another undercover FBI employee reached out under the name Janna, J-A-N-N-A-H.
Speaker 7: Janna posed as a 19-year-old Sunni Muslim woman whose husband had been killed in a Syrian airstrike while fighting for
Speaker 14: ISIS. She
had two cousins who
Speaker 14: were murdered by Shia militants in Iraq. Janna claimed to be depressed, suicidal, eager for martyrdom to avenge their losses.
And the
Speaker 14: FBI, of course, entirely fabricated this entire story. These tragic backstories were fake. They were manipulative on purpose. Their communications spanned multiple platforms, Twitter, SureSpot, Skype, Facebook, Telegram. They started around December 23rd of 2015. Khalil quickly developed feelings for Jonna, telling
Speaker 12: her, quote, it's like I knew you all my life, and I will ask you to marry me, but not now. End quote.
Speaker 12: He expressed concern for her well-being, quote, if you are
Speaker 14: sad, I am sad, end quote. He urged her to have patience and prayed for her happiness.
When Jonna steered the
Speaker 14: conversations towards violence, saying she had no desire for life and wanted to die, Khalil resisted. On December 26, just three days afterwards, she asked, what do you want from this world? He replied, honestly, I want to get married.
Speaker 14: I think if I get married, I will be happy. I'm just lonely sometimes. I want to start a
Speaker 12: family.
Later, on January
Speaker 12: 25, 2016, Jonna professed her willingness to join ISIS and give her life, if asked, and
then suggested
Speaker 16: they do it together. Khalil pushed back. You're young and confused. I don't think you know what you want. Don't do anything that will hurt
Speaker 17: you, yourself, or other people. I want us to be together.
He
Speaker 17: repeatedly tried to redirect towards marriage and a peaceful life, saying, quote, Honestly, you need to think about what you want. I can't be in this game.
Depression is
Speaker 17: real, but don't let it ruin your life.
Despite his
Speaker 14: reluctance, Khalil began sharing violent fantasies to try to impress her and maintain her attention.
He falsely
Speaker 14: claimed he had planned to shoot up a large Detroit church near his pizza shop.
I tried
Speaker 12: to once.
I
Speaker 12: don't know the name of it, but it's close to my job. It's one of the biggest ones in Detroit. Yeah, I had it
Speaker 18: planned out. I
bought a
Speaker 18: bunch of bullets. I practiced a lot with it. I practiced reloading and unloading. But my dad searched my car one day and found everything.
Speaker 12: He found the gun, the bullets, the mask I was going to wear. And he added it would have been a bloodbath and that he would kill everyone without mercy, including women and children. He
also boasted
Speaker 12: about wanting to kill the cop who arrested him in October, claiming he had a sword in his car.
It's
Speaker 12: noteworthy that FBI searches after his arrest found no AK-47, no extra bullets, no mask, and no sword. The
only weapon they
Speaker 12: found was the.22 caliber revolver that they confiscated in the traffic stop. Janna persistently pushed jihad themes. In a phone conversation shortly before his arrest, Khalil
Speaker 14: discussed his suicidal ideation, mentioning the rope.
only in
Speaker 14: like a minute or two, it'll be over. My family's going to be sad for a little while, but they'll get over it.
John
Speaker 12: encountered that suicide was only permissible in jihad. Like I told you before, when it's for the sake of Allah, when it's jihad or when it's based on our creed or for a cause, that's the only time it's allowed. But
to put your
Speaker 12: life to waste, just hang yourself like you say you want to do,
Speaker 7: that's not the right thing to do. Khalil responded by emphasizing he didn't want to hurt others or get arrested again.
so
Speaker 14: on february 4th 2016 just two days after a phone call where khalil emphatically insisted he would not harm
other people fbi
Speaker 14: agents its fbi agents
Speaker 12: arrested him they charged him with possession of a firearm by an unlawful user of controlled substances it's important to note that at the time of his february 2016
Speaker 14: arrest he did not own or possess a firearm Thank
you.
Speaker 14: Rather, the firearm for which he was arrested and possessing was the same gun police lawfully confiscated from him during his arrest in October of 2015. He was charged in October on state charges of unlawful possession of a concealed firearm. He entered a guilty plea on that charge.
And it's an
Speaker 17: inescapable reality that when it became obvious, Khalil would not be manipulated into becoming a violent individual.
It
Speaker 17: wasn't until that point that the feds arrested him and they arrested him for possessing the same gun he did not possess. It's the same gun for which the state police had already arrested him. He'd already entered a guilty plea for. And
despite the
Speaker 17: FBI's year-long investigation, they never charged him with terrorism because it became increasingly obvious over time. Khalil was, in fact, never going to become a terrorist.
He
Speaker 17: was just a lonely young man working for his dad's pizza delivery business, and he was looking for a wife. His
attorney pretty
Speaker 14: accurately summed up the FBI investigation as a mind-boggling double team of entrapment,
where the
Speaker 14: agents
Speaker 17: mercilessly manipulated Khalil by building him up with
God as
Speaker 12: romance, only to devastate him, then exploit that vulnerability with Jonna,
Speaker 12: attempting to elicit incriminating statements.
That is
Speaker 12: what happens when a patsy refuses
to become
Speaker 12: a patsy.
And that is your
Speaker 12: opening statement. I hope you enjoyed it as much as I did. I've always been drawn to that
Speaker 18: story. I've
always been drawn to
Speaker 18: that story. And the reason I'm drawn to it is I
was 21
Speaker 13: years old on 9-11.
And when
Speaker 12: everything changed, I mean, it's like the birth of Jesus, right? It kind of changed time. We talk about A.D. and B.C. time. If you say it's the year 1967, everyone on earth knows what year you're talking about. And
it kind of goes back
Speaker 12: to that time. Well, I think 2001 kind of divides time the same way. In a way, we're like,
instead
Speaker 17: of A.D., Anno Domini, 2026 now, we're like
Speaker 18: A.N., after 9-11, 25 now.
The
Speaker 18: world kind of divided
And I was
Speaker 19: 21 at the time, 46 now
And so for
Speaker 14: the vast majority of my adulthood And well past half of my life I've
sort of
Speaker 14: lived in this reality where
Speaker 14: We've
Speaker 18: been sold this bill of goods that the FBI is out there doing the right thing. They're constantly busting up terrorist
Speaker 17: attacks. They're constantly protecting us. Oh, we got to raise the level to orange. We were at yellow. Now we're orange. Okay, back to yellow. Never green. Never green. We go from orange to yellow, sometimes red. Ooh,
Speaker 18: got to go to red. Christmas is coming. Don't want you to be happy around family. Now we'll go back to orange.
You guys
Speaker 18: remember
Speaker 12: the color guide for the terrorist threat.
in
Speaker 12: the early years after 9-11. So I kind of grew up in this environment.
And at the
Speaker 12: time, it would not have dawned on me. It does now. Every time I see a case like this now, this
is the
Speaker 12: first
Speaker 20: thing I think of. But at the time, it never even dawned on me
that all of
Speaker 21: these could have just been made up.
Every one of these
Speaker 21: could have been made up.
every one
Speaker 22: of these busted threats. Oh, we got them at the last second. They were just a...
What role did you
Speaker 23: play? How
did you
Speaker 23: find this guy? How
Speaker 23: uncover this? Were you sexting him? Were
you sending
Speaker 23: him nudes? I
mean, I don't
Speaker 24: know. I don't know how they... I don't know what kind of conversations they had. They only released
Speaker 3: a few of the texts.
but
Speaker 3: something got the guy all hot and bothered. Something gets these people going. And I've constantly wondered that. It brings me back to Tyler Robinson, of course. That's one of the reasons I'm doing this series of
Speaker 25: openings on patsies and potential patsies and patsies gone wrong and patsies
who... Audio's in
Speaker 26 (lower-pitched voice): and out, really? That
must be a
Speaker 26 (lower-pitched voice): YouTube thing. It
shouldn't be in
Speaker 27: and out. It
should be
Speaker 27: steady, Eddie.
Speaker 28: I'll be quiet for three seconds.
And that might help it. Let me look at Down Detector and
Speaker 29: see if YouTube's having any trouble.
Hold, please. Yeah, a few
Speaker 30: reports. Nothing crazy, though.
There were a lot of reports about
Speaker 30: an hour ago. So
it
Speaker 31 (lower-pitched voice): may just be that YouTube's having some trouble.
Speaker 31 (lower-pitched voice): Um, but anyway, anyway,
my guess is
Speaker 31 (lower-pitched voice): based on the thing,
Speaker 32: and I've said this, and this is not the point of my show today. I'm going to go in a completely different direction, but my guess is just to tie it back in. Cause I saw people
Speaker 33: asking, my guess
is that
Speaker 33: Tyler Robinson, Lance twigs and others that they were busted on a,
uh,
If I had to
Speaker 32: guess, how did they end up in the Patsy business? My guess is they were looking at illegal activity online. Probably involving minors, if I had to guess. I
don't know
Speaker 34: that. I'm not calling them sexual deviants. I'm not saying they were looking at illegal stuff. I'm just saying my opinion, guys like that getting set up, that age,
Speaker 20: that environment, that crew, the things they were into, probably. If I had to
Speaker 1: guess, probably. Probably.
and then you
Speaker 1: get assigned an FBI agent like Khalil got assigned. And
that FBI
Speaker 1: agent infiltrates your life. And
Speaker 1: agent strings you along,
and
Speaker 20: you get more and more involved. That
FBI agent
Speaker 20: might have posed as a child and gotten them to really take explicit acts towards potentially meeting
Speaker 35: that child,
Speaker 8: in which case your life is basically over. You might as well go along with this murder plan because otherwise you're going to...
Speaker 8: Um, otherwise you're,
Speaker 36: you're going to prison for that. And that's not, that's not
going to
Speaker 36: end well for you. So that's probably my guess of what happened.
Um, but I will
Speaker 37: develop this theme as we go. I want to, I want to take the
show in
Speaker 37: a little bit different direction today because I
Speaker 11: have
deep concerns after
Speaker 11: some of the things we've uncovered and we'll talk about those tonight, but I have very deep concerns about their plans for Erica Kirk.
very
Speaker 38: deep concerns about the plans for Erica Kirk. And if we're right, if I'm right, I've got to get really bad cop with Erica Kirk. And
it can't
Speaker 38: be pretty.
And we've got to
Speaker 15 (lower-pitched voice): really evaluate her life. And I'll tell you what I mean by all that in just a little bit. But first, I want to go back to a
Speaker 13: page we keep going back to time and time again, believe it or not, because we have discovered yet even more lies on this page.
This
Speaker 39: is Erica Fransve's LinkedIn page. This is her education section. You remember last time we were together or recently, we talked about this line down here in the middle, Arizona State University, this Bachelor of
Speaker 32: Science, Political Science and International Relations. And we discovered they didn't even have an international relations major at the time. It could not have been a double major. Then we see this
Speaker 40: claim of summa cum laude here. We realized after we had to call the
Speaker 41: university and get them to forward us a copy of the program. She was, in fact, not in the program listed as summa cum
Speaker 37: laude. Well, Daisy noticed something different. She
went up here
Speaker 37: to this doctor of education, EDD Christian leadership. Also,
Speaker 42: strangely, summa cum laude, as was her juris master degree,
Speaker 43: summa cum laude, as was
her one year at
Speaker 43: Loyola Marymount. You can't graduate summa cum
laude in one
Speaker 39: year.
Speaker 37: Um, and this here, I don't, I mean, I don't know. I don't know what, what's going on here. So, but this was listed on her LinkedIn
share and
Speaker 37: LinkedIn page.
Speaker 44: So Daisy looks and says, does she really get a doctor of education? Is she Dr. Erica Kirk? Why
would she
Speaker 44: have claimed that? So
we
Speaker 7: instantly set out the way you would try to find if somebody, um,
had the
Speaker 7: degree they claim to have. First thing you do is go and see, is there
Speaker 37: a portal where we can look and see people who graduated in given years? Well, she said she graduated in the year 2022. Her
name was
Speaker 37: either France Bay or
Speaker 45: Kirk, so we can look them up both ways here.
This is
Speaker 45: all the people, no France Bayes in 2022 in Liberty University. So we'll try Kirk.
There are
Speaker 45: some
Speaker 46: Kirks.
but there are no
Speaker 46: Erica Kirks. There
are no
Speaker 46: Erica Kirks here.
Speaker 38: They're actually people who graduated with the degree she claimed as EDD in educational leadership. There's Stacey Amanda Coleman-Kirk.
Speaker 47: No relation, ladies and gentlemen. We're not the same. I'm
not related to
Speaker 47: Stacey Amanda, not that I know of.
And then Kirk
Speaker 47: Dwayne McDonald. There? Okay,
Speaker 49: yeah. No, not there.
So then
Speaker 49: you start to think, well, maybe a different year. Well, trust me, we went all through all the years. There's none
Speaker 41: there.
There's nothing
Speaker 41: in the find a graduate page. So
then you start
Speaker 50: thinking, well, what
if the
Speaker 50: LinkedIn page is fake?
What if
Speaker 50: it's not real? What if it's not really her page? If
you slide
Speaker 50: down the LinkedIn
Speaker 41: page, there's a weird entry on it. Frankly, it's weird.
And it
Speaker 41: leads me to believe somebody's trying to throw a red herring out. If
you zoom
Speaker 41: in on the Loyola Marymount, it says Bachelor of Arts Underwater Basket Weaving. Well, that's
a
Speaker 37: known fake degree. So is it possible someone's just messing with us
and that
Speaker 37: she never claimed to do this because this isn't actually her page, even though everything else seems to be pretty legitimate and even though lots of
Speaker 12: newspapers and magazines have quoted her LinkedIn page?
Like if
Speaker 12: you look in people magazine, they'll
Speaker 5: say, well, she has a double degree as stated on her LinkedIn page. But,
you know,
Speaker 5: hey, weirder things have happened.
Speaker 16: Maybe someone put it up and they faked it. Who knows?
So we dig
Speaker 16: deeper. We go farther. We
Speaker 51 (higher-pitched voice): press on. We're not satisfied with just wondering. We want to know the answer.
Bad
Speaker 41: cop. So
we go to the
Speaker 39: archives, the web archives.
Which
Speaker 39: is going to take a second to pull up because
Speaker 52: archive.org is lousy.
We'll go to the web archives. Here is a web
Speaker 40: archive from May of,
Speaker 42: what date is this? May 12, 2021. I'll pull it up so that you guys can see it as it populates.
This
Speaker 42: is the archive of her page. You can see her there on the right, some rando
Speaker 39: guy on the left. This is her page. It's ericafransve.com slash about.
And if you go
Speaker 39: down to the about page, you look at the education. Well, there it is. Liberty University, Doctorate in Education and Christian Leadership. It's
right there,
Speaker 39: plain as
Speaker 32: day. Says she's got a double major. We've already proven that we don't think that's accurate. In my opinion, that's inaccurate. So that's a lie.
I think. I'll hold off
Speaker 43: on this one for now.
But this
Speaker 7: one, I think we can establish pretty definitively she doesn't have. And I'll show you
why I
Speaker 7: think I can establish that soon.
But there it
Speaker 7: is, May. She's
Speaker 11: claiming it.
She's claiming
Speaker 11: it in May.
Well, when's the
Speaker 49: last time? Because these pages are archived every so often, right? Every so often,
Speaker 39: they'll hit a little...
they'll
Speaker 39: come by and they'll scan it and they'll see something. So it was actually archived again in November of 2022. November
of
Speaker 53: 2022, it was archived.
There's Erica
Speaker 46: Fransfay again.
Speaker 39: There's some rando dude. And
then you scroll
Speaker 39: down. There
it is right
Speaker 39: there. Doctorate of Education and Christian Leadership. It's still there.
That's
Speaker 32: her...
Speaker 32: Double major, also probably inaccurate, still there, but we're not going to focus on that one tonight. We did that one last time.
But that's the Doctorate
Speaker 32: of Education
Speaker 54: in Christian Leadership. So that's on November 14 of 2022.
November 4, excuse me, November
Speaker 55: 4 of 2022. Well, something happened in Erica's life between November
Speaker 43: 4 of 2022 and
November 4
Speaker 43: of 2022.
Speaker 43: And December 9 of 2022. I don't know what it
Speaker 13: is.
I've thought
Speaker 13: about it. I've put a little effort into it. It might be insanely obvious to you people in the audience.
You guys might get
Speaker 13: it.
Speaker 56: I don't understand what it is.
But we saw on
Speaker 45: November 4 of 2022, we saw the...
Doctorate in
Speaker 39: education, Christian leadership That's gone, ladies and gentlemen No longer is that there Now we have her
Speaker 1: website Her personal website has been updated To be the doctorate in biblical studies Current In
other
Speaker 57: words, I kind of wonder If somebody called her on it Like somebody she knows Like maybe her husband Or
someone she
Speaker 58: works with I'm trying to think of who would call her on that And say, hey, wait a minute
Speaker 21: Toots,
you don't
Speaker 21: have an EDD from Liberty University in Christian leadership. That's
not a
Speaker 21: real thing.
You should update your
Speaker 59: website accordingly. So she put this doctorate in biblical studies up there,
and it just
Speaker 59: says current.
I guess that means she's
Speaker 59: studying for it.
And
Speaker 1: so I go back to the LinkedIn page,
and I
Speaker 1: realize,
Speaker 20: yes, yes, yes, yes.
Speaker 20: Somebody put underwater basket weaving here. Maybe she did it as an inside joke. I don't know.
But you can't
Speaker 20: tell
Speaker 21: me she didn't also put that in there.
Because that right there matches what
Speaker 1: she had on her personal website, ericafransfay.com, for many
Speaker 52: years. For several years, she claimed to have a doctor of education.
an
Speaker 60: edd in christian leadership and
again when you
Speaker 60: check the liberty page
she
Speaker 38: doesn't show up as a graduate when you check
the linkedin page she claims to
Speaker 38: have it when you check
Speaker 61: her personal page she used to claim she has it now she claims she doesn't have it
things
Speaker 62: change things change and so i
At first, I
Speaker 62: thought, Barron, you're just being petty. Like, this is just
a
Speaker 20: petty approach. This is, you're picking at her for claiming to have a degree she doesn't have. Well, I'm not doing that. I'm not picking on her for claiming to have a degree she doesn't have.
I'm picking on
Speaker 58: her for having to claim, for claiming multiple degrees she doesn't have. I'm picking on her for claiming honors she doesn't
Speaker 20: have.
In
Speaker 20: other words, I'm picking on her for being a deeply dishonest human being
Speaker 16: about the most basic biographical facts of her life.
Because she
Speaker 16: wants to tell
Speaker 50: me
and tell
Speaker 50: you and tell the world
that we are to
Speaker 50: believe her when it
Speaker 5: comes to things like an alibi, where she was on the morning of September 10th,
where she was on the
Speaker 5: day of September 8th and September 9th.
We're
Speaker 5: just supposed to take her word for it. She is,
Speaker 57: after all, Erica Kirk. Well, I know that's the problem.
That's the
Speaker 57: problem. You're Erica Kirk. If you weren't Erica Kirk, perhaps I would
Speaker 63: take your word for it. If
you didn't
Speaker 63: have a documented history of lying about the most mundane
Speaker 1: things in your life,
maybe I would take you at
Speaker 1: face value.
But
Speaker 1: when every single thing I dig into,
Speaker 64 (higher-pitched voice): you just barely scratch the surface of it and an entire chasm of fraud opens up and we almost practically fall into it. It's
like a
Speaker 64 (higher-pitched voice): cartoon. You know, in the old cartoons, they would go out on the cliff and then the cliff would fall out and they would all fall down to the ground. That's
what her
Speaker 51 (higher-pitched voice): life feels like. Nothing's real. It's all fiction. It's a completely fake story. And
I'll tell you why
Speaker 51 (higher-pitched voice): that bothers me in just a second.
I'm not
Speaker 65: there yet. I
don't want to get
Speaker 65: there yet. Because the next thing I want to do is I
want to pull up
Speaker 66: a video of
Miss Erica Kirk promoting her
Speaker 67: candidacy for Miss USA 2012 or Miss Arizona USA 2012.
This is a
Speaker 67: video of Miss Erica Kirk
Speaker 38: Thank
Speaker 37: you.
telling
Speaker 67: you
Speaker 68: about her morals and values at this time. Can people change? Sure. But
typically
Speaker 38: when they do, they
let you
Speaker 38: know they've changed. And
if you
Speaker 38: listen to her interviews about her pageant days, she doesn't indicate she's changed at all.
But let's just see
Speaker 68: what it is.
Speaker 37: Let's just evaluate her, take her at face value. I'm not putting words in her mouth. I'm not trying to derive things out of it, but let's just listen to what she says. There's three questions here. Let's
listen to
Speaker 37: her three answers.
If I
Speaker 69: could be great at one thing, I wish that I could sit in front of a mirror or a makeup mirror in general and spend more than...
Quick
Speaker 70: question. Can you hear it?
I have to wait on the delay. No
Speaker 31 (lower-pitched voice): sound. Yeah, I can't hear it either.
Well, let's
Speaker 31 (lower-pitched voice): just read it.
I'll read it
Speaker 52: out loud. Oh, you guys say you can hear it.
Some of you can
Speaker 52: hear it. Okay, let me do this. I'm going to kill the sound to
it.
And
Speaker 52: I'll just read
it because I think it's
Speaker 32: important. I would love you to hear it in her voice. Maybe
Speaker 71 (lower-pitched voice): I'll link it in the description. Actually, you know what I can do? Let me try to play it on a different medium. I've got a backup copy.
Let me do this. This is from a
Speaker 72 (lower-pitched voice): based
Speaker 73 (lower-pitched voice): Sam Parker's account. He has this version. So
let me
Speaker 73 (lower-pitched voice): see if this one plays better. I
wasn't sure how that
Speaker 73 (lower-pitched voice): version would play, so I got a backup copy.
I'll
Speaker 74: share this one and see if it makes it. If not, I'll just read it.
I have respect for the
Speaker 76: individuals that
Speaker 69: are in the photography industry, not because they're grading women or anything like that, but because that's their field and they are professionals. So I give them credit for being able to have a job and make money and stimulate.
I don't think
Speaker 78: you guys can hear it, so I'm just going to read it. I'm going to kill the sound and just read it.
This is
Speaker 32: Erica's words when asked a question.
These are her words,
Speaker 32: not mine. I'll just read it as it comes up. I have respect for the individuals
Speaker 79: that are in the pornography industry, not because they're degrading women.
or
Speaker 79: anything like that, but because that's their field and they are
Speaker 39: professionals. So I give them credit for being able to have a job and make money and stimulate the economy that way.
But I think
Speaker 39: that there needs to be a way to shield it from the overall public, such as the kids. Keep it away from them. But in general, if
Speaker 32: that's a tough one, I, hold on, I looked away and then she got past me. That's a
Speaker 39: tough one. I don't.
Speaker 39: really have to say that we live in a free country. So if you want to watch it, turn on your pay-per-view. If not, then why don't you turn on something else a little bit
Speaker 32: more G-rated, just a thought. Now, that is on pornography. That's her position in 2012. I
don't know if that remains her
Speaker 32: position today, but she's never been pro-porn that I'm aware of in her current iteration. Now, what about pro-marijuana?
I do
Speaker 32: think it
Speaker 39: should be legalized. So just take this miniature journey with me for
just a
Speaker 39: second. And instead of looking at the negative side, let's look at the positive side real quick. After watching several documentaries, that's her source. She watched several documentaries, but whatever. After watching several documentaries, I do think it should be legalized
because it not only
Speaker 39: has some remedies to some modern day medicines that we use, but it also can be taxed. So
Speaker 32: we can get some extra stimulus money. Just a thought.
And on
Speaker 32: top of that,
I think that
Speaker 32: as our country is evolving and things
Speaker 80: are pending, hold on, things are happening, happening, things are happening around the world. We really need to start taking into
Speaker 32: consideration just some alternatives to things. So I think we need to see
both sides
Speaker 32: of this. So I open dialogue. I'm all for
it. It's a different side of
Speaker 4: her, the different side. And again...
So I'm
Speaker 4: leading up to a point where I'm going to explain to you why all
this is
Speaker 4: bothering me today, why I'm bad copying it today.
Because I'm
Speaker 52: bothered by this. I've
got a
Speaker 52: little bit of an issue with this right now.
And when I get there,
Speaker 82: you'll go, oh, okay, that's why he's mad. That's why he's mad.
Here is the first
Speaker 83: reason I'm bothered by it.
Here's the first
On
Speaker 35: September 22nd,
less
Speaker 35: than two weeks after Charlie Kirk
had
Speaker 33: been taken from us, the national treasure taken down in his prime, 31 years old, father of two.
Less than two weeks after
Speaker 33: that
Speaker 35: ordeal, the day after his memorial on September 21st, our
beloved
Speaker 63: Tyler Boyer, not a creepy guy at all,
takes to
Speaker 39: Newsmax I'll
Speaker 84 (lower-pitched voice): see
Speaker 85 (lower-pitched voice): you next time.
to have an
Speaker 39: interview and here is how Tyler Boyer described
Speaker 84 (lower-pitched voice): Erica Kirk pay close attention to what they were trying
to set up
Speaker 85 (lower-pitched voice): on us
do you
Speaker 85 (lower-pitched voice): see politics in her future down the road yeah you know it's funny uh I had had conversations with Charlie about that so he he he was like man Erica could be so much bigger and better than me at almost everything we laugh all the time about because people were like Charlie was going to be president someday he believed
for
Speaker 85 (lower-pitched voice): that Erica was going to be
Speaker 86: president someday. Is
there a single one
Speaker 87: of you who believes Charlie
Kirk
Speaker 60: said that? That
he believed
Speaker 60: firmly Erica Kirk was going to be president someday. Is
there a single
Speaker 60: person
Speaker 88: on the planet who looks at that and says, yeah, that makes sense. That's how I see it. I believe Charlie was
Speaker 58: sitting around all day long. He was running his multi-million
Speaker 68: dollar, a hundred million dollar
Speaker 68: organization. Now, he was asking his wife, please stay home with the kids. Don't get too carried away with your work life.
Speaker 89: Raise the kids. Make that your priority. But in the meantime, he believed firmly he was going to be president one day or could do better than him at being president one
day. Well,
Speaker 55: that was
Speaker 32: September 22nd of 2025. That was 12 days after
he was
Speaker 32: taken out. That was one day after
Speaker 32: Charlie Kirk's general.
Speaker 6: Now, I mentioned that was on Newsmax. This next clip is on NewsNation.
If you were with us Thursday for our
Speaker 52: part two of the Hunter Kozak series, we kind of outlined NewsNation's importance in setting the narrative. That was an organization that continually, time after time after time again, all these same actors would run out in front of NewsNation
Speaker 90 (lower-pitched voice): cameras and give I don't know.
the
Speaker 90 (lower-pitched voice): narrative. Charlie was shot. This is a religious thing, or this is a conservative versus Democrat
Speaker 91: thing. He was killed by
a leftist. It was
Speaker 91: a gunshot. He was killed by a leftist. It was a leftist gunshot. It was a gunshot that came from the left.
So then just a couple
Speaker 68: days after that September 22nd appearance, this is September 24th, September 24th. Again,
I
Speaker 20: cannot emphasize the rapidity with which this happened after he was killed. He
was taken out on
Speaker 20: September 10th.
He had his giant
Speaker 20: memorial service where they sold a lot of merch on September 21st. The following day, Tyler
Boyer wears his same
Speaker 20: in God we trust hat and he goes on Newsmax.
Speaker 52: And
on Newsmax,
Speaker 52: he says, Charlie believed Erica could be president.
And
Speaker 52: then he runs to NewsNation
Speaker 92: just two days later, just
two days later. And
Speaker 92: he has this to say to NewsNation. Some
of
Speaker 93: your colleagues from Turning Point on in the last few days, some of them have told me that Charlie always joked if something terrible happened, he wanted Erica
to be
Speaker 93: his
Speaker 94: successor. What differences do you see between the leadership of Charlie and when Erica does take over officially? So
a couple of
Speaker 95 (lower-pitched voice): things. First, I just want to point out
from a comment.
She
Speaker 53: believed that Charlie's colleagues were joking when
Speaker 96: they told her Charlie would say Erica would take over. I'll
go back to
Speaker 97: it. It sounded like the setup was
Speaker 38: Charlie's colleagues said Charlie would joke that Erica would take over. Listen again.
We've
Speaker 98: had some of your colleagues from Turning Point on in the last few days. Some of them have told me
Speaker 94: that Charlie always joked if something terrible happened, he wanted Erica to be his successor. What differences do you see between the leadership of Charlie and when Erica does take over officially?
Speaker 99 (lower-pitched voice): Yeah. I mean, Erica is already there. Erica and Charlie are one. Charlie is one with Erica. So it's just, it's such a natural fit. He had always looked up to Erica. He had always boosted Erica. Everyone always said Charlie would be president. Charlie always said that Erica would be president. So we have the person that Charlie believed in and loved the most in this world as leader and nothing here organizationally and operationally changes. And so we're really excited to keep doing the work.
Speaker 99 (lower-pitched voice): Uh, we know Erica is going to be, uh, the best carrier of Charlie spirit and
Speaker 100: his, and his legacy. And that is going to be something I think that will reach all the ends of the year. People
would always say that
Speaker 101: Charlie would be president one day. Charlie always said Erica would be president.
I don't believe it. I don't believe
Speaker 102: it at all.
And I think
Speaker 102: anyone who will
Speaker 68: look in the camera and tell that lie.
twice in
Speaker 68: two days, I think will lie to you about anything. I think they'll lie to you about where people were on September 10th. I think they'll lie to you about where people were on September 8th and 9th. I
think they'll
Speaker 68: lie to you about who was involved. I think they'll lie to you about how he passed away. I think they'll lie to you about the cause of him passing away. I think they'll lie to you about what they're doing as an organization, what kind of things they're getting involved with. I
think these people
Speaker 103: will lie to you about anything.
I don't
Speaker 103: believe it for
Speaker 13: a second that Charlie said that,
not for a
Speaker 5: second. I don't
think anybody else
Speaker 5: believes it either. I've yet to come across a single person that says, yeah, that
Speaker 57: makes sense. Even supporters of hers that I've talked to, even supporters. I said,
do you
Speaker 104: believe Charlie said that? No, I don't believe Charlie said that.
Nobody believes
Speaker 105: it.
But they
Speaker 105: were saying it, and they were more than saying it,
ladies
Speaker 50: and gentlemen. They
were more than
Speaker 50: saying it. I want to show
you a
Speaker 50: website that's been put up.
And then we'll talk about
Speaker 50: when this website
Speaker 35: was put up. But here is a website that is
currently on the
Speaker 20: interwebs. This website exists, vancekirk2028.com. And
you might
Speaker 20: think, well, it's March 8th.
Speaker 20: vance kirk
Speaker 106: 2028 i mean she's been in charge of turning point now for months they
seem to be raising a lot
Speaker 106: of money maybe someone's
Speaker 61: just getting out and reserving this name just on the off chance it happens she did say they were going to do everything they could to get
jd vance elected president
Speaker 107: in 2028 she did say that and so Thank
you.
Maybe
Speaker 107: there's some offhanded, maybe there's a deal where Erica
Speaker 38: Kirk would be on the ticket. Or, or, or you could argue and say, well, it's possible we've just discovered
Speaker 35: this page in March of 2026, but this page has actually been around a long time. This probably went back when Charlie was still alive and he was the natural pick potentially to be the vice president, even though
he would
Speaker 35: have barely qualified
Speaker 90 (lower-pitched voice): for vice president. He was 31 when he passed away.
He
Speaker 90 (lower-pitched voice): turned 32, or he would have turned 32
Speaker 52: a couple of weeks later. In
2028, when the
Speaker 108: election day rolled around, he would have only been qualified to be president of the United States. And you have
to be
Speaker 108: qualified to be president, to be vice president. He would have only been qualified to be president of the United States for one month, less than one month.
He would have only been
Speaker 40: 35 in one month.
Speaker 40: so maybe they put this website up when Charlie was still around
Speaker 38: or maybe they've just recently put it up. Well, I'm
here to
Speaker 38: tell you, we can answer exactly when this website was purchased. We can tell you when this website was created and
the date will
Speaker 40: shock you. The
date will
Speaker 40: shock you.
My dog's about to
Speaker 109: walk.
I hear
Speaker 109: her grumbling in the microphone.
Here is when the website
Speaker 67: was created.
You see this down
Speaker 67: here? This
is the
Speaker 61: created date.
This website was created on
Speaker 20: September 13th, 2025. September 13th,
Speaker 63: 2025 at 2 a.m. Universal time, known as Zulu time.
If you do
Speaker 63: the
Speaker 20: math, that equals 9 p.m. Central Time, 10 p.m. Eastern Time, 7 p.m. West Coast Time on
September
Speaker 8: 12th, 2025. September 12th, 2025.
Speaker 110: Somebody finds
out Charlie
Speaker 110: Kirk has been taken out.
On
Speaker 58: the afternoon of September 10th,
and then on
Speaker 58: the evening, about 50
Speaker 6: hours later, 52 hours later, maybe 57 hours later, 55
hours later, body's
Speaker 6: still very
Speaker 110: much cooling down. Someone
goes out and buys
Speaker 110: VanceKirk2028.com. Now, I want you to transport
Speaker 32: your mind back to September 12th of 2025.
we're
Speaker 32: just now seeing the first
Speaker 10: images of the alleged Tyler Robinson walking around.
We're just seeing the
Speaker 10: ring doorbell footage. We're
just seeing
Speaker 10: the footage where he leapt off of the Losey Center.
Nobody knows who
Speaker 10: Erica Kirk
Speaker 111: is. She has just given her first speech where anyone even learned her name.
and that
Speaker 33: was where she was dressed all in white standing behind Charlie's chair or next to Charlie's chair in his studio. And
somebody ran out and bought this
Speaker 35: website. Now here's what we can't do. We can't say who bought it. We don't know who bought it,
but was anyone on
Speaker 89: earth under the impression at that moment that
Speaker 111: Erica Kirk's,
Speaker 111: profile would be elevated to such a high level as to seriously be considered for vice president of the united states was there
anybody who
Speaker 111: thought that at that moment like when you watched that widow speech or whatever it was when you watched that was there any part
Speaker 16: of you
who thought to
Speaker 16: yourself
This
Speaker 16: girl's got the chops to be vice president. She could be president one day. She could be one heartbeat away from the presidency.
That's how
Speaker 16: powerful she is. That's how
Speaker 112: good that speech was.
Speaker 113: That's the only speech we'd ever seen her make.
That's the only
Speaker 44: speech we'd seen her make at that point.
I can show
Speaker 44: you the last time this website was modified.
Speaker 44: was September
Speaker 114 (lower-pitched voice): 13th. So basically it went up and has not changed since. The
last time it was
Speaker 114 (lower-pitched voice): modified
Speaker 80: right here, 2025, 9, 13. I don't know if that's Zulu time that it was never modified at all.
But that website's been sitting
Speaker 115: there since. It's active. You can click on it.
And here's
Speaker 115: the key.
There's a pay
Speaker 115: portal.
built
Speaker 111: into the website. If
you look at
Speaker 111: the site map, there's a pay portal, a
donation
Speaker 20: portal built
into the
Speaker 20: website. Meaning, whoever put this
website up intended it to
Speaker 3: one day take donations.
That's not
Speaker 3: somebody just
Speaker 107: reserving a website, I don't think. Like, I have websites reserved. You can go to realbaronpodcast.com
Speaker 33: right now. There's nothing on it. I just have it reserved.
I didn't
Speaker 33: want someone else to buy it.
So if you go
Speaker 33: to realbaronpodcast.com, there's
Speaker 53: no pay portal on it.
I didn't
Speaker 53: build a pay portal into it.
I wouldn't build a pay
Speaker 105: portal into it because I have no intentions of taking donations on it.
And so it's just
Speaker 50: a weird data point. But I
Speaker 20: would...
Speaker 20: I would have you know that at the time that website was purchased, the board had to seriously be considering her as the successor to Charlie Kirk.
Because they would
Speaker 20: make that
Speaker 38: appointment, I think, two days later, three
days later,
Speaker 38: publicly, which means they were already talking about what are we doing? Who's going to take over?
Is it
Speaker 38: going to be Tyler Boyer?
Is it going to be
Speaker 116: Lori Fransvay?
is it
Speaker 116: going to be i think i heard benny
Speaker 23: johnson's name thrown around ben shapiro's name thrown around who who are we going to put in charge of turning point
they settled on erica
Speaker 23: kirk a
Speaker 54: couple of days later but somebody was way out in front of this
Speaker 117: somebody was way out in front of this
i want to switch gears
Speaker 117: ever so slightly
I want to switch
Speaker 118: gears. I want to go to Central America. I have
a report
Speaker 45: here on corporate social responsibility on this word
Speaker 67: here. I don't want to necessarily say this phrase and let YouTube tag it, but the misuse of young people.
in
Speaker 67: Costa Rica,
Speaker 45: the misuse of young people in Costa Rica. And I will skip ahead. So
this is a dissertation,
Speaker 37: I guess. And
you've got the
Speaker 37: table of contents here, and you've got this story. And this person opens with a story about...
how
Speaker 37: they came to want to study this particular topic in Costa Rica.
So this is
Speaker 37: 54-year-old Eliza, an American,
started a
Speaker 37: safe
Speaker 67: house in Costa Rica for misused children, eager to
tell her
Speaker 67: story. And here's the story right here. So
I took my children
Speaker 40: on a vacation to Costa Rica. And when we were in Jayco,
Speaker 40: This is the name of a city in Costa Rica, Jayco, Costa Rica, which is a beach town. We were surrounded by a lot of women selling themselves
Speaker 80: for value and drugs. Jayco is a hotspot for sexual tourism.
It was all
Speaker 40: around us. We couldn't get away from it.
When we returned to the
Speaker 40: United States, I began to study
Speaker 44: I'm going
to ask you to take a look at your screen.
human
Speaker 61: transportation-ing. I'd never really
been
Speaker 44: approached by it or seen much of it.
But when she
Speaker 44: was in Jayco, she couldn't get away from it. She was surrounded by it. It was everywhere. And
I read this story and I
Speaker 62: think, and this was November of 2015. This
was a
Speaker 62: while ago.
And I start looking
Speaker 119: at that, and I think, where have I heard the name Jaco before? I
remember now where I
Speaker 119: heard Jaco. In fact, just because
Speaker 35: transportationing of minors seems to be such a hot topic
Speaker 33: everywhere you turn relative to the people
involved in this
Speaker 33: story we've been
Speaker 40: covering,
Speaker 40: Uh, here is a post from Travis on Twitter,
Speaker 79: ex Nilo X breaking Erica France. They had another charity helping children. You guys want to guess where it was? Anybody want to guess where this charity was that was helping children? We know she had one charity in Constantin, Romania, the trafficking capital of Europe on the black sea. We know that she had a charity there weirdly.
Didn't have
Speaker 79: one in Houston, didn't have one in Phoenix, didn't have
Speaker 120: one in Chicago, didn't have one in Indianapolis, but she had one in Constanta.
This time, her philanthropy would
Speaker 50: appear in Jayco, Costa Rica, under the name Kids First. Wow, weird. It's weird. It's like everywhere she
Speaker 1: sets up shop, this seems to be a recurring theme.
Romania, Costa
Speaker 1: Rica, not just any
Speaker 40: Costa Rican city, Jayco, Costa Rica.
Speaker 40: This is a headline from the website entry. Everyday Heroes Like You has teamed up with Kids First to help address the needs to create a safe environment for at-risk youth in Jayco, Costa Rica.
And if you go back on the
Speaker 67: internet archives and you zoom in here, this
is the
Speaker 67: everydayheroeslikeyou.com website. There's a forward slash kids first.
It was
Speaker 67: only active for a year or two,
Speaker 118: 2019, 2020, and early part of 2021. July
of 2019 to July of
Speaker 37: 2021, so two years. It was only active for those two years. But
this is the
Speaker 40: mission, Jayco Costa Rica. Everyday Heroes Like You has teamed up with Kids First to help address the need to create a safe environment for the at-risk youth in Jayco Costa Rica. The
Kids First
Speaker 40: organization helps children stay
Speaker 37: off the streets where they're exposed to drugs and crime.
Speaker 37: giving them environment to learn and grow our challenge too many children in our community are
raised by
Speaker 37: single mothers working six days a week who cannot afford daycare
left unsupervised so
Speaker 37: many hours a day these children are
high risk
Speaker 37: especially after school weekends and during summer
vacation kids
Speaker 37: first programs help children reach their full potential
so that
Speaker 37: was
A
Speaker 37: website that was up and here's some more of it. The core objectives, inspire
Speaker 121: and empower the leaders of tomorrow, richer and more fulfilling lives, provide a safe environment.
Speaker 79: Why
is it
Speaker 79: everywhere she goes, this is the environment? I'm
confused by
Speaker 79: it. It's almost intentional.
Not like they were
Speaker 68: in San Jose, Costa Rica. Not like they were in Mexico. Not like they were in Nicaragua or Panama.
Not like
Speaker 68: they were in El Salvador, they were in Jayco, Costa Rica, which is a total hotbed for this stuff.
And I look at this and I think at some point
Speaker 51 (higher-pitched voice): you have to begin to accept
Speaker 3: the reality
that
Speaker 122 (lower-pitched voice): there are far too many coincidences that add up in this woman's case and the people around her.
There are far too many
Speaker 67: coincidences that add up.
It's
Speaker 67: beginning to look like there's a pattern that exists
for a
Speaker 123: reason. You
know, they
Speaker 123: say stereotypes exist for a reason. Like I'm sure there's some really nice tigers in the world, right? But you don't go throw
Speaker 35: yourself in a tiger cage at the zoo because tigers have a bad reputation for tearing your face off and eating
you. This
Speaker 58: pattern exists.
And at a
Speaker 58: certain point, you can draw conclusions from it. Notice this is not on
Speaker 124: her list of anything she ever talks about. She talks about her work in China. She talks about her work in Costa Rica. She talks about her work in Puerto Rico. She
fails to
Speaker 124: mention she was in Puerto Rico
Speaker 38: and China to shack up with a ball player. But that's irrelevant. She talks about him at least. At least she mentions him.
never
Speaker 38: mentions Costa Rica, never mentions Jayco Costa Rica. Well,
Speaker 103: if you look at the news reports, it becomes very obvious because they had like a five-year run where they were arresting anybody who
Speaker 52: wiggled in Jayco Costa Rica. They started cracking down on this stuff about the time they got out of there.
And it's,
Speaker 106: again,
Speaker 68: Thank
Speaker 125: you.
if she was
Speaker 106: an honest person, I would
Speaker 68: take her word for it.
Like, if I didn't have her
Speaker 68: lying about her, like something as fundamental and basic and easily disprovable as your academic credentials, then
you might
Speaker 125: say, well, I was there in Jayco doing good stuff with kids. I wasn't there exploiting anybody. I was in Constantin, Romania, doing good stuff with kids. We weren't there exploiting anybody. Yeah, a lot of people exploit
kids
Speaker 50: over there, but we didn't.
Speaker 50: A lot of people exploit kids in Costa Rica, not us, not us. That's not what we were doing.
I'm very weirded out by the
Speaker 111: fact that all of
Speaker 10: the charity work seems to be overseas in hotbeds of this type of environment. That's all I'm saying.
And the weirding
Speaker 20: out is compounded by the
fact that
Speaker 20: she's a deeply dishonest,
Speaker 11: fundamentally dishonest human being.
Speaker 11: almost congenitally dishonest because the dishonesty goes back so far. I can't find anything where she's not dishonest about.
Speaker 126: Now, I want to switch gears again
because this is
Speaker 33: going to tie into
more dishonesty out
Speaker 33: of TPUSA.
This next story,
Speaker 33: believe it or not, is going to tie into even more dishonesty out of TPUSA.
This is a
Speaker 55: weird story. It's making its way on Twitter. I can't credit anybody because I saw it like 400 times
Speaker 121: today. World War III bunker manufacturer. There's a guy who makes bunkers
for
Speaker 42: rich people for World War III. Nuclear holocaust bunkers. They survived missile attacks. They survived nuclear attacks. This guy, this is what he does.
Speaker 33: His name is Ron Hubbard, not L. Ron Hubbard. I don't
know if
Speaker 33: they're related. Not the guy who started Scientology.
Speaker 33: Maybe he's related, I don't know, but it's not
Speaker 3: the same guy.
This is Ron
Speaker 3: Hubbard, not L. Ron Hubbard.
War, for most people, brings confusion. The article states,
Speaker 59: this is the Telegraph overseas. It's amazing how the American press never reports on stuff like this. War, for most people,
Speaker 79: brings confusion, fear, and destruction. But for Ron Hubbard, it brings something else altogether,
Speaker 1: opportunity.
What does
Speaker 1: he do? He builds bunkers designed to help customers survive drone attacks, ballistic missile strikes, or even nuclear Armageddon. That's his job. And
as of the last week or so,
Speaker 41: after the U.S. and Iran started spatting,
Speaker 41: business has never
Speaker 52: been better for his company. Now, you might think, well, these are just rich people. They don't know anything. These aren't connected. These people have no idea what's going on in the world. Well, let's read the next sentence here.
Next two
Speaker 79: sentences. I've been inundated with calls, says Hubbard. Inquiry's gone up tenfold since the war broke out Saturday. Who are these people calling him? Hubbard claims two senior cabinet members in the Trump administration are among his clients.
One of
Speaker 79: them, meaning one of the senior cabinet members in the Trump administration who are among his clients building a nuclear Holocaust bomb shelter, are asking him, when will his bunker be ready? One
of the Trump senior cabinet
Speaker 79: administration
Speaker 20: officials.
is
Speaker 20: asking, when is my nuclear holocaust bunker going to be ready? When
do I have the ability
Speaker 51 (higher-pitched voice): to survive nuclear? Well, what do they know that we don't? Keep in mind, these are the people who trade on inside information, congressmen, cabinet
Speaker 127: officials, and they get a bunch of money out of
it. Like if you follow
Speaker 127: their trades, you'll get rich.
And it's worth
Speaker 51 (higher-pitched voice): noting.
If
Speaker 51 (higher-pitched voice): you wanted to know, if you wanted to so inquire, it's worth noting that this war, we had a
Speaker 128 (higher-pitched voice): warning.
There was
Speaker 128 (higher-pitched voice): somebody out there. There was a voice in the wilderness telling us how stupid this would be.
There was someone on
Speaker 128 (higher-pitched voice): earth who said,
you
Speaker 64 (higher-pitched voice): know, if you go to war with Iran, you might need a nuclear holocaust bunker. Okay.
it might
Speaker 64 (higher-pitched voice): not go as well as you think. It's
the type of
Speaker 128 (higher-pitched voice): thing that could spiral out of control really fast. You might recognize the young man. Here he is. This
was the
Speaker 128 (higher-pitched voice): guy.
this was the
Speaker 41: guy telling you this was a terrible idea. I will let him do it. I'm not going to summarize what he said here. I'm going to play a minute or so of this and let him tell you what
Speaker 129 (lower-pitched voice): he thought about a potential regime change war with Iran.
Speaker 130: Let's do some updates about Israel and Iran and potentially the United
Speaker 131: States. On one side is the Lindsey Graham, John Bolton types, where they are actively calling for regime change. Here is Lindsey Graham. This is just lunacy.
Speaker 131: he's this kind of analysis is not helpful this kind of approach this kind of argument it says nothing new with nuclear weapons at this point this is now that we want to go all in and take out the regime it's time for us to close the chapter on the iranian ayatollah and his henchmen and start a new chapter in the middle east that sounds good doesn't it
Speaker 131: But what have we learned when it comes to wars, and especially wars in the Middle East? What you draw up on a whiteboard rarely happens.
What you think
Speaker 131: theoretically is going to occur,
there might be
Speaker 131: unintended and unforeseen consequences, especially when you're talking about a country two
and a
Speaker 131: half times the size of
Texas,
It has
Speaker 131: 90 million people and was an ancient and great power with well over a dozen ethnic groups. You have underground Christians. You don't really have many Jews left in Persia, but also you have secular younger Persians. Who's going to run the country exactly, Lindsey Graham? This sounds like Hillary Rodham Clinton in Libya.
So
Speaker 131: I'm pointing to the first extreme right now, the neoconservative extreme, the we must go take off the head of the snake right now. Play
Speaker 132: cut 285.
Speaker 133: - Be all in President Trump in helping Israel eliminate the nuclear threat. If we need to provide bombs to Israel, provide bombs. If we need to fly planes with Israel, do joint operations. But here's the bigger question. Wouldn't the world be better off
if the
Speaker 133: Ayatollahs went away and replaced by something better?
Speaker 134: That's what we're hearing today. Isn't the world going to be better once we get these people out of the way? Well, they're out of the way.
They've all
Speaker 134: been taken out.
The top 50 or
Speaker 60: so people in the Iranian government are gone. They've gone to meet their maker.
And even
Speaker 135: so, we have senior Trump cabinet officials calling a nuclear bunker
Speaker 136 (higher-pitched voice): guy and saying, is my bunker ready yet?
It sounds
Speaker 136 (higher-pitched voice): like things might not be going as well as we're being told, if I'm being honest. Like, that's usually a bad sign. The cabinet officials sit in the cabinet. They sit in the meetings. They have one-on-one conversations with the President of the United States. They walk out of those meetings. They pick up their phone.
and
Speaker 136 (higher-pitched voice): they
Speaker 128 (higher-pitched voice): call the bunker guy yeah bunker guy yeah hey this
is
Speaker 106: senior trump cabinet official yeah
yeah it's
Speaker 106: me it's me again i know i called a few days ago hey the bunker is it done yet oh
no the
Speaker 106: bunker takes longer than a couple of days i may not have much longer
we
Speaker 137: really need the bunker yeah i know my house
is in
Speaker 137: the united states that's a little weird right
Speaker 137: Yeah, yeah, yeah. Could you put the, could you, could you expedite the nuclear bunker? I can't tell you why. I mean, I'm just, you know, just want to be safe. That's all. Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. Great, great. I appreciate that. Yeah. Get on double time. I'll pay you double. Just get it in the ground and get it in the ground now. I can't tell you why. Got to go. Bye.
now let's
Speaker 138: hear what he had to say in response wouldn't iran be better off it's time to close the chapter on the iranian ayatollah and his
Speaker 133: henchmen let's close that chapter soon and start a new chapter in the mid-east one of tolerance to
Speaker 132: hope and peace okay that sounds good but that's pathologically insane i'm
sorry it is how
Speaker 132: pathologically
Speaker 51 (higher-pitched voice): insane
regime
Speaker 51 (higher-pitched voice): change wars in Iran, pathologically insane.
Speaker 1: You know, with a guy like this out there in charge
of a
Speaker 1: billion-dollar ground game operation that's in charge of trying to get people elected, that
has
Speaker 21: the hearts and minds of millions of young people around the country, a guy who's calling regime change in Iran pathologically insane, he could be a problem if we had to take out Iran. If we wanted to do a regime change war in Iran,
in
Speaker 21: iran a guy like that might be a real burden he might be a thorn in our flesh we might have to excise him we might have to get rid of a guy
Speaker 139: like that do you know it's going to be better yeah the ayatollah is awful
but maybe
Speaker 131: he's one of the few guys that can keep that country together and not have a 90 million person civil war
Speaker 131: lindsey graham is so consistently out of his mind it's hard to even comprehend iran is hugely diverse it is a massive country do the people agitating for war even know that because be clear regime changes war just to understand regime change is not like changing the head coach at the chicago bears it's not how it works it's not like a clean transfer
it's not like a clean transfer
Speaker 131: typically in the Mideast it's very messy creates a quagmire and then there is civil war do you understand how large Iran is it's massive it's a very big country it's mountainous it makes Afghanistan and Iraq look like a cakewalk just look at this beast of a country with all the different regions all the different dialects if we could put that up on screen and then you have a major refugee concern of Mohammedans that will come to Europe and
and
Speaker 131: endanger more Christians than Jews and Mohammedans that will come to America. Now,
let me just
Speaker 140: go on the record. I haven't seen the word Mohammedan since like the 19th century in literature.
But I digress, I digress. Are you getting the
Speaker 111: picture of the problem Charlie Kirk posed by his mere
Speaker 42: existence? Are
you getting
Speaker 42: the idea that
Speaker 42: That Charlie Kirk being alive would have
Speaker 34: been a significant impediment in the lead up to the war in Iran that kicked off, what, nine or 10 days ago?
And would
Speaker 34: continue to be an impediment day in and day out as it
Speaker 52: dragged on and turned into what he described as a quagmire. He said Afghanistan and Iraq would look like a cakewalk.
Speaker 79: Well, does anyone feel like those went like cakewalks?
Speaker 79: We went into Afghanistan to remove the Taliban. We spent 21 years there.
And when
Speaker 79: we left, guess who was in charge?
Guess who's still
Speaker 51 (higher-pitched voice): in charge?
Yes, yes, yes. Good
Speaker 51 (higher-pitched voice): job, class. You said it all the way. The Taliban. That's right. Meaning,
Speaker 58: perhaps, what
we were told
Speaker 58: as Americans, that the Taliban,
Taliban
Speaker 58: was oppressive and all
Speaker 13: the people hated the Taliban and they didn't want to be ruled by the Taliban. And if someone would just remove them, the people would rise up and they
Speaker 79: would rule the country peacefully.
Well, we fought
Speaker 79: for 20 years. We destroyed nearly everything
Speaker 52: in sight.
And the Taliban is still
Speaker 52: in charge.
That's who is in charge in
Speaker 52: Afghanistan
Speaker 32: today. That's who rules Afghanistan
Speaker 57: today.
it might
Speaker 57: lead one to
Speaker 5: believe that perhaps the locals weren't as against the Taliban as we're led to believe. I go back to the summer
Speaker 52: of 2020. You
remember the summer of
Speaker 52: 2020? Donald
Speaker 43: Trump is campaigning for re-election. There's an autonomous zone, the CHAZ, the Capitol Hill Autonomous Zone, that had been set up in Seattle.
A
Speaker 43: protest, if you will. There were
Speaker 96: Black Lives Matter protests, destroying things all over the country. There were women's marches. There was this tremendous groundswell from the
Speaker 35: left.
And if you were an outsider
Speaker 35: looking in, you might be able to build a very strong case to your people back home that
this country
Speaker 6: hates their leader. They don't want him. Well, he went out and got like 80-something million votes.
lost the
Speaker 68: election, but he got 80-something million votes. And there's a good argument that the election might not have been even Stephen,
Speaker 52: right? Someone might have had their thumb on the scale. And
then four years
Speaker 52: later, he won election. He's back in office. The guy that they were all protesting, that they were pushing back against, that everybody
Speaker 103: hated, as evidenced by the marches, the hundreds of thousands, the millions of people marching on the weekends, marching during the week, tearing up the city.
And he
Speaker 103: goes and gets elected again. It's almost as if the United States wanted to be ruled by that guy, despite the protest, maybe in spite of the protest,
Speaker 142: maybe because of the protest. The enemy, my enemy is my friend. I look at those people and think those guys are nuts. Who are they protesting? I'll vote for that guy. And
there was an
Speaker 142: element of that.
Now, maybe we realized we
Speaker 57: didn't get what we bargained for. Maybe a lot of us may regret our vote, but we voted for him. A lot of us did.
more
Speaker 11: than voted for the other girl.
Of course,
Speaker 11: they put up a mentally challenged drunk on the other side, but
you could have voted for her. You didn't
Speaker 35: have to vote for him. But
that's Charlie Kirk on
Speaker 35: regime change wars. Pathologically insane. Not
Speaker 58: going to happen the way you think it's going to happen. Might need to call the nuclear
bunker
Speaker 64 (higher-pitched voice): guy. Might
need to call
Speaker 64 (higher-pitched voice): the nuclear bunker guy. That's like a thing.
There are
Speaker 64 (higher-pitched voice): Trump cabinet level of we could pull up Trump's cabinet and two of them are calling the nuclear bunker
Speaker 51 (higher-pitched voice): guy. We don't know which two. Is it Pam Bondi? Is it Pete Hegseth? Is it Marco Rubio? We don't know. Is it Scott Bessette? But I'm talking like names you've heard of.
They're calling the
Speaker 51 (higher-pitched voice): nuclear
Speaker 128 (higher-pitched voice): bunker guy. That's their confidence in what's going on in Iran.
you're
Speaker 143: told to calm down. Everything's fine. We got it under control.
They're
Speaker 20: calling the nuclear bunker guy. I mean, I cannot emphasize that enough. That's a problem. That's a real problem.
But I bring
Speaker 127: it up not to point out that the war is a quagmire already. I think it kind of is becoming one, but that's not the point.
you
Speaker 144: know, we were sold on regime change after we were sold initially on, we just need to limit their ability to do nuclear strikes. We don't want them building a bomb, so we'd launch Operation Midnight
Speaker 145: Hammer this summer. Charlie tries to talk the president out of joining that strike, by the way. He
did it anyway. But
Speaker 105: afterwards, they were told, hey, success.
Speaker 50: We set their nuclear program back years. We destroyed it all.
it'll
Speaker 50: take them a long time to get
Speaker 146: that set back up. The world's a safer place today. Well, a few months later,
Speaker 147: they're like, well,
but we need to
Speaker 147: do regime change.
They still got
Speaker 147: a Navy. Well, we weren't sold on destroying their Navy. We were
sold on
Speaker 147: destroying their nuclear weapons. But
where
Speaker 55: did this Navy thing come from? So
we destroy their
Speaker 55: nuclear weapons in June or July.
Can't make nuclear
Speaker 55: weapons.
But they
Speaker 55: come back
Speaker 58: to us and say, we have to destroy the entire rest of the regime. We have to take them out. We have to remove them, the regime. We have to get rid of them.
Speaker 79: Okay. And
now we're
Speaker 79: told they're bombing police stations, bridges, oil refineries. Well,
when was
Speaker 79: that part of the deal?
When did they tell us that
Speaker 51 (higher-pitched voice): it was necessary to destroy all their civilian infrastructure that people rely on to get to the hospital, to
get to
Speaker 51 (higher-pitched voice): school?
when
Speaker 51 (higher-pitched voice): were we sold on that?
Speaker 79: But anyway, I digress, I digress. The point is, Charlie would have been a real pain in the neck. He would have been a real problem when it comes to
the regime
Speaker 18: change war.
So now I want to answer the weird
Speaker 148: question we've all been asking. Why are they still using Charlie Kirk's name
why are
Speaker 149: they
Speaker 37: still using charlie kirk's name on the podcast well we'll get to that but before we play that clip i want to play one small clip of these guys
Speaker 111: blake
Speaker 52: nef speed and
Speaker 111: andrew
Speaker 40: colvin
trying
Speaker 40: to convince us this actually isn't a regime change war, despite what your lying eyes and ears may be seeing. The
Speaker 150: point is, the
Speaker 151 (lower-pitched voice): ultimate secession plan remains pretty unclear at this point. It seems to be, there was an indication from President Trump where he was saying, we'll see who they choose, meaning it does seem that this is not a regime change war. I understand that can feel like...
Speaker 151 (lower-pitched voice): you know, a distinction without a difference, right? Because, yeah, the regime is going to change. These are targeted airstrikes to take out the leadership and allow the people of Iran to choose the next leader. So we don't know how that's going to play out.
So the guy sitting in Charlie
Speaker 152: Kirk's studio with
Charlie
Speaker 32: Kirk's name on the screen three times on the Chiron, Charlie Kirk show, freedom at charliekirk.com. Over here's a logo for the Charlie Kirk show.
Speaker 32: Is going to tell you, well, I know that
Speaker 4: everybody's saying it's a regime change war. And I know we've killed all the top leadership, thereby changing the regime.
But this
Speaker 4: isn't really a regime change war. Come on.
Why would they say
Speaker 4: that? Because they know there's this clip
Speaker 153: circulating where Charlie Kirk is telling everybody that a regime change war is pathologically insane.
It's a
Speaker 154: pathologically insane position.
now
Speaker 154: listen to this we get to we get to finally answer the question why they're keeping charlie kirk's
Speaker 35: name on the show and what would charlie have said about this now we heard his clip earlier where
he said it's
Speaker 35: pathologically insane it never works out
Speaker 52: like you think it's going to be a quagmire iraq and afghanistan would be a cakewalk compared to iran if you think you're going to go in there in a week and and flip the country over you're out of your mind we've already have that clip would know that's happened.
Speaker 52: here's how they describe what Charlie would say, even though we know what he already said. That's really what it is,
Speaker 155 (lower-pitched voice): is there'd be two competing impulses with Charlie. And the reason we cite him, a big reason we continue this show, a big reason it still has his name on there is people looked to Charlie as a leader,
as a
Speaker 155 (lower-pitched voice): leader in the movement, as a person who had wise perspectives, as a person who wasn't under the control of anyone
Speaker 156: else. And so he could be
Speaker 35: Yeah, he was frank and honest. He said that going to war in Iran would be a quagmire. It would be a disaster. It would be pathologically insane. He told us his opinion. I have a feeling that's why he's no longer among the living.
That's my guess. Because he was willing
Speaker 58: to speak his mind,
Speaker 35: because he was willing to tell his honest opinion,
he had to
Speaker 35: be removed.
Now, you'll
Speaker 35: notice that that motive eliminates Tyler Robinson as a suspect, but that's neither
here nor
Speaker 155 (lower-pitched voice): there.
Speaker 35: So...
Speaker 155 (lower-pitched voice): We're trying to maintain that voice to the best we can so that because that's what people are looking towards. And what I can say, and I think you agree, is Charlie would have two competing impulses. One is he was a millennial. He was a part of that generation, very shaped by Iraq and Afghanistan, two wars that looked very easy at the start.
But
Speaker 155 (lower-pitched voice): went on a lot longer than people thought, were more expensive than people thought they would be, and ended in ultimately either failure or, at best, mixed results in the
Speaker 156: case of Iraq.
Mixed
Speaker 157: results in the case of Iraq. Go
back to
Speaker 157: 2001, 2, and 3 and ask
Speaker 52: yourself, if George
Bush had
Speaker 52: come to you and said, look, 9-11 happened, we've got to do something.
Speaker 63: Thank
Speaker 158: you.
what
Speaker 60: we've decided to do is
Speaker 63: we're going to attack Iraq, but fear not. We'll only be there 20 years. We'll only be in, we've got to attack Afghanistan. Excuse me. We've got to
Speaker 158: attack Afghanistan. We'll only be there 20 years. And when we get done, the same people will be in charge that are in charge today. That just happens. You know, hey, can't be perfect. We're probably going to lose in the neighborhood of 5,000 to 10,000 American lives.
in
Speaker 158: this 20-year war? It'll probably cost in the
Speaker 68: trillions of dollars. We know that's a lot of money. We understand what that sounds like, but trust me, we'll just borrow it from China. We'll borrow it from other countries.
So don't worry about
Speaker 68: the details. Just focus on the fact that
because
Speaker 25: our buildings were knocked down, we're going to go into a 20-year war that's going to kill multiple times more people, more American lives than we lost on that day. But it'll be worth
it. Because
Speaker 129 (lower-pitched voice): when we get done, we'll make sure the same people in charge today are in charge then. How
many of you
Speaker 24: would have gone
along with
Speaker 24: that plan? How many of you would have been like, yeah, yeah, let's do it, George.
We
Speaker 24: good, baller. Let's go.
That sounds like a
Speaker 139: plan, W. I'll
put a W
Speaker 139: sticker on my car. W, the president. I'll
put that
Speaker 139: sticker on my car. My pickup truck. At
best, mixed results
Speaker 57: in Iraq. Who's in charge of Iraq right now?
Well, you know who controls large
Speaker 57: areas of Iraq? Iran.
Speaker 57: Iran controls large areas of Iraq. The same Iran we're going to war with now.
In the
Speaker 33: intermediate time, we had ISIS in control of large areas of Iraq. Syria controlled large portions of
Iraq at one point. That's why they can't be honest with you. That's why they can't be honest
Speaker 159: with you.
But it's
Speaker 43: one step further than that. Because Donald Trump can't get on the television and say,
we've decided
Speaker 43: to go to war with Iran. It's
going to
Speaker 43: take a
decade,
Speaker 52: maybe two. It's
going to require
Speaker 158: thousands, hundreds of thousands of American troops on the ground.
Probably going to lose 5,
Speaker 158: 10, maybe 20,000
Speaker 42: American lives over there.
Speaker 42: probably going to
Speaker 160: destroy their entire country. All their infrastructure, all their beautiful ancient buildings are probably going to be reduced to rubble. We'll
Speaker 61: probably kill in the neighborhood of one to three million Iranians just because that's how war is. You know, war sucks. There'll
be a flood
Speaker 61: of
Speaker 60: refugees. We'll get Iranian refugees that go out in every direction and just overwhelm other countries, their critical infrastructure, their hospitals, their schools.
and you
Speaker 35: can't blame them these people just want to live they don't want to be vaporized like is happening with the people who stay behind i mean i can't blame them for that you can't blame anyone who left afghanistan you can't
Speaker 128 (higher-pitched voice): blame anyone who left iraq you can't blame anyone who left syria they were dying we
were bombing
Speaker 136 (higher-pitched voice): them you can't blame someone if your country's being obliterated you can't Blame them for saying, maybe we'll go to Germany.
They don't
Speaker 162: seem to obliterate Germany very well. Not in the last 75 years have they obliterated them.
You can't blame these
Speaker 163: people. But
that is the
Speaker 163: inevitable result. And
if
Speaker 79: Donald Trump or Marco Rubio or Pete
Speaker 128 (higher-pitched voice): Hegseth got on television and was honest with you, if any of them were honest with you, if they said, listen, this is going to be, we're going to
tell
Speaker 17: you it's going to be quick, but it's not going to be quick. It's probably going to devolve.
Probably
Speaker 17: going to result in the loss of infrastructure for a lot of regional countries around there. UAE, Qatar, Oman,
Speaker 164: Jordan. These people are going to get hit hard. They're going to lose their salination plants, their desalination plants. They're going to lose oil infrastructure. Global shipping lanes are going to be shut down. Oil prices are going to explode. Airliners are going to be crushed. The average middle-class family is
Speaker 6: going to experience a fuel increase. It's going to feel a lot like a tax hike.
Speaker 6: Because a gas, a gas price increase is basically a tax hike. I mean, if, if gas prices go from $3 to $6 a gallon, but you have to drive 45 miles round trip to work, it's a, it's a tax hike. Like it, it takes money that you otherwise would spend on milk and bread. It
takes that
Speaker 6: money away
Speaker 58: from you.
It causes you financial
Speaker 50: harm, but if they came to
you and
Speaker 50: told you all this, you would not support it. You would revolt. Right.
in Charlie, there was a
Speaker 54: single human being probably with more influence over people under the age of 35 than anyone else in America. And
that single
Speaker 54: human being with all that influence was
telling you
Speaker 54: the truth. He
was telling you
Speaker 42: the truth. This would be a pathologically insane proposition.
If you
Speaker 42: go to war in Iran, you will regret it.
Not going to be
Speaker 42: easy, champ. Not
going to
Speaker 42: go well.
There'll be a lot of refugees. There'll be a lot of death
Speaker 54: and destruction.
And in the
Speaker 58: end, you may not get a regime change at all. They
may walk out
Speaker 58: of there 10, 20, 30 years later with the same people in charge.
We
Speaker 58: don't know.
And so he had to go. And so he had to
Speaker 165: go. I want to play just a few
more seconds
Speaker 165: of this.
That
Speaker 155 (lower-pitched voice): would have shaped his attitude towards this. You can say, we agree. He repeatedly said he thought regime change in Iran was a bad idea. The competing impulse there is he was a supporter of President Trump and President Trump's judgment in international affairs, and he was also an American patriot. And so this war having started, his take would similarly
be,
I was
Speaker 155 (lower-pitched voice): very hesitant for this, but I also do trust the president's judgment that he must have good reasons for this and that he would have a plan to keep this from extending
Speaker 156: endlessly and escalating out of control. Well,
Blake is lying
Speaker 167: to you.
He's just lying to
Speaker 11: your face.
with
Speaker 11: Charlie's name on the chyron in three different places, he's looking you in the eye and
Speaker 52: he's saying, Charlie would have been for this. He might have privately been opposed to it. He might
Speaker 61: have believed it was going to be a really terrible idea. He might have believed it was going to be a problem. But ultimately, he's a patriot.
He would have
Speaker 36: come around. Now, let me say this. I
like to think I'm a
Speaker 36: patriot. I like to think I'm going to come around.
But the
Speaker 146: difference is, and I think Charlie would have been this way. I don't know. I don't want to put words in a dead man's mouth. This is just my gut. I
want, I was very
Speaker 168: opposed to the strikes in Iran. Very opposed. But they've happened. A lot
of people
Speaker 168: have already died. Thousands of people on their side.
Speaker 25: At least six American service members on our side.
not
Speaker 25: to mention people around the Middle East that are getting hit, Qatar, Jordan, UAE, other places, Azerbaijan. Other
people are
Speaker 25: getting hit. They're knocking out missile sites. They're knocking out intelligence sites. They're knocking out civilian infrastructure.
But I don't want to lose. But I would
Speaker 146: much rather
Thank you.
the
Speaker 146: victory be pyrrhic or quick or even false, declare victory and get the hell out of there.
We came to do a
Speaker 169: regime change. We heard Israel was going to do a regime change. The
guy that was in charge
Speaker 169: is no longer
Speaker 170: alive. He's necessarily changed. We're getting out now. And
we're not
Speaker 63: getting back in. And whatever they do, however they recoalesce, however they come back together, However
they...
and
Speaker 63: reconstitute their
Speaker 52: government, that's them. We'll deal with them, and if they become a threat, then we'll figure it out down the road.
But they
Speaker 52: will coalesce, and they'll reconstitute the government knowing what happens if you remain adverse to us.
That's the best
Speaker 139: option you've got yet left. That's the best option that's still on the table.
Just get out. Get out,
Speaker 20: and on your way out, throw up. I'm sure they still have it.
it's
Speaker 20: got to be in a closet somewhere somewhere in the u.s military the department of now
Speaker 13: war not defense which frankly is is
more accurate the
Speaker 52: department of offense somewhere in the pentagon has to be george bush's mission accomplished banner it has to exist they didn't
Speaker 6: throw it away it's history did it the smithsonian but let's go get it let's put it up for ironic purposes we'll do
it in a
Speaker 6: very hipster fashion Thank you.
But
Speaker 6: we'll put it up on the White House lawn. We'll recreate the scene. But Trump's 80. He doesn't need to be flying around on
Speaker 52: fighter jet. So we're not going to land him on a carrier like George W. Bush did. We're not going to have him mosey up like he's in Top Gun and in Fatigue. But let's just have him walk out in his
Speaker 6: signature extra long tie, stand under the Mission Accomplished banner,
hold up
Speaker 6: peace signs on each
Speaker 64 (higher-pitched voice): hand, just like Tricky Dick did. I'm not a crook.
We'll have
Speaker 64 (higher-pitched voice): Donald Trump
Speaker 171: hold up the peace signs and go,
We
Speaker 171: won the war. Peace.
Peace is ours. Mission accomplished. I don't care how you
Speaker 139: do it.
Just
Speaker 172: get out. Get out. This is not going to end well. It's not going to go well. It's not going to end well.
But that's why Charlie's not
Speaker 173: with us. I'm
Speaker 5: convinced. I'm 100% convinced at this point.
I was
Speaker 5: only half convinced until the war started.
But now that the war
Speaker 96: started, I'm pretty confident that's
Speaker 160: why he's gone.
Because he
Speaker 174: would have been
a real
Speaker 174: problem. He
would have been a real problem. Because
Speaker 10: everything they're saying he would have said or done...
Speaker 10: who assumes he never sent that text on September 9th that said, I'm left with no choice but to leave the pro-Israel clause.
Once he sends
Speaker 175: that text,
he is a total
Speaker 175: liability on the Iran war.
A total liability. Because that's the only
Speaker 175: reason we're
Speaker 176: there. There's no American interest in this. There's no, oh, but
Speaker 177 (higher-pitched voice): Barron, we're going to change Chinese oil prices. That's what we're doing. That's why we're there. We're there to...
Speaker 177 (higher-pitched voice): Because the Iranians were selling oil to China.
That's not why we're there. That's not why we're
Speaker 179: there. We're
there because our
Speaker 179: greatest ally wants us to be there. They were going to war. They
were going to
Speaker 179: cause problems.
And I don't know what kind of
Speaker 179: dossier they have on Trump, but for whatever
Speaker 15 (lower-pitched voice): reason, they're able to drag him into anything they want.
i don't know
Speaker 15 (lower-pitched voice): if the tt dossier is real or what i don't know at this point
Speaker 5: but that's why we're there
that is why
Speaker 5: we're there but there's no tt dossier on charlie there's no russian hookers peeing on him that doesn't exist and
so he can confidently send the text i
Speaker 42: am left with no choice but to leave the cause send
but i'm an american i know
Speaker 180 (lower-pitched voice): 30 of the audience is from overseas i get it i see the stats i see you guys
but i'm an
Speaker 146: american i don't want to lose wars i don't want americans hurt i don't want to other people hurt frankly i don't like war you guys should know
Speaker 172: that by now if you watch regularly you know i hate war detest it despise
it but
Speaker 172: we're there so let's get out declare victory and let's get
out
But
Speaker 157: that's why he's gone. That's
why he's
Speaker 157: gone. You will never, ever, ever convince me
Speaker 32: otherwise at this point.
That is
Speaker 32: 100% why he's gone. There
was a time
Speaker 32: when I might have fucked a little bit on
Speaker 60: that.
I might
Speaker 60: have just a little bit wondered if there was some other reason. Some...
real
Speaker 181: estate deal that maybe he didn't want to get involved in and they all thought, oh, we
Speaker 182: were going to be billionaires.
Speaker 181: No, I don't think it's that anymore.
I think it's the war of
Speaker 183: the last nine days.
That's what I think happened. That's what
Speaker 184: I think. All right, now for the part that drives Gary crazy.
Speaker 185: Gary's mad. I
get
Speaker 114 (lower-pitched voice): it. He's mad. I do thank Gary for pointing out I took a pay cut to do this full time. but, um,
Speaker 114 (lower-pitched voice): Gary's mad because I entertain Q&A session at the end of the show. He thinks the show should be shorter
so that we're less
Speaker 186 (lower-pitched voice): effective here. We don't develop a good community and we don't have any fun, but I'm sorry. We're
not
Speaker 90 (lower-pitched voice): going to do that. On Saturday in Discord, we had a dog photo parade. Would be
Speaker 89: honored if Miss Tilly joined the puppy party next Saturday. I've had Tilly on air.
Have you
Speaker 89: guys not met? I've had her on air.
Or a
Speaker 187: lot.
I could
Speaker 189: bring her back on air. Let
me see if I can
Speaker 189: find her real quick. That would be fun.
She's coming in.
Speaker 190: She's coming in. We'll bring Tilly on air. She's more popular than I am.
I
Speaker 8: hear she comes I hear her come
Come on Kelly Come
Speaker 8: on I don't know if she'll jump up here She's too well behaved Come here
Come here Come up
Speaker 191 (higher-pitched voice): here Come on She won't come up I know you're a good girl Look there she is That's a good girl
Speaker 192: right there Look at you Yeah
she didn't
Speaker 192: want to come up Because she's a good
one
Speaker 192: he's a good one all right go
head out all
Speaker 192: right thank you
Speaker 193: that's tilly ladies and gentlemen that's tilly
it's hard to get her to jump up
Speaker 193: because i've trained her not to jump up
Speaker 195: she'll be like why do you want me to jump up i'm a good girl don't do that
to me
Speaker 195: don't do
that
Speaker 110: to me shabbat shalom daddy's home throw down the phone no not anymore
it's sunday
Speaker 110: this is the christian holiday
we
Speaker 196: don't Shabbat Shalom around here. Jesus paid the ultimate price. You guys like my mug I'm using today, queen of everything? Ah, yeah,
Speaker 110: yeah, yeah, well. Sometimes it's slim pickings. My, the humble cup of Joe Hopely's mugs are not in yet.
Speaker 198: Has
there been
Speaker 52: a moment
Speaker 32: where you and Daisy were searching for days for info on a particular show and you finally found what you needed in the nick of time? Baron has become the voice of my head. Can't fold laundry without it.
I
Speaker 39: found what I needed in the nick of time. No, but there have been times when the research has turned out to be in vain
because you look
Speaker 144: and you look and you feel like there's something there and you pull and you pull and you pull and you pull and you pull and then you look and go, that story
didn't pan
Speaker 144: out. That's
Speaker 43: happened. Nick of time research, I don't think so.
I
Speaker 43: don't think so. I mean, there
Speaker 36: have been times that the last notes are going into the run 10 minutes before the show. I mean,
Speaker 199: that kind of happened today, actually. I
don't know if Daisy ever
Speaker 200: tells you the dirty secrets of how these shows are put together, but I
Speaker 196: think I put the last show note in the run 10 minutes or so before the show came out. In fact,
I didn't
Speaker 196: even have time to queue up the link. I just threw a naked link in there.
Not
Speaker 201: a naked link. Not that kind of show. Not that kind of show. I'm talking about just a link without text over it. That's
Speaker 172: what I meant by naked link.
It's a
Speaker 38: technical term.
Just
Speaker 90 (lower-pitched voice): curious, how is Candace able to say the trigger words that gets everyone else throttled and show uninterrupted clips of other creators' content without being copyright struck? Love all your perspectives. So the copyright thing's interesting. I kind of explained this on the member show
Speaker 122 (lower-pitched voice): Friday. Okay.
Speaker 122 (lower-pitched voice): There's a difference in YouTube
Speaker 52: between creator content, meaning artistic content, and creator content, meaning commentary.
Basically, if you
Speaker 58: create commentary, like this show's commentary. So if somebody pulls up my show and, like, comments
about it, not much
Speaker 58: they can do.
But if it's art, if
Speaker 68: I create a song, if I put some song lyrics together and I've got an original Baron Coleman hit, right, and I'm doing my GACD thing on the...
On
Speaker 68: the guitar, I'm picking and grinning, and I'm singing about, you know, beer and pickup
Speaker 33: trucks and lost love, and I create a country banger. You can't steal that. Like, that's art.
You can't
Speaker 33: steal that.
That's the difference. That's the difference. So
Speaker 111: she doesn't really do the – she doesn't really play people's art without attribution.
And
Speaker 38: –
Speaker 38: she does what other people do. You can play a two, five, ten minute clip of somebody's content as long as you're providing commentary along the way.
And I
Speaker 38: get a lot of people like, stop stopping the clip and talking. Well, if I don't, I can't use
it. Like
Speaker 203: that's, I have to, I have
Speaker 38: to.
How does she get
Speaker 38: away with
Speaker 40: saying the trigger words? I don't know. It may be that it does serve to throttle her to some extent, but see, she is so overwhelmingly powerful
Speaker 10: and such a force that it doesn't slow her down
Speaker 90 (lower-pitched voice): any.
that
Speaker 90 (lower-pitched voice): could be
i don't know
Speaker 90 (lower-pitched voice): the answer to that america only yeah i'm about there honestly i'm
about to even tell
Speaker 90 (lower-pitched voice): canada to bump off i don't
care
Speaker 123: about you canuck no i'm just kidding i love canada we got your
back we
Speaker 123: got your back we've had your back since 1814 still
a little bitter about the
Speaker 178: war of 1812 but it's over it's
over and
Speaker 178: i've got
a 200
Speaker 172: year policy i
will only hold a
Speaker 172: grudge for 200 years
And
Speaker 172: you guys have passed that in the last decade or so. You are over the, I'm over the war of 1812. I'm
Speaker 52: over you burning down the White House. I'm over the attack on Washington. We're good.
You try it
Speaker 52: again. It's 54-40 or fight. You understand, Canucks? Moose jockeys, you get it? You understand what I'm talking about? Up there with drinking
Speaker 60: your Labatt's blue, watching hockey, drinking maple syrup. Don't tempt me. I'm
itching to get to
Speaker 60: that 54th parallel.
I
Speaker 60: haven't forgotten the fact that James K.
Speaker 13: Polk turned his back on 54-40 or fight in exchange for Manifest Destiny. I've not forgotten my American
Speaker 193: history, Canada.
Some of you
Speaker 204: guys
Speaker 193: are looking that up going, Manifest Destiny, 54-40 or fight? What the hell is he talking about?
James K. Polk, who's from
Speaker 32: Columbia, Tennessee, just down the road, gave up
on the
Speaker 32: Canadian fight.
Speaker 32: and he instead went for California which worked
Speaker 33: out in the long run
worked out
Speaker 33: in the long run hat on does that mean you got
a
Speaker 32: new barber and a haircut like last time no I got the same crappy haircut I had I was recommended to wear it I intended to go a little bad cop on the member show last time but then we started chatting and having fun and I didn't have it in
me at
Speaker 32: that point
Speaker 31 (lower-pitched voice): once
I started
Speaker 31 (lower-pitched voice): having a good time the bad cop goes out of
it
Goes
Speaker 205: out the window. So
I did it
Speaker 205: tonight instead.
What is the
Speaker 80: Baron Discord link? Will some mod pin it somewhere? I
think you
Speaker 80: guys can pin comments.
If you could pin it to
Speaker 3: the top, that'd be great.
Baseball cap is
Speaker 3: the male version of the low bun. Ooh, got your battle bun on, Candice.
The fact that she
Speaker 3: acknowledged the battle bun is amazing.
Speaker 3: amazing that had to be like the pinnacle of
of coach
Speaker 3: right there
Speaker 36: that is that was something
i was
Speaker 206: watching that live when it happened
Speaker 207: like oh she threw out coach oh
speaking of she
Speaker 51 (higher-pitched voice): mentioned george was watching coach and that's when
Speaker 52: she that's
when he was like you got
Speaker 52: to check out this clip of this
guy going
Speaker 52: crazy over your battle bun
I want
Speaker 52: to interview
Speaker 25: George Farmer. That's like my goal in life right now. I don't have many goals. I don't travel. I'm kind of a homebody. If you
look at my
Speaker 15 (lower-pitched voice): open scores, I'm not very good CrossFit anymore. I sit
in this
Speaker 15 (lower-pitched voice): office too long. Totally bombed 26.2. It was awful. I'm
going
Speaker 140: to redo it tomorrow. So I haven't put a score in yet.
It's not going
Speaker 90 (lower-pitched voice): to be good. It was funny. I was warming up the muscle-ups and
then I
Speaker 90 (lower-pitched voice): never got to them.
shouldn't
Speaker 90 (lower-pitched voice): have wasted my time
Speaker 154: um but no i uh
i want to interview george farmer i i think it would be
Speaker 96: such a good interview
george if
Speaker 5: you're watching candace if you're watching i don't want to she texted me today and we talked back and forth a little bit and i
Speaker 34: wanted so badly to write in
there i
Speaker 34: want to interview george
but I didn't. I
Speaker 34: don't want to do that. I don't want to play all my, I don't want to play my George card yet.
Speaker 208: Not yet. Not yet.
Speaker 33: 5149. Talking about James Lee. Had a great video recently about why the Iran war makes no sense. Almost like it's a planned Armageddon. Agree?
Let me come back to
Speaker 33: that. Let me read the rest of it. I have a knee replacement on Tuesday. If led, feel free to pray. I will do PT. Thank you for your work.
Speaker 33: Um, I actually have a friend of mine at the gym who had a knee replacement and I was very worried for him. He's actually stronger and
Speaker 10: squats better now than
he did
Speaker 10: before, but he did the PT buddy. And that PT involves some heavy squatting and some hard lifting.
So get a good
Speaker 10: PT and, uh, and
Speaker 106: gain that full, full range of motion. You only have a limited window. Like when I broke my ankle, they were like, you got a limited window to get your
Speaker 140: range of motion back. Cause once it sets in, it's in, that's all you got.
It's like a
Speaker 140: year basically. Um,
Is this a
Speaker 140: planned Armageddon? I think
Speaker 144: for some people, they would like to see it, and that scares the hell out of me. I was always brought up, again, going back to the George Bush era and before. We were told the other side
Speaker 57: were the ones that were trying to bring in the end times.
Now it's
Speaker 128 (higher-pitched voice): us. It's our leaders. It's scary. It's scary. Did
you see my email
Speaker 3: about friends dad used his patsy in murder? No, not yet. I'm a couple days behind. Okay.
don't
Speaker 3: usually catch a live
Speaker 33: yay appreciate when you read these super chats aloud i usually just pop the airpods in while i do stay-at-home mom stuff
Speaker 11: and don't always watch the video during that part appreciate it well i hope you just heard yours read aloud with your air buds doing stay-at-home mom stuff because um
yeah it's my it's my favorite
Speaker 52: part it's it's it's it's how i get to know you guys and to me it's my ability to jump in with the community because i don't get a chance to participate in all the comments
Speaker 32: During the show. I have
to do
Speaker 32: it after the show or at the end of the show.
Tell the
Speaker 32: haters to grin and bear. Yeah, they're just jelly.
Erica could
Speaker 140: have spent those eight months locked away while she had her son, Mikey McCoy. The time doesn't
Speaker 73 (lower-pitched voice): work. Mikey's too old for that. This, if she had a child, I mean, it's a big if,
but if
Speaker 73 (lower-pitched voice): she had a child during that eight months, that kid would be 17 or 18 years old now, not 23 or 24.
What if
Speaker 209: CK knew it was an arranged marriage
Speaker 107: and went with it for presidency, but then decided to divorce after learning more about EK and handling potential? I do think there's something to that, honestly. I
think there's
Speaker 41: something to the Charlie might have been aware there was a little arranged component to it,
Speaker 89: or at least, I mean, again, I'm not knocking him, but he
had not
Speaker 89: had a ton of success with the ladies. He just hadn't. And along comes Miss Arizona
Speaker 210: with her...
Speaker 210: giant blonde boof.
And she's got a
Speaker 211: thing for old Chucky, you know? I don't know.
Attend a mask for the first time today. At the
Speaker 211: end, everyone in
Speaker 213: the church drank out of three cups. No disrespect, but seems gross. Please explain.
At
Speaker 214: the end. And so a
couple of things. One is the
Speaker 26 (lower-pitched voice): cup is supposed to be metal, which helps eliminate knockdown germ transfer.
Speaker 26 (lower-pitched voice): Two, they do wipe it with what's
Speaker 32: called a purificator, a little napkin, essentially, linen napkin. Three, the wine has to be alcoholic. It has to have alcohol in it, so that's also going to cut down on the germ transfer. Four, you don't have to participate in the cup. In fact, a lot of places don't have one. I mean, I don't
know,
Speaker 215 (lower-pitched voice): maybe a lot.
Speaker 32: I don't
Speaker 215 (lower-pitched voice): know what the percentage breakdown is. Maybe half and half.
Half
Speaker 216 (lower-pitched voice): of them have it, half of them don't. Maybe it's a little more have it and don't. I primarily go to two different parishes around here.
One
Speaker 52: does have it and one does not.
But you
Speaker 52: don't have
Speaker 26 (lower-pitched voice): to. I never take it because I don't want to drink alcohol. I just take the host and go sit back down. I don't stop at the cup. The chalice,
Speaker 42: the chalice, the blood of Christ.
Speaker 42: I don't stop. I don't stop there. I just keep on going back.
Speaker 217: Well,
I
Speaker 218: arrived at the Joe crash out in my binging of this series. Best crash out ever.
Oh,
Speaker 219: gosh. That's there, huh?
I had to edit
Speaker 219: that down.
I hope you know what happens if you
Speaker 220: ask low IQ or
Speaker 221 (lower-pitched voice): make low IQ points. That happens. Thank you.
For the
Speaker 218: love of sweet six-pound, seven-ounce baby Jesus, please respond to my 17 emails about the MKUltra survivor and the Vegas shooting survivors I know. I cannot commit
to responding
Speaker 185: to any particular emails. Like, I commit that every email gets opened and read. I cannot commit to
Speaker 129 (lower-pitched voice): responding to every email. I know what you're talking about. I've seen it. And I've actually been contacted now by multiple people
Las
Speaker 129 (lower-pitched voice): Vegas shooting survivors and even a survivor
Speaker 222: of the shooting in Thousand Oaks, California, someone that was at both events.
Weird.
Speaker 223: But I can't commit
to responding to
Speaker 90 (lower-pitched voice): every email. Let's just like a slow day. Let's say we get 200 emails on a day. If
you spend one minute
Speaker 90 (lower-pitched voice): on every email,
Speaker 224: that's three and a half hours.
That's a
Speaker 224: lot. That's a lot of email reading.
If
Speaker 224: you read,
Speaker 67: respond, watch any video that's linked, you know, go to some web. I mean, you're looking at like a full seven, eight-hour
day
Speaker 164: just opening emails. I can't do it. Like, I cannot physically do it. I'm familiar with what you're talking about. If
it becomes
Speaker 164: time, that
Speaker 36: that becomes something I want to follow up, and I will. But I can't be...
Speaker 225 (lower-pitched voice): I can't be compelled to respond to any particular email. But no, I appreciate your emails. I've seen your emails. It wasn't 17, by the way. I don't think it was like five.
Unless
Speaker 226: you sent
a bunch more
Speaker 226: that I didn't see, but I think, I think there were just
a few, but I
Speaker 226: appreciate it. I genuinely do. And, and I have, I have interest in talking to different people on different stories, but
yeah,
And it's, you
Speaker 32: know, we've got shows planned, we're doing shows in order, and that's not quite on the agenda right now. So hang tight with me, hang tight with me. I'm not being rude by that, I promise. It's just fact. I mean, there's only so many hours in a day. There's only so many of us that work
on this
Speaker 32: operation. It's my sister, Daisy, me. That's it. That's the sum total of
this
Speaker 33: operation.
Speaker 33: uh did you see ad fleet's new music video about shabbat shalom featuring candace it's such a pop i love it i did i saw that one um i think everything
fleet
Speaker 154: does is
Speaker 35: great i
even heard tale of a
Speaker 35: potential new hit coming out soon i don't know
if it's
Speaker 35: out yet but i
Speaker 32: think there might be another one on the horizon that's
gonna slap i
Speaker 32: might listen to it uh first super chat. Love your Boilermaker
Speaker 227: colors.
never
Speaker 227: wearing this combo again, ever. We'll call it Vandy. How about that? I like Vandy. They're all right. You're
a fellow
Speaker 140: Boilermaker? Well, I'm not. I'm not. I like teams
that win
Speaker 140: national championships in both sports.
Are you
Speaker 25: originally from Indiana? Yeah, I was born in Indiana. I lived there until 1988. So for the first roughly nine years of my life, I lived there. And
then I went
Speaker 25: to law school
Speaker 33: at IU.
do you
Speaker 33: believe Mercedes takes it this year man I thought Ferrari was the team to beat until qualifying in the race last night holy mackerel Mercedes is fast
I don't
Speaker 4: see how they don't unless somebody else just figures it out between now and like the halfway point of the season but man they're fast man they're
Speaker 228: fast uh hi
I've been
Speaker 4: vacationing in Florida the past four nights trying to catch up
Speaker 229 (lower-pitched voice): what have I missed
not much
Speaker 229 (lower-pitched voice): not much Adrian you've got just a few just a few
Speaker 37: hours to catch up on. Watch it on Two Speed.
You'll see
Speaker 37: me doing this.
You'll love
Speaker 91: it. Counselor, no Shabbat Shalom from your Fed followers and radicalists. YouTube
Speaker 25: isn't going
to like
Speaker 25: that. I
actually did
Speaker 25: give a Shabbat Shalom at the end
Speaker 129 (lower-pitched voice): of the members show Friday, if that helps you feel better. But it was kind
of ironic and
Speaker 32: in jest maybe. Was Butler of Pennsylvania set up? In your opinion, Trump's your thing. Yes.
Speaker 32: Uh, my birthday was
Speaker 67: yesterday, but couldn't create, couldn't celebrate due to my daughter being ill. I'm happy to be with the jury now. God is good.
Speaker 26 (lower-pitched voice): Christ is king. Emojis are blurred. Um, Christ is king. Indeed. I don't know what that last line means. Emojis are blurred. They're blurred for me because I'm old and the computer's small. I
bear
Speaker 229 (lower-pitched voice): on. Did you get my email on the narrative credibility index? If so, I'm curious what you think. Appreciate your opinions. Christ is
Speaker 11: king. Go max. Christ is king. Indeed. I don't.
I don't
Speaker 129 (lower-pitched voice): know about the narrative credibility index. It's possible it's come in the last couple of days and I'm behind. But I promise you
Speaker 108: guys, if you send an email, I'm going to get it. Killer B outfit, black hat, yellow hoodie. Big Baron fan, love this high
Speaker 90 (lower-pitched voice): IQ outfit.
I'm a big fan
Speaker 90 (lower-pitched voice): of you, Linda. I
had no, I wore
Speaker 90 (lower-pitched voice): the black tee because I knew I was going to wear the black
Speaker 114 (lower-pitched voice): hat and I wanted to
kind of
Speaker 114 (lower-pitched voice): set it off, you know. I thought the white tee would cause the hat to look a little out of sorts.
With
Speaker 114 (lower-pitched voice): such a bright hoodie.
Have you
Speaker 36: noticed Operation Einstein Fury has worked? Almost nobody's talking about CK, Einstein, or Gaza. Makes me sick, but God
is
Speaker 52: slowly and continually giving us eyes to see. Christ is king. Yeah, I've noticed. Everything seems
Speaker 35: to be away. The news is just trashed right now.
Baron, first
Speaker 51 (higher-pitched voice): time Super Chat, making Mississippi pot roast. I love Mississippi pot roast. Holy mackerel. I haven't had that in a while. Mrs. Coleman, a Mississippi pot roast, please. No butter.
You
Speaker 114 (lower-pitched voice): and CO are my preferred pods. Keeping up the good fight. Love you.
Christ is
Speaker 114 (lower-pitched voice): king. Christ is king indeed.
Speaker 10: Hey, have you done a Mississippi pot roast with chicken thighs? It's
also very good. Very
Speaker 125: good. I love Mississippi pot roast with some roasted potatoes. Woo. Those
Speaker 33: pepperoncinis. That's
it all,
Speaker 33: baby. Thank you. That gave me a good idea for dinner one day this week.
Everyone hit the
Speaker 45: like button.
Speaker 45: See, here I was, not shaming you guys, and one of you shames you guys for me. We're
getting close
Speaker 45: on likes, people. We're
a little
Speaker 231: over a third. We've got to get more than that. These openings are top tier. The really new need to be put into a book format. Roll that beautiful bean footage.
I'm
Speaker 80: not opposed to that. We've got a website opening, and I think what I'm going to do is link the website to a substack
Speaker 31 (lower-pitched voice): that has the openings. Like,
has them in
Speaker 31 (lower-pitched voice): written
Speaker 226: form with the clips of the videos. That's where I think I'm headed next. I'm not sold on that, but I think I'm headed that way.
Hey,
Speaker 106: Barron, just wondering if anyone interviewed any of the pilots that flew into Utah. Barron, just wondering if anyone interviewed any of the pilots that flew into Utah.
Speaker 146: Um...
I have
Speaker 146: not. I don't even know
how we
Speaker 146: would know who they are.
I guess we could call
Speaker 3: the companies maybe and ask.
Speaker 194: Oh, wait a minute.
I can't tell you
Speaker 194: what's happening. I'm like, oh gosh.
There's some cool work being
Speaker 129 (lower-pitched voice): done out there. Hopefully it'll not a show of mine, but a fellow YouTuber. Hopefully
Speaker 26 (lower-pitched voice): it'll turn into a pretty cool show in the near future.
Speaker 26 (lower-pitched voice): Um, but it doesn't have to do with the pilots, but it has to do with some on the ground work and calling people and making connections.
Speaker 129 (lower-pitched voice): Um, yeah.
Uh, coach Barron need
Speaker 229 (lower-pitched voice): 26.1 and 26.2
Speaker 226: scores on record. My horrific 26.1 score is in, you can search it on the leaderboard. Uh, my 26.2 score hopefully
Speaker 129 (lower-pitched voice): will improve tomorrow and then I will put it in tomorrow after. So hopefully by...
Speaker 129 (lower-pitched voice): 10-ish, maybe noon-ish. I'm done with it, and I'll go ahead and put it in when I finish. I'll
get
Speaker 123: there. I'll get there. Just understand, I'm not fit right now. I'm out of shape. I'm
out of
Speaker 123: shape. I've never been like a 99th percentile guy. I think I was 70th percentile, give or take, last year. This year, I won't
be as
Speaker 123: good. It'll be lower than
that. A
Speaker 157: lot. Please
pray for
Speaker 157: my daughter-in-law, Meg. She is leaving tonight
for the
Speaker 157: war. Oh, Meg. I'm
sorry to hear
Speaker 157: that.
Speaker 232: I will. I will. That's so sad to me.
But
Speaker 164: baby Barron, still think brown shirt guy needs to be looked into. Please say happy birthday to my hubby Vinny. It's
Speaker 213: also our anniversary, 35 years. Happy anniversary, happy birthday. You don't
look old
Speaker 213: enough. I
Speaker 233 (lower-pitched voice): can't tell you're small, but you don't look old enough to have been married 35 years. Unless you got married when you're
Speaker 185: like three. But I, I mean, I've looked into Rick Cutler. That's brown shirt guy. But
I haven't found
Speaker 42: anything that would make a show.
Speaker 42: About Rick Cutler. Not really.
Did y'all
Speaker 42: watch Ian's
Speaker 34: 9-11 show Friday night? I haven't had a chance to see it yet,
but I
Speaker 34: intend to. I intend to. It was called Let's Talk About 9-11 or It's Time to Talk About 9-11. I intend to watch it.
I sent a
Speaker 26 (lower-pitched voice): chat about the Economist's magazine cover during member show, but you couldn't find. Do image search. YouTube won. They sent me original message.
I don't
Speaker 234 (lower-pitched voice): remember the keywords you told me to look up.
But
Speaker 234 (lower-pitched voice): let me try that real fast.
Speaker 235: Economist magazine cover?
Oh, it's
Speaker 237: called The World Ahead. I'm looking at it. Yeah, I
looked at
Speaker 237: it last time. I don't know what to make of it. It's like a bunch of cartoon things. You didn't
Speaker 59: tell me what I'm supposed to be looking for. You gave me that vague thing where you're like, look
at it and tell me
Speaker 59: what you think.
Speaker 37: I think there's a bunch of red and blue art
Speaker 37: some dollar signs or tank. I don't know. I don't know what I'm looking
for in there. I wish I did. I wish I knew I
Speaker 238 (lower-pitched voice): would love to be in on the inside on that cool, a cool thing. They seven, six Ford him and
Speaker 123: then captured him as a Patsy.
That probably
Speaker 123: means, Oh, that's that Sean Ryan thing. Yeah, maybe
what are your
Speaker 123: favorite healthy snacks? Um,
I don't know how
Speaker 122 (lower-pitched voice): healthy they are. They're big sugar bombs. I love medjool dates. Big fan of medjool dates. I like macadamia nuts, bananas.
Speaker 239 (lower-pitched voice): Look,
Speaker 240 (lower-pitched voice): meat and vegetables, nuts and seeds, some fruit, little starch, no sugar. That's how you eat. That's how you eat. Meat and vegetables, nuts and seeds, some fruit, little starch, no sugar. But yeah, I
Speaker 226: mean, I like macadamia nuts, pistachio nuts, almonds.
Speaker 226: Mac, uh, uh, dates, medjool dates in particular, uh, though sometimes I like the rolled up
Speaker 129 (lower-pitched voice): dates that have, uh, coconut flakes on the outside. Those are good
too. Um, you
Speaker 129 (lower-pitched voice): know, blackberries, raspberries, blueberries, any
kind of
Speaker 129 (lower-pitched voice): berry, strawberries, apples, um, Lara bars, L-A-R-A bars, uh, the, the chocolate ones are good.
I can't
Speaker 129 (lower-pitched voice): get out of my head the pick of TR in Dairy Queen.
Superman
Speaker 90 (lower-pitched voice): sponsored DQ back in May 2025, not September when the pick was supposedly taken. I think they looked into that and they said that the promo didn't end until like the end of September. So maybe there's nothing to that. Baron Babcock hat. That means a
Speaker 185: Joe style lashing in the stream. No, it just means me calling a bunch of people liars because they are, in my opinion. Hey,
Speaker 240 (lower-pitched voice): Baron, in my backyard, there's a private faith-based K-12 school with a founder from NASA as
well
Speaker 239 (lower-pitched voice): as a deacon who has 20 years military experience.
Speaker 239 (lower-pitched voice): you
Speaker 242: know that's
Speaker 147: kind of weird good evening Jamie
good evening great
Speaker 147: opening statement
Speaker 11: it was absolutely infuriating what these demonic three letter agencies keep doing and getting away with it has to be stopped shame on us for thinking Trump was the guy Christ is king indeed Lamb
Rocker
Speaker 168: let me tell you I think unfortunately I think Trump was our last chance Thank you.
I
Speaker 168: don't know that it gets better from here.
It's going to be
Speaker 168: hard not to fall into that trap again and feel like
Speaker 243: we're getting duped.
Good girl, I
Speaker 234 (lower-pitched voice): miss you so much. You are the most amazing woman I've ever known. I love you, and I'm a risk, but I promise I understand that. Love Harvey?
What are we
Speaker 234 (lower-pitched voice): talking about?
Running with
Speaker 244: scissors. I
think what
Speaker 170: happened is Harvey's gal left him Thank you.
Speaker 170: Harvey knows the gal watches the program,
and she's not
Speaker 106: accepting his DMs, may have blocked him, probably blocked him from texts, blocked his emails, and
so he's sliding into
Speaker 226: my comments, hoping I pull up the comment so that he can send a message to his good girl. I
hope it works out for you,
Speaker 184: Harvey.
I got
Speaker 184: bad news. I don't think it's going to, but I hope it does. I hope it does for you, Harvey, for you.
Speaker 184: five on it.
Speaker 123: Doctorate in evolution of flying squirrels.
Speaker 226: Yeah. So they, you just blew apart the Excel spreadsheet timeline I sent to you. EK liar, liar. Did I blow it apart? I don't know what that means. I
have to check
Speaker 71 (lower-pitched voice): something out real quick. I just, I just got an idea.
I think
Speaker 71 (lower-pitched voice): they pulled a fast one on us, and I think I might be able to expose it right here. Give me just a moment. The
way my
Speaker 71 (lower-pitched voice): brain works, you just reminded me to do something.
I'm going to way back
Speaker 72 (lower-pitched voice): machine her LinkedIn if it's available and
see when
Speaker 72 (lower-pitched voice): they change to all those ridiculous
Speaker 71 (lower-pitched voice): basket weaving. It may not have
been way
Speaker 71 (lower-pitched voice): backed, but it may not have been
way backed,
Speaker 71 (lower-pitched voice): did it
Speaker 245: get oh there's index there but did they keep it sometimes it shows it's indexed and then you click it and it says no
Speaker 237: yeah I tried the things I do for you guys oh this is a good one maybe this is it uh no not
there we'll have
Speaker 39: to find a way to do that
Speaker 114 (lower-pitched voice): because I doubt that's been that way for long I doubt they I think they realized they're caught and they updated it to make it look crazy
Speaker 36: We'll be right
Speaker 90 (lower-pitched voice): back.
ASU
Speaker 36: website says they only started an international relations degree in 2024. She said 2012, right? Yep. Hi, Baron. As an Aussie, I'm so disappointed about Oscar. These things are proving to be, these cars are
proving to
Speaker 36: be horrible. Even the loss of Max in qualifying was shocking. Keep up the good work. I love the
show. Yeah, the
Speaker 90 (lower-pitched voice): cars are terrible. That rear lock for a guy of Max's caliber should never happen.
So something's
Speaker 36: wrong with the cars.
Speaker 36: Never had EK defending XXX stars on my 2026 bingo card. Me either. I was kind of frankly shocked.
TPUSA claims
Speaker 36: Charlie Kirk
Speaker 246: wanted Eric Kirk to run for president. Puked in mouth. Yes. Bull butter. He never said she should be.
BB did
Speaker 31 (lower-pitched voice): it. He said it like OJ Simpson. If I did it, what's next? Nothing. Number one is bothered enough.
Speaker 247: Number one.
I don't
Speaker 238 (lower-pitched voice): know what all that means. Did you see the bust in Scottsdale? Candice reacting to it on X a few hours ago. No, I didn't.
But thank
Speaker 248: you. We will shortly. I
was preparing
Speaker 248: for a show a few hours ago.
Let me
Speaker 248: look. We'll all look together if it's up. Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah. Let's look at this. This is interesting.
Good
Speaker 248: call on this,
by the way.
Speaker 249 (lower-pitched voice): Let's see you guys. Let me see here. Where is it? Share screen. Share screen. There we go.
All
Speaker 37: right. Yes, I'm aware this allows people to traffic and sell without any consequence. Their law
Speaker 121: must be changed in Arizona. If a reporter learns
Speaker 250 (lower-pitched voice): the names of those arrested, please email them over to me.
is
Speaker 250 (lower-pitched voice): currently against the law in Arizona to post mugshots and names on social media related to arrests. There are exceptions for emergency community notifications such as wanted armed and
Speaker 121: dangerous suspects. Scottsdale, Arizona just arrested 202 people who were involved in transporting children and selling their
Speaker 250 (lower-pitched voice): services. Despite announcing this bust, neither the names or the faces of those have been released. Over
and over
Speaker 250 (lower-pitched voice): again, those are caught
have
Speaker 250 (lower-pitched voice): their faces protected. Federal law stipulates their mug shots are not released to the public. Why?
That's
Speaker 251: crazy. 202 people.
People are sick. That's a lot of
Speaker 184: people. I
wonder if any of
Speaker 184: them work at DPSA. I'm just asking questions. I'm just asking questions.
Speaker 252: Barron, please be Pat Copperture. I'm trying.
He did
Speaker 252: believe this, and I know why.
Speaker 90 (lower-pitched voice): Believe that it was a quagmire? I don't know what you're talking about. Oh, he did believe that
she would be
Speaker 90 (lower-pitched voice): president?
Speaker 226: By all means, realbaronpodcast at gmail.com. Feel free to email me the evidence. I'd love to see it.
Maybe they
Speaker 226: already printed the Vance Kirk ticket for 2028. Charlie Kirk out, E-K-N, Kirk surname,
Speaker 253: hence the narrative. Yeah, the problem is they put the...
They put
Speaker 253: the website up two days after he died.
Speaker 90 (lower-pitched voice): Random. Why don't you wear a wedding band? You don't seem like the kind of man to think that's not a big deal. Because I work out and my
Speaker 129 (lower-pitched voice): hands get all torn up. And I did wear one for a while, but it was just tearing my finger to shreds. It was tearing where you grip a pull-up
Speaker 31 (lower-pitched voice): bar. It was tearing that to shreds. So
I went
Speaker 31 (lower-pitched voice): to one of the silicone bands thinking that I might actually have one of those in here.
I went to
Speaker 31 (lower-pitched voice): the silicone bands thinking that that might work. No, I don't have one in here. And that actually
didn't work
Speaker 90 (lower-pitched voice): either. I don't go anywhere. I don't leave my house. I stay
at my
Speaker 254 (lower-pitched voice): house. I go to the gym. I come back to the house. I go to church. Come back to that. I don't go places. So I'm not, I'm not like a threat.
Like I
Speaker 254 (lower-pitched voice): don't go out
to dinner
Speaker 254 (lower-pitched voice): with buddies and
Speaker 42: stuff. I don't go to bars. I don't
go to
Speaker 42: clubs. I don't
go to clubs.
I go to
Speaker 42: church, I go to the gym, I come home.
Speaker 226: And my wife goes to those places with me most, you know, most of the time. So, um, but
that's
Speaker 216 (lower-pitched voice): why it's, it's just because taking it on and off every day got to be a hassle. So I just stopped
wearing, not a
Speaker 216 (lower-pitched voice): big deal. I
Speaker 154: would, yeah,
Speaker 255: not a, I mean,
that's why, uh, like I said, I
Speaker 55: don't think she wears one either actually for the same reason. I don't know.
Honey, if you're listening, do you wear a
Speaker 55: wedding ring?
Speaker 229 (lower-pitched voice): Um,
Speaker 229 (lower-pitched voice): Like I said, we're all living in one big episode of House of Cards, and that should scare the doo-doo out of all of us.
Yeah,
Speaker 140: yeah. Is Candace still pressing EK for a Fort Huachuca alibi? I think the request is on the table. We'd love to see an alibi. I
mean, that
Speaker 256 (lower-pitched voice): would be brilliant if she could come out and just say she wasn't there.
That would
Speaker 256 (lower-pitched voice): be the easiest way to solve the problem.
It might not
Speaker 63: work out for her well if she does that, but she could. She could.
She
Speaker 63: could absolutely just come out and definitively state, I was not there. I
love how Tyler's
Speaker 63: justification
Speaker 238 (lower-pitched voice): for Erica being CEO was the Erica was already there. Like, yeah, she's dumb as a sack of potatoes and as a demon lizard woman, but she's literally present. That's how low the bar was. Yeah. Yeah,
that's
Speaker 34: not ideal. Follow the money. Leah files on Substack and TikTok. The series will blow your mind. Thank you.
EK
Speaker 34: has a naughty video or she's Antichrist.
It wouldn't shock me. Either one,
Speaker 34: frankly. Regarding website, EK and Vance were together 9-11.
That's
Speaker 26 (lower-pitched voice): correct. They were. He flew into Utah to transport the body. That's a good point. Good point.
But no
Speaker 26 (lower-pitched voice): one was talking about her being president at the time.
Jameel Javani
Speaker 34: launched Restore the North campaign based on CK's campus model. Javani equals Vance's best friend from Khaled. Weird data point.
Speaker 229 (lower-pitched voice): Okay. Duly noted.
Speaker 154: That's the reason they were telling CO she was negatively affecting the Republican elections. It was about how it would impact EK's electability. Ah, and I didn't put that together.
That's a
Speaker 154: good call there, Gaga mom.
That's a good
Speaker 154: call.
Speaker 243: would you ever be up for doing a series in the
Speaker 180 (lower-pitched voice): future on government cover-ups et cetera surrounding different wars the u.s has been involved in i'd love to hear your insights bless uh god bless you yeah i'd definitely be up for that we could go back a long way
we go back to
Speaker 180 (lower-pitched voice): the mexican-american war if you want to and
that was a
Speaker 180 (lower-pitched voice): issue uh
now tp
Speaker 180 (lower-pitched voice): usa wants the
Speaker 226: kids in public schools
yeah i was
Speaker 226: watching a clip i don't remember what clip it was one of those clips i was watching had um
They were
Speaker 226: bragging about being in 30,000
Speaker 259: high schools.
Yeah, that's a lot. Erica
Speaker 111: equals Liv Schreiber's character in the film Manchurian Candidate. If not
familiar
Speaker 124: with that movie, Google for the synopsis. I mean, I'm familiar with the purpose of it, but not familiar enough to know who Liv Schreiber
is.
Leah
Speaker 218: Files on Substack
Speaker 25: says the way back shame proclaim 365 edit on 910 was she put up the Matthew 2540. Will you read that for us, please? Will
I read Matthew
Speaker 260: 2540? I'll
even read it out of the
Speaker 261: new Bible. I
don't get a
Speaker 262: chance to open this one as I
thought I would. What did you say?
Speaker 260: 2540?
I'm
Speaker 263: getting close
And
Speaker 264: the king Will answer
them Truly I
Speaker 266 (lower-pitched voice): say to you As you did it to one of the least of these my brethren You did it to me
She edited her website
Speaker 267: to put that up
New Bible
Speaker 268: um yeah
Speaker 238 (lower-pitched voice): okay done there
Speaker 90 (lower-pitched voice): are no coincidences everything happens for a reason yeah good call Erica I've grown a I'm a grown 35 year old man who's been all around the world that's legit seen some sketchy and outright creepy
Speaker 106: doo-doo and even all this gives me the creeps it's time we go tombstone that's my favorite movie
hell's
Speaker 194: coming with me Ha ha ha ha
ha ha.
It's
Speaker 194: not revenge he's looking for. It's a reckoning.
Speaker 240 (lower-pitched voice): Yeah, we need a reckoning. We definitely need a reckoning. That's kind of what I feel like we're doing here. Off topic, but have you figured out what plane EK
Speaker 33: is flying these days? For
some
Speaker 269: reason, N102DZ doesn't show any flights
for me
Speaker 269: since January. I'm
one of those
Speaker 229 (lower-pitched voice): curious people that wants to see where she's going. Yeah, so in January, they stopped sharing the public details.
You
Speaker 226: can still find
it on ADSB
Speaker 270: Exchange.
But I do
Speaker 270: think she's flying a different plane most of the time, if not all the time.
Show Vance Kirk
Speaker 229 (lower-pitched voice): 2028 was
Speaker 25: registered by Beacon Mask, a contractor out of Scottsdale, Arizona. Beacon Mask.
Speaker 218: I
don't know what that
Speaker 271: means. Beacon
Speaker 72 (lower-pitched voice): Mask.
Let's
Speaker 72 (lower-pitched voice): do this. I'm getting a lot of searches for beacon mask, like two words. Let me do one.
Is that a
Speaker 253: privacy company,
Speaker 238 (lower-pitched voice): probably?
Good data
Speaker 238 (lower-pitched voice): point. We'll look into that. Thank you.
I started
Speaker 272 (lower-pitched voice): to understand now why 300,000 kids went missing during the Biden open border years and more importantly, why this story just disappeared. Yeah, hundreds of thousands of kids go missing every year.
That's like a
Speaker 114 (lower-pitched voice): dirty little secret that nobody likes to talk about.
Maybe EK
Speaker 25: is a twin and that's why the story never aligns. I don't think so. Also, AK was definitely the one who gave CO the ex-log interview EK's feed a few weeks ago. What?
why
Speaker 114 (lower-pitched voice): would you say that? I mean, I don't know that you're wrong. I don't know that you're right, but I'm curious why you're so confident in saying that.
This is for
Speaker 114 (lower-pitched voice): Mrs.
Speaker 234 (lower-pitched voice): Coleman. Thank you for
Speaker 229 (lower-pitched voice): sharing Baron with us. You're the real MVP. My husband and I have been married for 16 years this year. Teamwork makes the dream work, praying for y'all daily. Thank you, Emily. Little do
you
Speaker 226: know, Mrs. Coleman gets all of it.
So that
Speaker 226: was hers anyway. I
don't spend
Speaker 229 (lower-pitched voice): money. She does.
Speaker 229 (lower-pitched voice): favorite day of the week sunday means baron show in the evening and one day closer to a new week with candace thank you for all you do baron home sweet rome was a powerful
book
Speaker 272 (lower-pitched voice): thank you for the share of such a great book yeah i love it i think it's a great introductory you know very readable book uh for
people who
Speaker 272 (lower-pitched voice): are curious or inquiring into the faith so thank you thank you for
Speaker 273: sharing
that uh let me some
Speaker 218: bad cop baron and sigh and slick back candace lol y'all rocks
I
Speaker 218: imagine we're going to get a power bun tomorrow. That's
Speaker 168: my prediction. That's my prediction. We're going low bun. Battle bun. My prediction is battle bun. I think
I
Speaker 107: know where she's going tomorrow. I think. I
think. I'm
Speaker 107: not 100% sure. I'm 80% sure. Charlie8625 said on MK he was writing a book. I don't
Speaker 90 (lower-pitched voice): think he is the one who finished that book and he was taken out before he could run
Speaker 274: for president.
I
Speaker 274: agree. I don't think he finished the book. I think it was substantially rewritten after his death. I'm
wondering if Eric and
Speaker 272 (lower-pitched voice): the gang are lying so much to distract you and Candace and Coach to
Speaker 240 (lower-pitched voice): go off in different directions away from the truth of who
Speaker 253: killed CK. Maybe. That's an interesting thought. But my thought on the lying is it's important to me...
to
Speaker 218: document
Speaker 108: the many different lies and inconsistencies and story changes and all that kind of stuff. Trust me, I'm sitting on a bunch that I haven't shared. And the reason is because it
Speaker 202: attacking her credibility or not attacking it, demonstrating her lack of credibility
cuts into her
Speaker 256 (lower-pitched voice): ability to say, I wasn't there. I was over here. I did that. Y'all got to believe me.
And
Speaker 256 (lower-pitched voice): so that does go to help
Speaker 25: solve the case because it takes her out of the equation. We can stop worrying about where she said she was. She's not a believable person.
Thank you for your
Speaker 25: research, Arch, and wanting the truth. You're a
great
Speaker 266 (lower-pitched voice): warrior, man of God, provider, protector, warrior, blessing, his family and community. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you for
Speaker 25: those kind words. I really do appreciate that. Barron, you do have talent on loan from
Speaker 146: God. You're
not a
Speaker 146: phony, baloney, plastic, banana, good time, rock and roller. Okay.
Speaker 275 (lower-pitched voice): No, I hope not. You should come out for T. Roo's library opening. Medora, North Dakota, 7-4-ish. Going to be a big deal. That
Speaker 242: sounds like
a fun time,
Speaker 242: actually. I've never been to North Dakota.
That sounds
Speaker 276: fun. That sounds fun. Is it safe? What
I worry about
Speaker 277: these days. Did you see Super Smart Crow?
I see a
Speaker 278 (lower-pitched voice): lot of super smart crows. Is there like a particular something called a super smart crow? They
also
Speaker 254 (lower-pitched voice): bought Kirk Vance 2028 on 9-21 and Erica Kirk 2028 on 9-12. Kirk Vance 2028 was 9-12 U.S. time. I
will look at
Speaker 254 (lower-pitched voice): Erica Kirk 2028
Speaker 279: after this. I did not know to look for that. If
Charlie thought Erica
Speaker 90 (lower-pitched voice): would be president one day, he was not the genius we're made to believe.
love
Speaker 90 (lower-pitched voice): you baron that's kind of the problem is they're destroying his legacy by saying stupid stuff like that
i wish i
Speaker 90 (lower-pitched voice): could send a pic but i just checked the security certificate of vance kirk and the location
Speaker 226: of issue is scottsdale that's interesting it's right
in line
Speaker 36: with my thoughts
been watching jesse
Speaker 36: i'm convinced crisis king i'm not convinced i like jesse but i'm not convinced
I
Speaker 36: wonder where those cabinet members live. That's a good
Speaker 90 (lower-pitched voice): point. Which two cabinet members, sir, are your customers? How
do you deal with
Speaker 146: family members who are
Speaker 233 (lower-pitched voice): Zionist? With love. I mean,
the same way
Speaker 233 (lower-pitched voice): you deal with anybody. You deal with them with love. Not worth destroying families over, you
Speaker 250 (lower-pitched voice): know? In
other
Speaker 280: words, say it's your grandma, right? It's your grandma.
Speaker 280: Both of my grandmas are past, but let's say I had
a living grandma and
Speaker 280: she was just a
Speaker 218: hardcore. Is it worth destroying all of my relationship with my grandma to convert one person
out of
Speaker 247: 330 million Americans? No.
No. No. We
Speaker 281 (lower-pitched voice): guarded poppy fields and patrolled villages about it. I was there.
Speaker 84 (lower-pitched voice): I'm ashamed as a vet now. I'm told that that was a lot of the
Speaker 84 (lower-pitched voice): plan was to keep the heroin running israel
and western
Speaker 266 (lower-pitched voice): allies spent two years turning gaza to dust complete air dominance genocide hamas is still de facto leaders and armed we think we can do anything to iran this is
Speaker 272 (lower-pitched voice): insane yeah i think that's a good point i mean you've got a
very
Speaker 90 (lower-pitched voice): little small strip of land very sparsely populated i mean not sparsely but not a lot of people
um and you're not able
Speaker 90 (lower-pitched voice): to defeat them what makes you think you're going after a country and 92 million people
and you're going
Speaker 90 (lower-pitched voice): to have
any
Speaker 272 (lower-pitched voice): kind of success.
Rad
Speaker 272 (lower-pitched voice): Catholic mom of three, number four on the way any day now. Husband is a lawyer. We both really love your show.
We are
Speaker 272 (lower-pitched voice): curious if you want to say which Latin mass do you attend? Thank you for all you do.
Christ is
Speaker 272 (lower-pitched voice): king. I don't
Speaker 254 (lower-pitched voice): want to say that, but thank you. Thank you. I appreciate it.
It's a
Speaker 254 (lower-pitched voice): TLM. It's not none of the other ones.
We haven't
Speaker 254 (lower-pitched voice): pressed hard
Speaker 282: enough on why Mikey just walked away.
I mean, we pressed
Speaker 282: pretty hard.
We pressed so
Speaker 283: hard they had to issue a statement supporting him and do a whole show on it.
But we can
Speaker 283: look back
Speaker 243: into it. Best friend's son in reserve just got called to get his affairs in order and be ready. Just had a little baby boy less than a month old. Heartbreaking. This
is not going to be
Speaker 83: quick, guys. Got
my master's in nonprofit
Speaker 215 (lower-pitched voice): leadership at Barrett University of Miami in the 2000s. Apparently, I missed class the day they taught laundering money and transporting kids. I guess
my
Speaker 38: degree is worthless for EK's gigs. Thanks for all your hard
work.
Go
Speaker 38: Mags. Y'alls, the rare double apostrophe, guys. The possessive
Speaker 284: contraction. The
possessive
Speaker 153: plural contraction. That's a true Southerner right
Speaker 172: there. That is not every day you get the rare double high comma. God's comma. Comma to the top. Thank you. Yeah, you can't
Speaker 239 (lower-pitched voice): work there. Too honest.
Speaker 239 (lower-pitched voice): E.K. is kind of like typhoid Mary, infecting everyone she comes in contact with in a bad way. She doesn't even realize she's the problem. Oh, she
Speaker 38: might.
I did hear DJT was
Speaker 38: having a new bunker built. I think it's under the east wind. I think it's under the ballroom, right? I mean, they've got a giant hole there.
What are
Speaker 38: they doing down there?
You wouldn't need
Speaker 38: a giant hole for a ballroom. Just
put a slab
Speaker 38: down and get to building.
and we
Speaker 229 (lower-pitched voice): gave the Taliban billions in our military equipment. Oh, yeah, it was a great success. It's all done by design. One world order. Christ is king. Christ is king indeed. Baron, you're so good. You've got your enemies tuning in.
Speaker 114 (lower-pitched voice): Oh, they're tuning in. They definitely tune in. I love this attack that broke
Speaker 153: up. I mean, I'm thankful because I told everyone I took a pay cut to do this, and Gary's out there proving it. Thank you, Gary. I appreciate that.
Speaker 153: Uh,
Speaker 218: regarding opening statement, Patsy's or CIs are allowed to continue criminal behavior. Even if it's blank of kids in Wisconsin, in my experience, very disturbing. Christ is
Speaker 45: King. Christ is King. Indeed. I have experienced that myself. In fact, there was in Auburn a few years ago, there was a young woman named Anaya Blanchard who was killed
by a
Speaker 129 (lower-pitched voice): guy. It
was a
Speaker 129 (lower-pitched voice): tragic story. I was on the radio when it happened.
And...
I
Speaker 129 (lower-pitched voice): surmised that the guy
Speaker 175: who killed her was a confidential informant. Why? Because he had multiple arrests, including trying to run over a police officer. Charges dropped. Jumping over the governor's fence with a gun in his hand. Charges dropped. Like, he just kept getting away with crimes. And
then he finally
Speaker 142: killed a girl. And I thought, this guy was a CI. Like, he was a legitimate CI. He was just breaking laws. Or
he was
Speaker 285: something.
He was something. Great
Speaker 285: job, Baron. Enjoy your lighthearted competence and articulate. Lighthearted competence.
I'm taking that as a compliment. And articulation. Why are you against the
Speaker 285: handgun theory? You mean the palm gun? Because it's not true. I mean, I don't think it's true. A,
I've watched that
Speaker 285: slowed down
Speaker 42: video from every angle you can. I don't see room for a palm gun in his hand.
Speaker 42: B, I've stopped the high-quality, high-definition footage the moment after he pulls his sleeve up and there's no room for it.
C,
Speaker 218: or three, I don't know if I'm counting or doing letters, but I'm on my third point here, third sequential
Speaker 229 (lower-pitched voice): point. He doesn't move his arm until after the noise. He's just reaching over. He hasn't even grabbed
Speaker 224: his sleeve or anything yet. The noise goes off, and then he pulls his arm up.
It just
Speaker 224: doesn't make sense to me.
Speaker 224: And D or four or
12 in base three. You math
Speaker 253: nerds got
a kick
Speaker 253: out of that. He
would have had to make an
Speaker 36: impossible shot in
such a
Speaker 36: fast, I mean, he didn't even have time to aim. He just picked it up and I just don't buy it. That's why.
I just
Speaker 229 (lower-pitched voice): don't buy it. They always say keep your friends close. And because a hardcore, well,
they always say keep
Speaker 229 (lower-pitched voice): your friends
Speaker 286: close and your enemies closer was true for Charlie because his friends, enemies, and wife are all on
the same
Speaker 286: team. Blake says
they're trying to
Speaker 286: maintain CK voice and yet they
Speaker 202: deleted all his videos. Make it make sense. And they're saying the exact opposite of everything he said. Please invade.
Speaker 287: Salamander salute Hoko for Morse code Bondi blinks? Huh?
Speaker 285: Okay, okay. Bayron, can't confirm, but I've heard the new White House ballroom was less about a ballroom and more
Speaker 288: about what's under it. That's what I just said. Modernized, expand, bonkers. That's what I said.
Safety
Speaker 289: car pit
Speaker 90 (lower-pitched voice): killed LeClaire. Okay.
You
Speaker 90 (lower-pitched voice): mean Ferrari was being Ferrari. They wore their clown noses.
They
Speaker 25: wore their rainbow afros. They wore their white paint on their face. They had their giant size 43
Speaker 121: slippers on.
They were honking
Speaker 121: their noses.
Ferrari can't get out of
Speaker 229 (lower-pitched voice): their own way.
They not,
Speaker 215 (lower-pitched voice): counselor, no ragging on pickup trucks. I'm
Speaker 290: not, I drive one. I'm not ragging on them.
Speaker 186 (lower-pitched voice): Charlie said, Erica would be president one day. It's hard to find
words to
Speaker 186 (lower-pitched voice): describe how ridiculous they sound. Pathetic, embarrassing, delusional. Yes,
Speaker 292: yes, yes. And more. What
if
Speaker 90 (lower-pitched voice): Charlie was a warning to comply or else? I believe that is, I can't tell you how many people I talked to in the immediate aftermath.
Speaker 153: They're like, we're not
going in
Speaker 153: public. I
Speaker 285: mean,
people who go in
Speaker 285: public are like, I'm not going in public right now. Do we figure out what's going on?
Speaker 285: jess happy thank
Speaker 218: you jess i'm gonna put a w sticker on my pickup truck sounded just like how theo would say it you've got to get on with theo and rogan people need to hear what you're saying keep going max crisis king indeed christ is king indeed um i
Speaker 285: would go on with either one of them in a heartbeat i don't know if they want to have
me um but you know how people say
Speaker 96: you have an open invitation i have an open acceptance
there are
Speaker 96: some shows that are just open acceptances
Give
Speaker 96: me the travel terms. Tell me when to be there. We'll record at 2 a.m. on a Sunday. I don't care.
Just let me
Speaker 96: know. I'll show up. No preconditions. No signing. I'll just talk. Candace was
that way. Never too
Speaker 36: late to smash that like button. When I saw it's never too late to smash, I didn't know where you were going. But yes, also smash the like button.
Speaker 42: Yes. Also smash the like button.
Speaker 42: Pronounced red dog good. Oh.
Oh. Hubby
Speaker 277: laughs at me because I always mistakenly say pansy instead of patsy. Question everything and trust no one. Well, maybe pansy.
Oh
Speaker 225 (lower-pitched voice): my gosh, you're kidding me. Maybe pansy is the right word. I'm getting a note from Daisy. I don't know how we're going to prove
Speaker 202: this, Daisy.
Speaker 202: After we did the video about the ASU program, I'm
going to pull
Speaker 202: it up. I'm told that's
Speaker 80: when the LinkedIn changed.
You know, we did the
Speaker 80: program about recently, the show about her lying about being summa cum laude and having a double major. After
Speaker 36: we did that show is when I'm told
that.
that
Speaker 36: it changed oh we got a time stamped video this is
Speaker 49: gonna be great
okay oh oh oh oh
Speaker 49: oh oh daisy's the best goat tier ladies
Speaker 38: well first let me show you what we're
talking about so if you go to her
Speaker 38: current educational status this means she still has control
over it if you go to her
Speaker 33: current meaning erica france phase current educational status Hold on, I got to get this pulled down.
you'll see
Speaker 80: right here that summa cum laude has been added to everything and you've got post-game stretching, underwater basket weaving. So they're trying to make it look like we don't know what we're talking
Speaker 105: about. But
ladies and
Speaker 105: gentlemen, we keep receipts. We
keep
Speaker 38: receipts. And
I've got a
Speaker 38: time-stamped receipt here showing you definitively it
Speaker 45: did not look like that.
just
Speaker 45: a week ago so let me share with you the screen and show you it did not say underwater basket weaving
it did not
Speaker 45: say summa cum laude on everything
you see what i'm you see
Speaker 110: what's happening
here these are
Speaker 103: deeply dishonest people
they
Speaker 10: added that so that when people, this is weird because I'm like right next to
Speaker 52: myself here. They added that so when people went to fact check my show and the claims, and as people were talking about it, they would see the underwater basket weaving, they would see the pre and post-game stretching, and they would assume, oh, this must be a parody. This must not be actually Erica France-Vey's
Speaker 293: account.
Honest
Speaker 294: people don't act like this. Honest people don't act like this.
This is not
Speaker 56: how honest people act. This is not how innocent people act.
We
Speaker 295: are
Speaker 42: dealing with a deeply dishonest organization led
by a
Speaker 42: deeply dishonest human being.
There's no other way to
Speaker 111: put it.
there's
Speaker 111: no other way to put it. A deeply dishonest organization
Speaker 21: led
by a
Speaker 21: deeply dishonest person who, when caught lying,
Speaker 128 (higher-pitched voice): doesn't have the shame in her soul to say, you know what, I've been lying this whole time and I feel bad about it and I'm sorry. I
shouldn't have
Speaker 5: told people I had an EDD in Christian leadership. I never did. I shouldn't have told people I had a double major
education.
At
Speaker 5: ASU. I didn't. I shouldn't have told people I graduated summa cum laude. I didn't.
Speaker 58: Instead, they update the website to
make sport
Speaker 58: of it. Now, it's
Speaker 11: just my opinion that she has control over this website. It's an informed opinion because it's been up a long time before anyone knew who she was.
And it's said the same
Speaker 11: thing for a very long time, for multiple years.
And I
Speaker 146: just cannot imagine somebody...
would
Speaker 144: be playing the long enough game to open a LinkedIn under her name five years ago and populate it with all these things that are not true.
On the off
Speaker 144: chance that one day she gets
Speaker 6: married to someone who's influential, who dies tragically, and she takes over his job and she gets caught lying.
that's
Speaker 296: not a reasonable set of facts on which you could rely. These
people deserve
Speaker 297: all the hell we're giving. They just do. They just do. I
would like to
Speaker 298: see
Speaker 60: I'll see
Speaker 229 (lower-pitched voice): you
Speaker 90 (lower-pitched voice): next
Speaker 11: time.
Tyler Boyer, Andrew
Speaker 60: Colvett, or Erica Kirk come out and say that they had nothing to do with it.
They have no idea
Speaker 229 (lower-pitched voice): who controls that page and
that they had nothing to do
Speaker 229 (lower-pitched voice): with it changing and they had
Speaker 90 (lower-pitched voice): nothing to do with the errors on there and that they have no idea why Erica Kirk's articles talk about her
being a
Speaker 90 (lower-pitched voice): double major because she's
never
Speaker 11: said that because that major didn't exist. She never claimed to graduate summa cum laude or magna cum laude because she knows she didn't.
or
Speaker 96: here's evidence she did. Here's my official transcript.
Speaker 7: Here's my
Speaker 96: P.O. box,
Speaker 7: guys. Here's how you
can prove it. Every
Speaker 7: school will mail transcripts wherever you
tell them
Speaker 7: to mail it.
Like if you apply
Speaker 144: for a
Speaker 5: job or a security clearance or you apply for a bar license or a medical license, you have to, or school, a lot of schools require
Speaker 38: that. You have to mail your transcript directly from the school. It cannot pass through your house on the way there.
Speaker 38: If you guys will mail me the transcripts, I'll review them,
and I
Speaker 38: will report whatever they say.
But that's
Speaker 299: bonkers. That's
just a level of
Speaker 299: dishonesty that just shouldn't happen. Oh,
gosh, you
Speaker 300: serious?
see
Speaker 25: why i'm against war some family line was just devastated somebody's grandchild somebody's son or daughter
brother
Speaker 234 (lower-pitched voice): sister aunt uncle niece nephew mom dad all
the kids that wouldn't
Speaker 247: be born from that person all the grandkids that wouldn't be born from that person an entire line just wiped out for what
Speaker 301: I'll
see
Speaker 34: you next
Speaker 303: time.
For what? Stop,
Speaker 34: guys. She's just happy it's her first
at company
Speaker 34: that's made Delaware over 50,000, not to be morbid, but her husband had to die for that hit. Yeah. Ugh.
Speaker 303: Hmm.
Sorry,
Speaker 303: that news of the seventh shook me.
If Erica shows
Speaker 215 (lower-pitched voice): up on the ballot, I will vote for the opposing candidate. She's pure evil, horrible
Speaker 229 (lower-pitched voice): speaker, and has no business being the vice president. Well, that's, again, if they're even considering
Speaker 226: that, this series must continue.
Ah, Barron's rants
Speaker 226: are the best. Thank you, ShortCoin. Your comments are the best. They've had so many deceased coming
Speaker 266 (lower-pitched voice): into Dover AOFB, they are hiring in the mortuary. I
thought they
Speaker 266 (lower-pitched voice): only had six or seven. Are they slow rolling them?
Are there
Speaker 266 (lower-pitched voice): more when they're not telling us?
Check
Speaker 304: out podcaster George Galloway for his intel from Iran, Israel. My non-Zionist pastor told us about it today. Much
Speaker 291: more devastation in Israel than we're being told with nukes available.
Speaker 239 (lower-pitched voice): If they keep taking hits, they may resort. Surely not. I just, surely not.
RBP and the high
Speaker 218: IQ and common sense that keeps us sane in the insanity of the slop. Thank you, God bless.
Speaker 218: thank
Speaker 41: you very kind show us the dog I showed you the dog oh that probably came in
my hands
Speaker 41: still smell like the dog
Speaker 153: from petting her
I got
Speaker 153: dog hair on me she's
a very good
Speaker 153: dog she doesn't jump and so now she's
Speaker 238 (lower-pitched voice): probably confused she's probably sitting in there on one of her two beds she's got two beds three beds really she has a cage she sleeps
in
probably
Speaker 238 (lower-pitched voice): sitting on one of her beds, shaking her head like, why did granddad make me jump up on him? He tells me all the time not to jump up. Why
did he
Speaker 238 (lower-pitched voice): make me jump up? She
calls me granddad. And then I got to go in
Speaker 36: there tonight,
and I
Speaker 36: got to explain it to her.
We only jump up for the
Speaker 36: camera, Tilly. We don't make it a habit.
Speaker 153: You can show off on the show. Outside of that, stay down.
Speaker 153: I can assure you nobody cares
Speaker 90 (lower-pitched voice): what Gary thinks. Don't mess with the moneymaker. He's jealous. Edge. Yeah, I don't care
what he thinks. I just
Speaker 90 (lower-pitched voice): appreciate him helping me out. You, not Baron, can't be for war and not be willing to be a fighter in it. Most won't be willing to fight. Not
Speaker 96: you, Baron. Oh, you other fictitious you can't be for war and not be willing to fight in it. Most won't be willing to fight or sign your kid up.
or
Speaker 243: sign your kid up if you're too old. Why
has no one talked to
Speaker 239 (lower-pitched voice): Charlie or Tyler's parents? Also, did you ever show the picky reference of Erica at Wachuka on the 9th? So second
Speaker 90 (lower-pitched voice): question, no. Why
has no one talked
Speaker 90 (lower-pitched voice): to Charlie's or Tyler's parents? I don't know.
Speaker 305: Charlie's, like Tyler's parents would be very dumb to talk on the record, frankly.
I
Speaker 306: mean, their kid's sitting on death row. I mean, in a death penalty case. That would not be
Speaker 180 (lower-pitched voice): smart for them. Charlie's parents, you know, they're free to talk, but they're mourning the loss
of
Speaker 243: their son. I think it would be a little invasive to call them and ask them to go on the record
or even
Speaker 243: off the
Speaker 218: record. I
mean, if they reach out to
Speaker 218: somebody, that's different. I believe your thoughts on why he has gone, it absolutely breaks my heart. If that's true, even if they win a war, they will never make it out of hell. Kids lost an
Speaker 226: amazing dad for this, so sad.
Rest in
Speaker 226: peace, Charlie. Yeah, I tend to agree with that,
Speaker 307: unfortunately.
Pray for reigning
Speaker 234 (lower-pitched voice): Christians, one million plus, ready
to share
Speaker 234 (lower-pitched voice): Christ. Revelation 7, 9 to 10. Great multitude from every nation,
Speaker 180 (lower-pitched voice): tribe, and tongue. Christ is
Speaker 38: king indeed. Yeah,
I read
Speaker 38: that the other day. They had a million. It's a pretty high volume considering what
Speaker 90 (lower-pitched voice): we're told. Tilly looks like my old soulmate dog, Jackson.
My
Speaker 90 (lower-pitched voice): great Carolina yard dog, he was the best. Yeah, I can't figure out if Tilly's a Feist or a Carolina dog. She's kind of in between the size of the two, and she
looks like both. If you look
Speaker 90 (lower-pitched voice): up brown
Feist, she
Speaker 90 (lower-pitched voice): looks exactly like one. But if you look up brown
Speaker 34: Carolina dog, she looks exactly like one. She's kind
of right
Speaker 34: in between, like 10 pounds too big for a Feist and 10 pounds too small for a Carolina dog.
She might be a
Speaker 20: mutt of a Carolina dog and a Feist.
Not ruling it
Speaker 164: out.
uh
Speaker 164: djt betrayed
Speaker 114 (lower-pitched voice): his loyal base the war is mission accomplished only for little country controlling the entire admin much by infiltration allegedly
we
Speaker 226: must all pray for a quick end ps hugs to tilly until he's popular more popular than your humble host
uh raise your
Speaker 226: hand i think baron should accept one of the sponsorships
he's
Speaker 90 (lower-pitched voice): been offered so i haven't mentioned that on the attacks um
but I
Speaker 90 (lower-pitched voice): promise you I've turned down
Speaker 153: more than I'm making. I just told you, I actually had one guy say, you are out of your mind. And I'm like, I don't, I'm not ready to do that. Like I,
Speaker 308: this is a listener supported operation. We do a Q and a, it's already long enough. You know, if I cut it to an hour and didn't do the Q and a and we, we switched it. So the listener, you know, but right now I'm enjoying this and they seem to be enjoying it.
And so
Speaker 252: that's how we do it. Um,
But I
Speaker 252: promise you that would be a revenue increase if I did. And I'm not going to right now. So
Speaker 226: I, you know, but I don't want to indulge the haters. I don't want to indulge the critics. But just thank you for pointing that out. But I'm not going to
Speaker 90 (lower-pitched voice): right now, Natalie. Unless you're one of the
Speaker 38: advertisers trying to get me to join you. I love Bad Cop. Please bring Bad Cop out once a week at least. I don't know about once a week.
Still
Speaker 38: trying to force a Vance Kirk ticket. Are they really? Is that
still a thing? Please do a
Speaker 38: deep dive on Vatican
Speaker 34: translator Mauro Biglino reports on Bible mistranslations of Kavad, Rosh, Elohim, El Shaddai, Yahweh, El Elyon, et
cetera. Let me look real
Speaker 310: quick.
Let me
Speaker 310: just type in a note here to look at it. This interests me. This is the type of
stuff
Speaker 248: I like. Mauro Biglino.
Okay, I'll look at
Speaker 226: him. He's on my notes.
Baron, my
Speaker 226: nickname is the queen.
Well,
Speaker 291: Mary, so
is my
Speaker 291: wife. That's why we have the queen of everything mode. She's the queen.
Why are
Speaker 90 (lower-pitched voice): people so territorial? We are all children of the world. I do not appreciate Trump at all. He's a liar. Well, I'm certainly starting to trend
Speaker 226: that way. I love how you always have Candace's back. It's also fantastic when you laugh. Oh, well, thank you.
I do, I
Speaker 226: do, because
Speaker 90 (lower-pitched voice): I think she's, I
think the
Speaker 90 (lower-pitched voice): work she's doing is so incredibly important right
now.
Have I heard
Speaker 180 (lower-pitched voice): from Mark and Shani lately concerned about her? Seems like it's been a while. She chimed in last week. I mean, she's kind of a once-a-weeker, sometimes a twice-a-weeker. So I anticipate we'll see her.
But you're
Speaker 226: right. If we don't, I'll have to try to track her down. I do worry about her. You're right about CK Aran being a thorn to them, IMO. I wonder whose fingers over the delete button watching all the videos TP pulled immediately. His family erasing selected...
Speaker 226: opinions from history. Disgusting.
Speaker 223: I'm
Speaker 90 (lower-pitched voice): curious who has the authority to delete those videos. It's a good question. Baron, the Iran war coupled with bizarre American Zionist global
Speaker 311 (lower-pitched voice): goal to force the second coming is why this happened to Charlie. The motive and why they went along with it so easily, allegedly.
Let me just
Speaker 311 (lower-pitched voice): point out a very basic tenet of Christianity.
and I know
Speaker 311 (lower-pitched voice): there are people that are going to disagree with this, and I'm happy to hear your suggestion, but this is my understanding. I'll
Speaker 36: entertain people saying the other side, if there is one. But when Jesus died, the temple veil split from top to bottom. And
the classic
Speaker 175: Christian interpretation of that was, it's because the temple no longer had significance. The temple housed
Speaker 129 (lower-pitched voice): God's presence.
When Jesus
Speaker 129 (lower-pitched voice): died, it split from top to bottom, opened up, meaning the presence of God is now in the world.
In the
Speaker 129 (lower-pitched voice): hearts of his believers,
Speaker 125: it's in the Holy Spirit.
So why are
Speaker 125: we trying to force some go backwards into some system that nullifies
the
Speaker 96: sacrifice of Christ? I don't get it. It was the ultimate sacrifice, the Paschal Lamb. I don't understand this fascination with temple
Speaker 6: worship.
It is so contrary
Speaker 6: to Christianity. And I have yet to find anyone explaining. And I've gone looking.
I
Speaker 6: looked on Rob McCoy.
Speaker 96: looked for Frank Turek. Someone explain to me why reinstituting temple worship will
Speaker 175: further the cause of Christ. I can't find an answer to that. So that's an open call. Anybody knows the answer to that,
Speaker 218: email me. Realbaronpodcast at gmail.com.
FYI, someone has clips from
Speaker 218: a member
Speaker 114 (lower-pitched voice): show on their YouTube. Well, they're not supposed to.
I mean, I really don't
Speaker 147: care, but...
Speaker 147: Um, I do care because people pay good money
Speaker 80: to be a member in those shows. What happens in the member chat stays in the member chat. So send me a link to it. I'd like to
at least look
Speaker 80: at
Speaker 279: it, see if it's something that bothers me. Um, yeah,
Speaker 268: realbaronpodcastgmail.com.
Speaker 254 (lower-pitched voice): Go ahead and email me. I'll look at it. Daylight savings time.
Speaker 254 (lower-pitched voice): Not savings, savings in the bank.
Yeah,
Speaker 36: it's a Southernism. Like we say, the Kroger's.
I got to go to
Speaker 278 (lower-pitched voice): the Kroger's and pick up some milk.
We add S to everything. It's not
Speaker 278 (lower-pitched voice): you, it's me. It's 40,
Speaker 272 (lower-pitched voice): 37 years, 35 years of living in the South. I can't help it.
We
Speaker 240 (lower-pitched voice): say savings time.
we
Speaker 240 (lower-pitched voice): say driver's license. Like there's more than one driver on each license. No, it's a driver license, but we
Speaker 38: say drivers. And
we get frozen
Speaker 38: yogurt at the TCBYs. Some bro-yo. Remember when that was a thing? CO
hosted a
Speaker 38: debate
Speaker 229 (lower-pitched voice): with George and AB Stuckey. He was amazing. Thank you.
Only one
Speaker 168: of them would have been amazing Not, I mean Candace obviously amazing But only between George and Allie Beth Only one of them could be amazing
Speaker 36: I am so unimpressed with that woman So unimpressed Did
you ever
Speaker 36: find the large object being carried in the background Of the USA guy video Hosted in Discord RBP pod discussion tab 2 It's
Speaker 312: really strange I haven't seen that
I was
Speaker 95 (lower-pitched voice): 11 on 9-11. My fifth grade class watched Second Tower Fall Live for basically 20 years. I believe they
Speaker 90 (lower-pitched voice): hate us for our freedom and we will be treated as liberators. Eventually realize propaganda happens in America.
Yeah, we were not
Speaker 90 (lower-pitched voice): treated as liberators. And
they
Speaker 313: don't hate us for our freedom. They hate us because we keep destroying everything around them. Jumped in on, and
Speaker 314: well, that's assuming that that's the best reading of it, frankly.
um
Speaker 254 (lower-pitched voice): the probably more accurate reading is even darker than that
jumped in
Speaker 254 (lower-pitched voice): on
Speaker 25: live from binging on past episodes up to 45 now there i see djt blacklisted
captures
Speaker 240 (lower-pitched voice): my sentiments exactly is bad cop going to crash out on djt or did i miss it already um
no no i mean i
Speaker 180 (lower-pitched voice): might
Speaker 168: it's building it's coming if things don't turn quickly
Iran, no
Speaker 168: Rothschild Central Bank, just like Libya, Iraq, Venezuela, and Afghanistan.
Speaker 254 (lower-pitched voice): Coincidence? Probably not.
Don't hold
Speaker 254 (lower-pitched voice): back, Iran. We're counting on you. I'm not rooting for the defeat of America. I'm not going there.
I just want it
Speaker 254 (lower-pitched voice): over. I
Speaker 240 (lower-pitched voice): want it done.
Barberin, Ms.
Speaker 240 (lower-pitched voice): AZ, and a basketball player. She was totally set up for CK. He never knew about her real past.
Speaker 218: Yeah, I wonder things like, did Charlie think she graduated summa cum laude with a double major? Did
Charlie know she only
Speaker 218: played one year of college
Speaker 256 (lower-pitched voice): basketball at Regis? I
mean, of
Speaker 256 (lower-pitched voice): all the
lies were
Speaker 256 (lower-pitched voice): continually fed, did he buy them?
I
Speaker 315: feel so
Speaker 316: bad for that, man. I
feel so
Speaker 316: bad that that was his life. Hey,
Speaker 114 (lower-pitched voice): Baron, please look at footage I sent you titled security camera
Speaker 240 (lower-pitched voice): footage of a lead shooter walking to and from UVU has been edited. Look in new email. Maybe Eric is Uncle Rick at UVU with podcaster that gives us so much. Uh...
Yeah, I'll
Speaker 317 (lower-pitched voice): look at it.
Thank you. He has
Speaker 226: broken so many stories. He has done more to support Candace Owens than
Speaker 240 (lower-pitched voice): probably anybody else on YouTube. Your humble host included. I credit many things to Charlie. His passing introduced me to the atrocities Philly has committed. I had no idea how embedded they are into our nation's political system. Last, how is lobbying legal?
Good
Speaker 164: question.
Speaker 164: E.K. told Jesse Waters she saw the evidence. Her lawyer told CO they haven't seen anything.
Tracy
Speaker 318 (lower-pitched voice): trailed off saying C.K. had told E.K. home needed her. Her mom needed her during the interview with Big Ears.
Thanks,
Speaker 240 (lower-pitched voice): Fleet. Can't unsee it. These bug me.
Oh, you're
Speaker 240 (lower-pitched voice): saying the inconsistencies, the lies, the.
Yeah, remember that was a thing
Speaker 240 (lower-pitched voice): that you should
Speaker 319: see the evidence that the police have shown them.
It's not even
Speaker 320: anything.
but for
Speaker 185: Candace,
Speaker 320: we wouldn't
Speaker 185: know that.
Thank you
Speaker 185: for that contribution, Mother.
From
Speaker 114 (lower-pitched voice): Quebec, Christ is King, indeed. Iran, Tehran, last October, new subway station, all about Jesus Christ and the Virgin Mary. I have, Iran have one million Christians, Palestine, land of Jesus Christ, Nazareth, go Max guys. It's almost
Speaker 26 (lower-pitched voice): like they're targeting those sites for a reason, almost like,
Speaker 26 (lower-pitched voice): Jesus is an impediment.
Super
Speaker 90 (lower-pitched voice): chat's dedicated to that guy, the most unlikely promoter of Barron's High IQ
Speaker 239 (lower-pitched voice): Grand Jury. If
you are
Speaker 239 (lower-pitched voice): watching, Gary, this one's for you. Let's
not
Speaker 124: attack. I
shouldn't have
Speaker 124: brought him up.
I shouldn't have
shouldn't have
Speaker 124: brought them up we need a full stream members live on the iran situation especially from
Speaker 218: an attorney's point of view yeah i might do that
Speaker 234 (lower-pitched voice): on a members live i don't feel like i can unleash
and have youtube
Speaker 234 (lower-pitched voice): not freak out so i might
have to
Speaker 234 (lower-pitched voice): put that behind a paywall how
Speaker 146: did i end up south of nashville i've lived here since 1988
off and on uh
Speaker 146: just where my parents moved when i was little
and it
Speaker 146: always
Speaker 90 (lower-pitched voice): felt like home so we came back
Speaker 90 (lower-pitched voice): Uh, did CK actually go
Speaker 175: to Tempanogos? Oh, I learned it's not Tempanogos. It's Tempanogos. That's
from a Utah
Speaker 175: native. He
said, you
Speaker 254 (lower-pitched voice): know, you pronounce Tempanogos wrong. I was like, what do you, how do you pronounce it? He's like Tempanogos. And I'm like, that's what I say. He's like, no, you say Tempanogos. It's
Speaker 25: Tempanogos. I'm like, gos, gos.
Speaker 164: It's like my wife thinks that D-A-W-N and D-O-N, Dawn and Dawn, she thinks those are pronounced differently.
like
Speaker 176: my sister thinks Laura and Lara are pronounced differently. Oh, the same word,
Speaker 31 (lower-pitched voice): Laura.
Speaker 185: Um, oh, sorry. Uh, what about M Tala? Could hospital have been a meetup communication hub, 100 hospital with baby or H case cover story. I don't know.
Speaker 239 (lower-pitched voice): That's good. That's good thought. I don't know. Maybe
I never thought about
Speaker 239 (lower-pitched voice): the hospital being a
Speaker 267: hub of, of an Intel spot that would explain them trying to get the cameras, the
Speaker 266 (lower-pitched voice): footage.
There's an
Speaker 266 (lower-pitched voice): interview with Henry Dell.
He said
Speaker 266 (lower-pitched voice): when security was screening their questions, Hunter
got a
Speaker 266 (lower-pitched voice): different question approved.
Nothing at
Speaker 266 (lower-pitched voice): all about guns.
Then
Speaker 321: switched when he got up there. Henry's confused.
Send
Speaker 322: me
Speaker 321: that interview. Send me that
Speaker 114 (lower-pitched voice): interview, Jennifer. Realbaronpodcast at gmail.com. I'll put it up on the screen so you know how to spell it. Realbaronpodcast at gmail.com. Realbaronpodcast at gmail.com.
Send me
Speaker 114 (lower-pitched voice): that interview.
Speaker 129 (lower-pitched voice): Put in the subject
Speaker 114 (lower-pitched voice): line, Henry Dell interview.
Okay.
I have not
Speaker 114 (lower-pitched voice): seen that.
If I
Speaker 114 (lower-pitched voice): did, I don't recall it making an impression
Speaker 26 (lower-pitched voice): at the time. Big
family, try
Speaker 26 (lower-pitched voice): this.
Speaker 275 (lower-pitched voice): I'm 66
and my
Speaker 275 (lower-pitched voice): mother's ninth and youngest. My father's fourth and youngest and
the only
Speaker 275 (lower-pitched voice): child of both my parents.
That's pretty
Speaker 323: wild. You
got a lot of half-siblings. Pilots could
Speaker 323: email clandestinely.
I
Speaker 264: don't uh oh you mean the uh the pilots from
the from
Speaker 264: that day could email
Speaker 25: your humble host
at realbaronpodcast.gmail.com is
Speaker 324: that what you're saying they could I'm open
Speaker 325: pilots if you're watching how
did I know Erica's
Speaker 239 (lower-pitched voice): lying her lips moved yeah granted
Perhaps
Speaker 239 (lower-pitched voice): someone needs to look into the possibility of L. Graham being behind or part of the CK event.
Who's L. Graham? What are these athletic
Speaker 229 (lower-pitched voice): scores? Where to find? Oh, you don't want to look at mine. It's the CrossFit Open. It's an annual competition. It takes place over three
Speaker 226: weeks. One workout per week. Everybody puts
Speaker 129 (lower-pitched voice): their score in by Monday night. Your humble host is doodooing the bed this year. Way too much time podcasting.
Speaker 239 (lower-pitched voice): Not nearly enough time working out. It's
Speaker 6: catching up to them.
uh
Speaker 277: baron bad cop looks good back to seeing christ thank you please give a shout out to my son wade we love you yes
Speaker 41: go see
Speaker 277: go see
Speaker 41: the lord go see the lord um what
up wade
Speaker 41: pages is it page
i
Speaker 316: can't pronounce it
Speaker 129 (lower-pitched voice): last time uh that last name
but page your son
Speaker 129 (lower-pitched voice): wade is probably brilliant if he's watching
very high
Speaker 239 (lower-pitched voice): iq outfit here
Speaker 239 (lower-pitched voice): Sorry for the upcoming Indiana loss in Bloomington, November 14, 2026. This is the year fight on.
Sound
Speaker 15 (lower-pitched voice): like a
USC fan
Speaker 15 (lower-pitched voice): or something.
Please watch out,
Speaker 15 (lower-pitched voice): Charlie Kirk. Operation 220 part five.
I don't know what that
Speaker 326: means. I
know you said you weren't
Speaker 326: putting anyone in the frame, but I
Speaker 226: think Candace deserves a spot.
Speaker 226: Yeah, I think it's its own statement right now.
I mean, I might
Speaker 226: eventually put somebody up there.
But right
Speaker 226: now, it's its own statement.
CK could have
Speaker 327: waited to run for office against JD. Ooh, could have.
Why is USVI House
Speaker 327: delegate Stacey
Speaker 254 (lower-pitched voice): Plaskett, who texted with Einstein while on
the House
Speaker 254 (lower-pitched voice): committee, avoided testimony? I don't know. I'm
not in charge of the
Speaker 254 (lower-pitched voice): House committee that's taken testimony.
Please
Speaker 254 (lower-pitched voice): listen to the
Speaker 224: first minute of Raw Thoughts. Man, if I listened to everything you guys told me to listen to, I wouldn't be able to do a podcast. I'd just sit around listening to shows all day. Watching, reading, listening. I would have no
Speaker 227: time to podcast. I
mean, it
Speaker 227: takes hours to put the show together every day. And then I can do a show for three or four hours. I'll think
Speaker 114 (lower-pitched voice): about it. I'll think about it. He doesn't even start going after Einstein people until 140. But I think the first minute would convince you to listen to the rest of the show.
Speaker 240 (lower-pitched voice): Oh, it's a song.
Speaker 239 (lower-pitched voice): somebody just made a super chat about their family going to Iran this pisses me off like nothing else right now I'm so sorry been there done that and it blanking thugs
yeah looked at
Speaker 122 (lower-pitched voice): merch still no women's v-neck yeah we talked about that we're working on that the first rollout
Speaker 239 (lower-pitched voice): is is limited for a reason but we have talked about that I brought it
Speaker 305: up to Nurse Casey on the agenda
sending
Speaker 305: love and prayers to all military and their families my mc
Speaker 240 (lower-pitched voice): son has avoided war deployment for six years with standing orders for other ops christ is king christ is king indeed i hope he continues that stellar streak bella
baron i'm 17
Speaker 96: years old i really like listening to your show like being part of this high q outfit here are you going to try to find out who made the vance kirk website yeah of course i don't know that we'll be able to i mean they put
Speaker 180 (lower-pitched voice): privacy there for a reason but yeah of course
Speaker 180 (lower-pitched voice): And thanks for listening, Matthew. You sound like a very high IQ 17-year-old. You've got a bright future ahead of
you. And Hex says
Speaker 240 (lower-pitched voice): confirmation hearings he swore to
not
Speaker 186 (lower-pitched voice): sending our men and women to battle for needless war. So now he seems so overboard in his statement for non-just war. So why not just resign? Good question. Why was he confirmed in the first place?
Please don't push
Speaker 186 (lower-pitched voice): us Canadians out, Baron. We need you. I'll send you real
Speaker 91: maple syrup if I have to.
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
I love
Speaker 91: your show and our awesome community.
Speaker 91: the community. I love the jury. The members of the
Speaker 114 (lower-pitched voice): jury are phenomenal. It makes it
Speaker 229 (lower-pitched voice): so fun to show up here. Real maple syrup will go a long way. If you knew how much real maple syrup we used
Speaker 218: in this house, my kids do not eat my diet. They eat a lot of pancakes and waffles and stuff like that for breakfast
with real
Speaker 218: 100% maple
Speaker 239 (lower-pitched voice): syrup of the Canadian variety with some Vermont thrown in it.
that would go a
Speaker 328: long way. Oswald
was
Speaker 129 (lower-pitched voice): just the same with communism as a patsy. Easy target, no internet at the time. Also, I find Liberty University questionable as a bona fide uni.
Speaker 281 (lower-pitched voice): No, I think Liberty has legitimate degrees and legitimate programs. I've met some
Speaker 329: Liberty grads who are very astute. But
that
Speaker 129 (lower-pitched voice): doesn't mean everything they do is legitimate or bona fide.
Speaker 11: 202 new potential patsies. That's right. If you don't put their name out there, we don't know if they're patsies. You're picking up. You're wearing
Speaker 125: your Real Baron podcast glasses and you're looking at the news the way I look at the news. Oh,
look, there's
Speaker 125: news. Here's
what it
Speaker 330: means. Oh,
Speaker 331: look, more news. Here's
what
Speaker 330: it means.
do
Speaker 273: they just have another weapon of mass destruction to dig up in iran allegedly yeah
i do think there's something to this
Speaker 273: ancient tech and ancient sites theory i do
uh love your work sir the guys at
Speaker 186 (lower-pitched voice): tpusa
Speaker 240 (lower-pitched voice): are so repulsive and gross agreed and that's not even getting onto their politics or
lying it's
Speaker 332: just looking at them i'm kidding
Speaker 227: andrew You're a handsome man.
maybe the
Speaker 227: only one there, but that's okay. Okay. I
would love
Speaker 277: to see Andrew's history and you know, there's nothing Christian about it. I think he was, I think it was raised in the faith. I just don't know that it's stuck. Coach
Colin
Speaker 114 (lower-pitched voice): today, eight, 10 intro into video, Frank T, MMC, Rob MC talking about Vance Kirk, 2028
Speaker 185: podcast was a week after Charlie Kirk Memorial. They could not stop smiling. I
need to
Speaker 185: check that
Speaker 254 (lower-pitched voice): out.
Speaker 254 (lower-pitched voice): With the time change and everything, I did not have a chance to watch his
Speaker 278 (lower-pitched voice): show today. I slept a little longer, and I didn't do too. How do I gift a membership?
I think you go, and
Speaker 321: instead of doing like a chat or a super chat, it gives you the opportunity to gift memberships. I think it's one of the options.
If haven't yet, screenshot EK and
Speaker 240 (lower-pitched voice): others' LinkedIn backgrounds, history, et cetera. Deleted old
Speaker 185: Charlie videos, and they'll try to delete their own professional credentials. I did better than that. Daisy had the presence of mind to realize I had put it up on the
screen.
And
Speaker 13: they changed it after the fact, dishonest, lying liars who lie,
allegedly, in
Speaker 333: my opinion.
Speaker 334: Do
you think Vance is aware of
Speaker 334: the Vance Kirk ticket? I don't know.
You're
Speaker 164: right. That would make it even worse if he was. Trump
Speaker 229 (lower-pitched voice): just said, Iran, give up. We're going to blow up the face of the earth. Yeah, right. We're lucky. Nothing has landed on U.S. soil. Crisis king. God bless. Crisis king indeed.
Speaker 229 (lower-pitched voice): Obviously, there are
Speaker 169: Trump cabinet members worried that something could land on U.S. soil. They are begging to have their underground nuclear bunkers built and built quickly. Barron, long-time listener
Speaker 224: and fan, you're calling Tilly in your accent and bringing her on camera was worth a super jet.
Go Max
Speaker 224: Barron, did I
call
Speaker 36: her with an accent? I'm going to have to go back and listen to that now. Now I'm self-conscious. I'll
never call
Speaker 36: my dog again on this show.
Speaker 108: Counselor.
How
Speaker 108: does a live video become demonetized in 9-11? Do they demonetize that video?
They just
Speaker 108: turn it off.
I've had a few done
Speaker 37: that way.
And the danger
Speaker 37: isn't that you're not going to make money on it.
The danger
Speaker 229 (lower-pitched voice): is when they demonetize it, it kind of puts a tab on your...
it puts
Speaker 114 (lower-pitched voice): your
Speaker 26 (lower-pitched voice): channel on notice. You get a little closer look. That's part one. Part two is they don't push out demonetized videos. It doesn't show up in people's feeds. You
Speaker 224: got to go looking for them because they only want to put videos in front of people they can sell ads on.
I'm going to look at the
Speaker 335: grumblers.
Speaker 336: We
have grumblers
Speaker 336: over there itching to be heard. I
look at you
Speaker 251: guys.
i don't see any grumblers i see
Speaker 337: grumblers oh
there's a
Speaker 337: grumbler i don't
give a
Speaker 45: dumb is this you no the department of war actions sound like pam shouting
the dow
Speaker 45: the dow is over 50 000 the jeffrey files are not in iran but securing
Speaker 226: stealing venezuela's oil
Speaker 250 (lower-pitched voice): helped circle back america you can't say circle circle back i say circle back.
Speaker 250 (lower-pitched voice): E.K. used to stop the plug vicariously, use the evil stop to plug vicariously Charlie's book. Oh, I see. Stop in the name of. Barron,
if we
Speaker 287: end up officially at war with Iran, can a wartime president suspend an election, thus keeping Trump in
Speaker 180 (lower-pitched voice): office for a third term? Interesting thought. I don't think so. I mean, Lincoln had an election in the middle of the Civil War and half
Speaker 199: the states didn't even participate. I don't know. Thank
you for
Speaker 199: that generous contribution, Tracy.
Or
Speaker 199: trace, I'm not sure which.
I'm not
Speaker 226: good at spelling.
I'm not good
Speaker 226: at pronouncing, I'll say that. I
was in Desert Shield
Speaker 226: Storm. My son was in Afghanistan. We're coming up on three generations in Middle Eastern wars, keeping troops in prayers.
Christ is
Speaker 275 (lower-pitched voice): king indeed.
See, I look at the
Speaker 275 (lower-pitched voice): grumblers. Y'all act like I don't. I love you people.
Don't bring you
Speaker 275 (lower-pitched voice): guys over there.
Speaker 122 (lower-pitched voice): uh baron israel was behind butler pa wiggle in your seat for yes stay still for the rest of the show for no i honestly
Speaker 326: i don't think so um that that was not my conclusion that i drew
Speaker 239 (lower-pitched voice): re-watched joe rogan episode 1125 with candace prophetic she was young brave and steadfast salt of the earth it's relevant to the case talks about charlie a ton more than the clip that's circulating i'll
go back
Speaker 239 (lower-pitched voice): and watch that i haven't watched that in years i
watched it
Speaker 239 (lower-pitched voice): when it came out but That was years ago. How many years ago was that? Three, four, five years ago?
As a
Speaker 239 (lower-pitched voice): former homeschooler, I feel attacked by TPSA. Where were they when I was a teen in
Speaker 338: 2001? Charlie was, how old was he,
13 or
Speaker 338: something? They
weren't
Speaker 180 (lower-pitched voice): around. Mentioning missing kids, those kids in Maui during the fire, still no word. Ooh, that's a good point. That's
a good
Speaker 180 (lower-pitched voice): point. Can you do a members only when we look into some of these
Speaker 218: tips and see how you and Daisy investigate leads and help?
Speaker 218: Daisy and I talked about that. I think
it would be
Speaker 114 (lower-pitched voice): boring. A lot of the research is very boring, very tedious. So that wouldn't make an exciting show at all. The second thing
Speaker 52: is, it's more
of a
Speaker 52: curiosity thing. It's not something that can be taught necessarily. It's something that as you observe and you see the curiosity in action, then I feel like you know what
to go
Speaker 52: look for. But just to...
Have
Speaker 52: someone say,
Speaker 239 (lower-pitched voice): here's how you search deed records in Ohio. Here's how you search birth records in Arkansas. Here's how you search. I mean, I'm not sure that makes
a good show. But to have
Speaker 239 (lower-pitched voice): someone
Speaker 240 (lower-pitched voice): that has the curiosity to go, wait a minute, I bet if we find deed records in Ohio, it'll give
us names
Speaker 240 (lower-pitched voice): that'll
Speaker 185: put us onto this, that'll help us draw the connection, that'll help us close. You know, that's just
a level
Speaker 185: of curiosity that can't be taught. Just got to be observed and mimicked.
I made
Speaker 33: spicy vodka pasta for dinner to eat while we watched Baron High IQ and High Calorie Outfit. I
had
Speaker 31 (lower-pitched voice): pasta today. It was a gluten-free pasta, but it was delicious. Mrs. Coleman made a nice tomato sauce to go with it. It was wonderful. I
went to Jayco in
Speaker 240 (lower-pitched voice): September 2015 with a couple of friends, one Israeli that planned the trip. There are a ton of Israeli hostels there. We stayed
in
Speaker 180 (lower-pitched voice): one. Always wondered why there were so many there. Now it's making more sense.
Speaker 147: Oh, my goodness.
Speaker 147: that's an interesting data point thank you for sharing that that's something that needs to be looked into
i used to be addicted
Speaker 240 (lower-pitched voice): to loud earth crowder he was sanity every morning during biden years now it's you and candace and i don't know what happened to crowder but i still don't recognize him anymore but i don't
Speaker 311 (lower-pitched voice): recognize him um i don't
know what happened
Speaker 311 (lower-pitched voice): to him
he had that spat
Speaker 311 (lower-pitched voice): with his wife and he's not been the same
Speaker 114 (lower-pitched voice): since
All
Speaker 114 (lower-pitched voice): GoDaddy domain parking is in Scottsdale. Oh, that makes sense. That helps answer that question.
Can you talk
Speaker 305: about your favorite moments during the Father Ripperger on
Speaker 285: Sean? It is the reason I attended my first mass this morning. Favorite moments? I did watch it.
If you've ever
Speaker 339: watched...
if you've
Speaker 339: ever watched The Exorcist Files, but not watched, listened
Speaker 31 (lower-pitched voice): to The Exorcist Files on Spotify, a
lot of what he
Speaker 129 (lower-pitched voice): said was kind of rehash. He
and Father
Speaker 129 (lower-pitched voice): Carlos Martins do
very
Speaker 281 (lower-pitched voice): similar ministries. And Father Carlos Martins is the host of The Exorcist Files. And so I don't
Speaker 226: know that I have a favorite moment Thank
you.
I think
Speaker 226: watching
Speaker 318 (lower-pitched voice): Sean's questions were very good because he normally doesn't do a good job of follow-up questions, but he actually did do some really good follow-up questions like on particular topics,
Speaker 240 (lower-pitched voice): sexual sins, lying, and listen to Father Ripperger talk about the impact those sins have in
Speaker 305: terms of opening up your soul for use,
Speaker 225 (lower-pitched voice): occupation.
Speaker 225 (lower-pitched voice): I think was a very enlightening refresher, perhaps. But yeah.
Speaker 26 (lower-pitched voice): Baron, your Charlie clip. Look
at his
Speaker 26 (lower-pitched voice): wedding ring. I noticed it was on his middle finger.
It was not on his
Speaker 26 (lower-pitched voice): ring finger.
But he moved around
Speaker 218: a lot. He played with that thing a lot. Actually, let's see if she responded.
Not
Speaker 340: yet.
I
Speaker 240 (lower-pitched voice): actually asked a friend who would have seen Charlie's wedding ring up close. What is the wedding ring? I can't find an up-close image of it. It looks like a signet ring of some sort, but I don't know why that would be his wedding ring. I'm
the girl with the
Speaker 129 (lower-pitched voice): info on Vegas
Speaker 229 (lower-pitched voice): shooting, including pick a phone case. Shout out of my hand. I'm stupid and don't know how to share. I'll
Speaker 318 (lower-pitched voice): give my number. Don't give your number. Hold on, hold on,
Speaker 341: hold on, hold
on, hold on.
real
Speaker 318 (lower-pitched voice): baron podcast at gmail.com real baron podcast at gmail.com oh you're saying you don't know how to share it with me well
Speaker 233 (lower-pitched voice): email me and we'll work it out we'll do a screen share or something you don't
have to give me
Speaker 233 (lower-pitched voice): um but
email me
Speaker 233 (lower-pitched voice): say and put like whatever
Speaker 242: in there
it's not
Speaker 242: out of my hand that's
scary that is
Speaker 108: really scary uh again edge
Speaker 108: I'm in Bean Footage's camp. Let's go to Tombstone. I
Speaker 114 (lower-pitched voice): mentioned a reckoning in a previous chat, and I'm serious.
How to
Speaker 114 (lower-pitched voice): initiate an investigation in TPSA? Her. Why haven't they? Well, A, we don't know that they haven't.
Maybe it led to 202
Speaker 239 (lower-pitched voice): arrests in Scottsdale. I don't know. But I, at
some point, a
Speaker 239 (lower-pitched voice): reckoning is due.
No wedding
Speaker 342: ring on CK725. EK equals Philly's new long game.
I have
Speaker 268: to look at that clip again. I saw he had a wedding ring on, it just was on his middle finger, that clip I played. Happy
Speaker 226: Sunday, Baron. Have you read Zechariah Sitchin's book about ancient astronauts? Humans are alien ape hybrids. Please pray for my 16-year-old Desmond having lots of angst and behavior issues. St. John Bosco, pray for
Speaker 221 (lower-pitched voice): us. I've not read his book, but I've heard a lot about it. I don't buy the ancient human-alien-ape hybrid theory.
Speaker 221 (lower-pitched voice): but I do buy that demons have been visiting humanity for a
Speaker 343: long time under the guise of aliens and whatnot. True
Speaker 308: Oddity, I built a large system that I watch you on. Recently rebuilt 320
Speaker 266 (lower-pitched voice): inches of monitor, twin water-cooled I-7s. Counselor, only your podcast crashes my browsers. Just odd. I
didn't
Speaker 185: know that, but that's
a heck
Speaker 185: of a setup. I'll
be a
Speaker 185: Huckleberry.
So
Speaker 129 (lower-pitched voice): being here with you, Candace, Coach, Lionel, et cetera, is more than fortuitous. Yes, I can quote the whole movie. Same. I've quoted
it on the record
Speaker 344: before in court cases, and nobody knew I was quoting it.
Someone asked me
Speaker 281 (lower-pitched voice): about something.
Speaker 114 (lower-pitched voice): I said, well, that's the rumor. And others. And others.
Speaker 114 (lower-pitched voice): Tyler Boyer lost a lot of weight in the last year. I
wonder if
Speaker 114 (lower-pitched voice): the stress of all this had something to do with it. Just an observation. Either that or
Speaker 305: Wegovy.
Or what's the
Speaker 305: big one everybody takes? I
can't
Speaker 226: remember. But the weight loss shot. I think that probably is it also. You
got to have a
Speaker 226: conscience to have a, to feel guilt. For mods, maybe they can help my secrets. You have secrets?
I
Speaker 226: covet everyone's prayers. I feel comfortable asking since this is a show that has a heart for sobriety. Kamar, my brother, will
Speaker 25: start his 12-year sentence for DUI rec. Everyone was okay. My brother has a wife, 13-year-old, and 3-year-old. Oh,
Speaker 345: man. 12-year sentence?
Speaker 346: That is ludicrously long. I'm sorry to hear that. I'll
pray for you
Speaker 328: guys.
That's a
Speaker 328: long sentence for DUI.
Just
Speaker 321: happy with the fellow pickup truck.
You got a W
Speaker 321: sticker
Speaker 114 (lower-pitched voice): on it?
More, I
Speaker 114 (lower-pitched voice): watched the change in Trump stance. A.D. Kirk, I believe they used that to scare him into this. I think
there
Speaker 281 (lower-pitched voice): was a there there. They
would have
Speaker 281 (lower-pitched voice): used it during the election. Oh, if there was a there
Speaker 347: there, they would
have used it.
Speaker 281 (lower-pitched voice): Maybe,
Speaker 348: maybe. I don't discount that entirely.
Have you
Speaker 164: considered that Charlie had to fake his death oath due to threats but could have
Speaker 123: took him out in the back of the car? Oh, have I considered Charlie set up to fake his death? No. I have considered Charlie set up to fake
Speaker 114 (lower-pitched voice): an attack,
and then they
Speaker 114 (lower-pitched voice): used it to finish him off. I have considered that. I don't necessarily
Speaker 254 (lower-pitched voice): land on that,
but I have
Speaker 254 (lower-pitched voice): considered it
and put a lot
Speaker 254 (lower-pitched voice): of thought into it,
Speaker 349: frankly. I really
loved
Speaker 180 (lower-pitched voice): your opening statement, how you highlighted Charlie Kirk's position on current affairs.
Your
Speaker 180 (lower-pitched voice): investigative work is truly top-notch. Thank you for the fantastic show. Well, thank you for the fantastic compliment. I appreciate that.
Follow-up
Speaker 308: Excel timeline spreadsheet sent today to consolidate pageants, school, life with CK. I know you're behind. Just send it today. Yeah, we'll chat. If you send it today, I'll see you. Hey, man. Definitely makes sense that Vance would have had
Speaker 231: knowledge of the plan. Thoughts? Thank you. Maybe? I don't know that they would have to have his knowledge.
Candace
Speaker 229 (lower-pitched voice): owes you a George interview She says one a year Has not done one since the end of 24 Thank you, God bless you for your work Candace I'm
Speaker 143: asking First
I'm assuming
Speaker 143: you're watching And if you are I'm asking
But if you
Speaker 153: don't watch I will shamelessly text you at some point And ask you Ha ha ha ha
ha.
The
Speaker 153: domain doesn't imply belief or support in ability.
Betting on
Speaker 114 (lower-pitched voice): probability because candidates pay top money for domains, it's a literal business. I buy domains to flip as well. Another perspective. No, the domain is not definitive proof that there was some sort of inside effort with the Vance or Kirks
Speaker 240 (lower-pitched voice): to purchase this domain.
But the
Speaker 240 (lower-pitched voice): timing is suspicious. No doubt about it. Look at tpusa-faith.org.
Speaker 234 (lower-pitched voice): Same layout
Speaker 249 (lower-pitched voice): as Vance 2028. It's probably because it's just a holding thing, but I'll look. TPUSA tpusa-faith.org
Oh
Speaker 350: yeah, it is the same, isn't it?
I wonder if
Speaker 350: that's just a holding
Speaker 310: thing. The copyright's the same too. That would have been added.
Let
Speaker 351: me look
Speaker 226: at my GoDaddy hold, see if it looks the
same.
I've
Speaker 278 (lower-pitched voice): got several. Oh, yeah. My GoDaddy holding is the same, and I didn't buy the Vans Kirk 2028. So that doesn't sell me well.
Daisy,
Speaker 111: literally, Savage. I love you, Daisy. Yes, Savage. Oh, I
Speaker 353: didn't show that one. Sorry.
Speaker 354: Yes. Pete
Hegseth just ended
Speaker 355: 60 Minutes with, we are just at the beginning. Grand Jury definitely needs a discount on bunkers. Code Barron. Idaho for when you can.
Speaker 355: Brian K., a
Speaker 229 (lower-pitched voice): super patsy. The Brian Kohlberger case is
Speaker 356: very interesting to me because
of the
Speaker 356: idea that there was witness testimony that there was another person there.
Or witness
Speaker 226: statement, perhaps, is the proper way to say it. Y'all hear that? We
were
Speaker 254 (lower-pitched voice): talking about you. TPU is a cat. Their ears are burning. That's what we non-Yankees
Speaker 225 (lower-pitched voice): say. Black Dog is a no-Joe patrol. L-O-L. Love it. Christ is king.
Speaker 225 (lower-pitched voice): Amen. I
don't know
Speaker 114 (lower-pitched voice): who Black Dog is, but Christ is king indeed.
Kate Grand
Speaker 114 (lower-pitched voice): Rapids, AK does not seem intellectually capable of starting any overseas non-profit, but especially one as
sophisticated
Speaker 186 (lower-pitched voice): as trafficking. Do
you believe another
Speaker 186 (lower-pitched voice): entity fully created
Speaker 90 (lower-pitched voice): these and then simply found someone sick enough to
agree to
Speaker 90 (lower-pitched voice): be affiliated? You mean like her mom?
Thank you for that generous
Speaker 90 (lower-pitched voice): contribution, buddy.
Speaker 90 (lower-pitched voice): Ivan, the new ballroom includes a massive underground data center. New architect Shalom Baranis also built the Pentagon wedges 2 through 5 post 9-11. I didn't
know that about the
Speaker 90 (lower-pitched voice): architect. Do we have evidence on the data thing or is that just speculation? Why
would you put a data
Speaker 229 (lower-pitched voice): center there? Hi, Baron. Have you checked out Professor Jang's YouTube channel regarding U.S. losing Iran war, moving towards Pact Judea, Israel becoming global superpower?
Speaker 218: I hate to say it. His lectures are very compelling.
I'm
Speaker 218: wondering what you think. I used to watch his stuff, and I've watched a few here and there
after I
Speaker 218: quit watching. I feel like he has
Speaker 185: an agenda, and I can't quite put my finger
on it. My same reaction, man,
Speaker 114 (lower-pitched voice): saying this doo-doo pisses me off to no end.
The last live, you
Speaker 114 (lower-pitched voice): said you didn't know what Jesus really looked like. Someone did an AI of the Turin Shroud. I tweeted it to you. I've seen that. I've
seen that, but it
Speaker 114 (lower-pitched voice): looked like it took a lot of
Speaker 357: artistic license.
My
Speaker 357: husband is deployed for over a year now. Oh, I'm sorry to hear that. It's a long deployment these days. I mean, back in the World War I days, you'd be deployed three or four years. But these days, a year's
a
Speaker 286: long deployment. I hope he returns home safely and soon. JD
did say
Speaker 286: EK would make a great VP on Candace's pod. That
makes me judge his
Speaker 225 (lower-pitched voice): character.
Speaker 248: Erica Kirk equals Elizabeth Holmes.
There it
Speaker 248: goes. Elizabeth Holmes had an interesting tweet last night
where she
Speaker 248: was looking for an independent investigator to look into something. I responded to her.
And I never
Speaker 72 (lower-pitched voice): went back to look and see if she ever got back to what I'm doing now.
I forgot to
Speaker 72 (lower-pitched voice): look. Let's see. I'll
have to
Speaker 72 (lower-pitched voice): go. Oh, there it is.
I'll have to
Speaker 72 (lower-pitched voice): go through and find it.
Let's see if
Speaker 358: she responded. She
said something
Speaker 248: about tag the independent journalist who would look at it. And I was like, I'll look at it. What are you talking about? She suggested
it was
Speaker 317 (lower-pitched voice): dangerous. I wondered
if it
Speaker 317 (lower-pitched voice): had to do with my opening. Not
Speaker 240 (lower-pitched voice): like she saw my opening and
thought I
Speaker 240 (lower-pitched voice): needed to follow up on this. But if it was the same subject.
Speaker 240 (lower-pitched voice): uh psa for everyone bringing up the palm gun watch number 33 with
Speaker 84 (lower-pitched voice): blake bednards convincing stuff regarding brian harpole hard for me to believe anything else at this point um duly noted we had brian on to i mean we had blake on to talk about the episode have
you happened to see the
Speaker 238 (lower-pitched voice): music video released yesterday candace owens shabbat shalom daddy's home by ad fleet you got to check it out i have i thought it was phenomenal uh she
made
Speaker 229 (lower-pitched voice): candace amazing uh baron
I
Speaker 229 (lower-pitched voice): highly enjoy your show. Great work. And Daisy behind the curtain. And sometimes on the screen, if you guys are on the member shows, you'll get to hear from her from time to time.
Thank you for
Speaker 229 (lower-pitched voice): that contribution, brother.
You
Speaker 153: are hilarious as a high Q outfit, but you just did the Gary Blink after Daisy had you go EK LinkedIn education.
Speaker 321: First time super chat, but I haven't
Speaker 36: missed the show since October. Go back.
Yeah, I
Speaker 359: did, didn't I?
i'm
Speaker 36: behind got in late but baron calling the bunker guys one of the best things i've ever
Speaker 153: seen
had stand up junior
Speaker 153: things to do i would i i don't know that i would do stand up um i'm jealous
of those guys
Speaker 153: though because
Speaker 90 (lower-pitched voice): it looks like they're having so much fun up there
maybe jimmy
Speaker 90 (lower-pitched voice): door will have me along if he's ever in the southeast i'll go visit him and i'll do like a two-minute
set i've got
Speaker 90 (lower-pitched voice): one
Speaker 277: good joke i want to tell
Happy Sunday, Crisis
Speaker 277: King. Well, happy Sunday indeed. Thank you, Shoe Lady from Huntsville, Alabama. Very generous and kind. Who
are the
Speaker 185: friends, family that are from Utah?
Speaker 129 (lower-pitched voice): Erica mentions
in her
Speaker 129 (lower-pitched voice): wedding video. I don't know. Actually, it might be the, I know,
I do know
Speaker 129 (lower-pitched voice): actually. It's the
Carla in,
Speaker 84 (lower-pitched voice): Carla Solomon, I think is who it is. But I could be wrong about that, but I'm pretty sure I'm right about that.
I
Speaker 84 (lower-pitched voice): literally
Speaker 321: LOL'd when you said she calls you granddad. Yeah, she does. What's wrong with that? I'm
her
Speaker 360: granddad. She's
Speaker 318 (lower-pitched voice): technically my 16-year-old daughter's dog, but my 16-year-old daughter has
kind of gone
Speaker 318 (lower-pitched voice): full teen mom on the dog and
isn't really
Speaker 318 (lower-pitched voice): raising her.
She's
Speaker 361: been dumped
on
Speaker 362 (lower-pitched voice): grandma and granddad.
And
Speaker 362 (lower-pitched voice): grandma and granddad take good care of her. She sleeps in our room.
She growls at
Speaker 362 (lower-pitched voice): every bump in the night. You
wake up in
Speaker 362 (lower-pitched voice): the middle of the night, and you realize a bird just tapped on
the window
Speaker 362 (lower-pitched voice): or something.
Speaker 363: She's great,
Speaker 84 (lower-pitched voice): though. Great dog. CK
has firmly
Speaker 84 (lower-pitched voice): stated she was not interested or planning to run for president. Also, what are your thoughts on Mike Evans and Fawz, commissioning pastors? I don't know anything about that last
Speaker 168: sentence. The first sentence, I don't believe anything she says. Nothing. Nothing.
She
Speaker 168: also said she wasn't interested in pageants
and sort
Speaker 168: of did it against her will.
So count me
Speaker 168: among the Erica skeptics.
Charlie Kirk
Speaker 106: said he thought his stay-at-home wife
would be
Speaker 106: the next great president, eh? They genuinely think we're stupid. It's laugh-out-loud ridiculous. Yes, indeed, they
Speaker 25: do. Edge, because they do not recognize
Speaker 90 (lower-pitched voice): Christ's sacrificial offering of salvation or Christ as the high priest and they're done. Edge has a way with words.
Hope
Speaker 90 (lower-pitched voice): Candace sees every bit of proof of
what
Speaker 114 (lower-pitched voice): Devil Barbie just did on LinkedIn and does a show on it. Peeps need to know what a liar she is. Also, what's happening in the run is awful. BB equals devil. I
could
Speaker 317 (lower-pitched voice): make her aware of it. I could send it to her. But yeah, she's such a scam artist.
Assuming
Speaker 175: that's her. I mean, I'm assuming she has control over that page. Speaking to my Southern Georgia soul counselor. I'm trying. I'm trying.
Speaker 364: Are
you
Speaker 175: from Waycross?
Speaker 282: Albany, Georgia? Are you from Albany? Oh,
Speaker 114 (lower-pitched voice): sorry. James Comer said today Epstein victims turned into victimizers. Immediately thought that's what EK is.
Stay tuned. Stay
Speaker 365: tuned. There may be more coming down the pike.
Speaker 321: Rebuilding the temple isn't about furthering the cause of Christ. It's about bringing the end of times. Evangelical Zionism is a death cult. Heaven's gate on global
Speaker 366: scale.
Hard to disagree with any of that. EK Bible in
Speaker 36: 365 points to Proclaim 365 site. Proclaim Streetwear
Speaker 90 (lower-pitched voice): site was a separate site. Now all point to Proclaim 365 site. Kicker changed on 825. 25 per Leofold.
Speaker 367: Daisy, are you catching any of that?
We need to
Speaker 367: look at that.
I'm taking a picture. That's
Speaker 367: going to you.
Thank you. That's good information. If these
Speaker 52: pilots value their lives, they're going to keep quiet.
We have a way of protecting people. Thank you,
Speaker 180 (lower-pitched voice): Barron, for your views on Iran and connecting the dots to Charlie. It all resonates so
Speaker 114 (lower-pitched voice): loudly. Keep up your amazing work, you and your team. Yes, thank you.
We're
Speaker 114 (lower-pitched voice): doing our best out here. We're doing our best out here. I just don't understand why E.K. is lying about everything. Do you think she was MKUltrad,
Speaker 90 (lower-pitched voice): like Coach Colin thinks? Also worrying Prospect, more Muslim migrants who won't integrate into European culture. I
mean,
Speaker 218: anytime you dump a bunch of migrants, like a bunch,
Speaker 108: not a few here and there, but anytime you dump
a bunch, it's
Speaker 108: going to change the character of the country. Like if you dumped 30 million
Speaker 185: Christians in Iran, it would not be the Iran that the Iranian people love to live in.
Speaker 185: It just wouldn't.
It would fundamentally
Speaker 185: change the place.
And it's, so
Speaker 277: that's, I mean, but is that part of the plan?
You know, that part of the plan? I
Speaker 311 (lower-pitched voice): believe there's nothing we can do to bring about the
second coming
Speaker 311 (lower-pitched voice): of Jesus. Jesus will return on his time. Just shows the arrogance of the human
Speaker 291: race. Yeah.
Also, I also firmly
Speaker 95 (lower-pitched voice): believe Eric and Tyler had everything to do with Charlie's death, and they just showed their hand with all the VP stuff on 9-12.
Speaker 175: Yeah.
Speaker 175: Well, a couple things. One is,
it's an
Speaker 175: opinion. Two, we don't know for sure that they were the ones who reserved that
Speaker 25: website on 9-12, but we do know for sure he was the one saying that on 9-22 and 9-24. We do know that.
Literally the
Speaker 25: day after his memorial. Hey,
Speaker 90 (lower-pitched voice): Baron,
been practicing my
Speaker 90 (lower-pitched voice): steno skills with your
Speaker 11: opening statements. Appreciate the high IQ content. You
make a
Speaker 11: great record. Much aloha to you and your family. Thanks for all you do, and Daisy,
Speaker 229 (lower-pitched voice): too.
Speaker 229 (lower-pitched voice): um steno is uh incredibly complex when i used to give depositions or do trials and i would watch
Speaker 114 (lower-pitched voice): those typically ladies there were a
few men um
Speaker 114 (lower-pitched voice): but you know say i've seen a hundred stenographers 92 of them were women but they would just tap those buttons and the buttons don't have any numbers or letters or anything they just are there and they tap them in a pattern that makes sounds
it's fascinating
Speaker 114 (lower-pitched voice): it's truly fascinating i don't know how they do it my wife's aunt was a stenographer may still be
I don't
Speaker 114 (lower-pitched voice): know if she's retired yet or not.
USA
Speaker 25: has sent the Doomsday E4, was supporting AWACS that has an AI dead man switch. It's flying there now. It's
flying
Speaker 218: there? It's been flying. Well, we've had, well, there's several E4s, not only one, and they do
Speaker 317 (lower-pitched voice): fly a lot. The
other day,
Speaker 114 (lower-pitched voice): there
Speaker 317 (lower-pitched voice): were two in the air. That was a little unusual. I can look real quick.
Okay.
Speaker 369: and see what you're talking about. I
do not
Speaker 369: see the E4 in the air right now. But maybe it's
over the
Speaker 71 (lower-pitched voice): water. A lot of times when they're over the water, they turn
their transponder off. Or they don't broadcast. But
Speaker 73 (lower-pitched voice): thank you.
I'm
Speaker 114 (lower-pitched voice): fascinated by people who are fascinated by keeping track of planes because I look at them all day. From Quebec too, what about a picture of
Speaker 218: St. Michael on the back? Destroying Satan, continue the good job. We have two St. Michael icons in our house. So we're thoroughly St. Michaeled up at Club Coleman.
Enjoy full-time
Speaker 229 (lower-pitched voice): RBP and love watching this show with this great community. Thank you. I appreciate that.
Most
Speaker 238 (lower-pitched voice): evangelicals see Third Temple as signal of Antichrist. Yeah, that scares me.
That's bad theology. Have you watched
Speaker 218: Fallout on Amazon Prime? If not, you should. Then compare to the bunker manufacturer. I have seen that, yeah.
Speaker 229 (lower-pitched voice): Yeah.
Many
Speaker 90 (lower-pitched voice): intelligent, genuine people have been victim to partners we thought... Wait a minute, wait a minute, Fallout, Fallout. I thought I saw that on Netflix. Was that kind of the end-time
Speaker 84 (lower-pitched voice): show on Netflix about the couple that escaped with their daughter and had to bunk out with another couple, or is that some other movie? I'll check it out. Sounds like an interesting
Speaker 362 (lower-pitched voice): movie. Many intelligent, genuine people have been victim to partners we thought we knew. Until you live it, you can't comprehend your spouse could
be a
Speaker 267: demon. Well...
Speaker 267: demon's a strong word
and
Speaker 184: probably accurate probably
Speaker 123: accurate in this situation alright, just saying EK might be John Lovitz in drag
oh
that
Speaker 308: got me that made me laugh Charlie got played by Eric and his TPUSA staff so sad RIP Charlie we miss you what's
Speaker 299: sad is he hired these people in under trust and they took advantage of it that's what's
sad to me if it would help
Speaker 318 (lower-pitched voice): I can search physical family court records in Hennepin County Lori marriage divorce records let me know if something would be helpful emailed you last week
Speaker 256 (lower-pitched voice): did they get well I know Lori
Speaker 108: had was it Hennepin County I know Lori had a divorce in Minnesota Yeah.
I don't
Speaker 108: know if that was Hennemann County. Yeah, send me what you can
find.
Speaker 229 (lower-pitched voice): RealBaronPodcast, gmail.com.
Yes, you should
Speaker 229 (lower-pitched voice): have brought him up because every show he involves you and Candace. He wouldn't have a show without you.
Speaker 373: And
still only
Speaker 229 (lower-pitched voice): 9,000
Speaker 254 (lower-pitched voice): people watch. Common
Sense Show said Charlie filed
Speaker 122 (lower-pitched voice): for divorce three to four days before September 10th. He
Speaker 36: was also questioning his paternity. He must go watch. Unless they have proof, I'm not going to watch.
I'm not
Speaker 36: going to speculate on stuff like that.
You show me
Speaker 36: evidence, I'll be happy to entertain it.
Do you think
Speaker 286: the offer to take TPSA to the next level was in exchange for CK promoting regime change in Iran?
Speaker 374: Maybe. It could be. I don't know.
But Barron,
Speaker 25: I just sent you why reinstating temple worship would be a motive for Zionists. The email is titled, reinstating temple worship could perhaps also be the reason why Trump thinks he won't go to heaven. I'm
really
Speaker 129 (lower-pitched voice): weirded out by Trump saying that.
Like he
Speaker 129 (lower-pitched voice): doesn't think he's going to go to heaven.
If
Speaker 26 (lower-pitched voice): you believe
in
Speaker 186 (lower-pitched voice): heaven, granted, there's some people who don't. They're not going to be moved by what I'm about to say. But
if you do
Speaker 375: believe in it,
and you also believe in
Speaker 375: the alternative,
and you think you might not
Speaker 375: go, and
you think there's a
Speaker 136 (higher-pitched voice): way you could,
you should pursue
Speaker 143: that, the latter.
You
Speaker 143: should pursue that last option with everything you got.
If you think you
Speaker 23: might not go, and if you believe it, and
if you
Speaker 23: believe in the alternative, you should pursue going.
And if you don't,
Speaker 23: that bothers me. It bothers me a lot.
It's about
Speaker 124: Christianity. Russian is Orthodox. Christian Ukraine is SOS removed from Russia centuries ago.
thank
Speaker 366: you i don't know what this means no i don't know i mean i know what it means i
Speaker 226: don't understand the relevance nearly every adult has
ignored
Speaker 234 (lower-pitched voice): red flags early in relationships charlie was no exception doubt he ran a background check he once mentioned an interview he didn't handle his own
socials yeah
Speaker 234 (lower-pitched voice): that's
Speaker 376: telling
Speaker 377: erica's
Speaker 284: white camilla
oh
Speaker 317 (lower-pitched voice): gosh oh is she that bad camilla
Speaker 317 (lower-pitched voice): Uh, that golden voice of yours
Speaker 180 (lower-pitched voice): is so articulate that when I'm late to your live stream, I can clearly understand you 3x speed. Brilliant, sir. God bless you and yours. Well, thank you. That might just mean I talk slowly. Michael Jackson's They Don't Care
Speaker 229 (lower-pitched voice): About Us came on my YouTube feed. It's 20 years old. I didn't really understand it till now. Many people commenting on it. Yeah, they've edited it too.
That's a good
Speaker 226: theme song. Can't stand the parroting weasels at Turning point.
And why
Speaker 226: do they all have that nasally annoying Shapiro
Speaker 229 (lower-pitched voice): voice? Good call. If Char was Electro, wouldn't his hair have been poofed? Not necessarily. Not
Speaker 114 (lower-pitched voice): necessarily. That's
kind of
Speaker 114 (lower-pitched voice): a cartoon thing.
Media, let's
Speaker 114 (lower-pitched voice): get America to be emphatic to our cause. Let's tell them Moran has a million Christians that need America to rescue them. I'm a vet. In my opinion, praying for them is more beneficial than war.
Speaker 226: Hi, Baron.
Speaker 317 (lower-pitched voice): Might be off subject. I'm sorry if this has been talked about before. Frank Turk says that Catherine LeCastro flew in with Erica that day. That's a good piece of information. I didn't catch that. I
will look
Speaker 317 (lower-pitched voice): that up.
First, I got to know who
Speaker 317 (lower-pitched voice): she is.
Speaker 378: Yeah,
I don't know who that
Speaker 236: is. A multilingual and world-traveled Dominican Republic-born actress.
the
Speaker 243: hell was she doing with Erica? I felt miracles, I felt Jesus'
Speaker 114 (lower-pitched voice): mercy, excuse me, including CK's knowledge. Oh, sorry. I felt Jesus' mercies included limiting CK's knowledge of EK, if any at all.
Speaker 90 (lower-pitched voice): God protected his purposeful soldier in his own ways. It's possible God spared him the pain revelation of EK. It's possible. I believe Temple Gate is to force
Speaker 240 (lower-pitched voice): God's hand to
Speaker 234 (lower-pitched voice): promise We'll see
Speaker 122 (lower-pitched voice): you next
Speaker 240 (lower-pitched voice): time.
The
Speaker 234 (lower-pitched voice): land, since Judaism doesn't believe J.C. was the Messiah, made a new covenant, spiritual manipulation to grow richer, bigger, be corrupt.
But
Speaker 122 (lower-pitched voice): Barron, I need to talk to you. It's pertinent talking to the brains. The operation would be suffice. Well, email me. Tell me what you
want to
Speaker 122 (lower-pitched voice): say. I'll
Speaker 240 (lower-pitched voice): review it. Realbarronpodcast.gmail.com. Thank you for that generosity.
I don't
Speaker 240 (lower-pitched voice): think Charlie
Speaker 234 (lower-pitched voice): would participate in some fake neutralization attempt considering how he feared and shared this with others that he thought they were going to kill him and crush the king. That's a good data point, a great data point. And maybe he wouldn't have.
Maybe he
Speaker 267: wouldn't have at all.
Wasn't the Etsy Witches
Speaker 267: website created on 9-12 or 13 as well? I don't know. That's a good... See, this is why we do the show.
Speaker 72 (lower-pitched voice): Etsy... Oh, I can't delete that one because that's got the Catherine thing I need to
look at.
Speaker 249 (lower-pitched voice): etsy witches website creation date all right hey baron hey
Speaker 123: trick worm first time i've ever said trick worm in my life
uh erica got her
Speaker 123: bachelor's degree in puerto
Speaker 124: rico and her master's in china just saying go max crisis king i don't i've not heard that before crisis king indeed i've not heard that they think we're
dumb.
i've
Speaker 124: heard that
in my research
Speaker 239 (lower-pitched voice): no less than five updates creations of ek's grandpa obituaries and grave marker no obit for grandma
ken's parents i
Speaker 114 (lower-pitched voice): don't know how relevant but odd that's odd is
it true the ring
Speaker 114 (lower-pitched voice): charlie was wearing on 9 10 was a hinge ring
was that his
Speaker 114 (lower-pitched voice): wedding ring that's what i keep hearing that it was a hinge ring and that was
his wedding ring my
Speaker 311 (lower-pitched voice): super chat keeps getting blocked i can't say what i want to say browser has crashed several times error after error
Speaker 311 (lower-pitched voice): email it, realbaronpodcastgmail.com. I want to know what you're saying
Speaker 114 (lower-pitched voice): that's causing it to crash. I agree, Ron, yes, but in my opinion, there's a significant reason they chose 910. If
you want more info on the
Speaker 240 (lower-pitched voice): data center, the Dre dossier is a high IQ channel. I'd rather you just
Speaker 114 (lower-pitched voice): send me an email with the evidence. That way I don't have
to go
Speaker 114 (lower-pitched voice): look at some channel and watch a bunch of episodes because I don't have time. Good evening and, well, bye. Also another good
Speaker 21: quote from Tombstone.
Speaker 21: Thank you, Edge. Please, George. Yes, it would
be such
Speaker 21: a good interview.
So good. How is
Speaker 226: that group like us of approximately 200,000 cannot get in touch with anyone at Justice Department and demand a real CK investigation? How can we be
Speaker 114 (lower-pitched voice): ignored? They don't care about you.
They don't really care
Speaker 114 (lower-pitched voice): about us.
The
Speaker 114 (lower-pitched voice): movie Heads of State
Speaker 186 (lower-pitched voice): struck me as predictive programming. It's a
plot to
Speaker 186 (lower-pitched voice): kill POTUS and the UK Prime Minister. Spoiler alert, the villain ends up
Speaker 380: being the VP and her name is Elizabeth Kirk.
That's kind of terrifying. Love the
Speaker 123: hat. Thank you, bad cop. Go Max, have you heard that Charlie was not wearing his wedding ring during
Speaker 90 (lower-pitched voice): his last episode ties into missing wedding picture? No, I
need to
Speaker 90 (lower-pitched voice): look at that. I haven't heard that.
Speaker 38: Kayla Castro on Charlie's show with Megyn Kelly. I'll look at it. I'll look at it. I believe you. I believe you. All right, guys, we've reached that time. That time that comes every night when
Speaker 52: we must bid adieu.
But not
Speaker 52: before. I tell you to like, subscribe,
Speaker 90 (lower-pitched voice): click notifications, share with your friends. Don't feed the trolls on Twitter. Just,
I appreciate
Speaker 240 (lower-pitched voice): your support. I genuinely do. But
all you're
Speaker 226: doing is giving them interactions.
You
Speaker 226: know, there's no reason for it. But I do appreciate your support. I went over there and read it and hearted
a bunch of
Speaker 226: the replies. But yeah, happy to have you guys here for yet another
Speaker 175: night. We'll be back tomorrow night. Tomorrow night, probably in the six o'clock range, give or take, maybe as late as seven, but usually try to go around six. And in the meantime, don't forget, don't you ever forget.
Jesus loves
Speaker 175: you.
Speaker 175: Thank you guys. Have a wonderful night. Get a good night's sleep. It's daylight savings time. A lot of people have heart attacks this time of year because
Speaker 308: their bodies are not sleeping enough to adjust. So make sure you get in bed early tonight, even though you don't feel like it's 830 central time. It is. So make sure whatever time you go to bed, make sure you get in bed at the normal time and
get a
Speaker 308: full night's sleep. And see you soon. Jesus loves you.